Chapter 863: Red-Named Monster, Please Stop!

The dynasty's search mission in the Shattered Star Ring lasted longer than anyone expected. Three months went by in a flash, and the Beyond Grade As of the dynasty were still waiting there.

However, the dynasty's pursuit mission did not yield many results as a Beyond Grade A in disguise was far too nimble. Over the past three months, the dynasty had only caught many of the Arcane Church's spies and a few suspected traces of Sagman and the others. The Beyond Grade As were unable to find any of the Arcane Church's Beyond Grade As when they took action.

These Arcane Church's spies were naturally interrogated and were unable to keep any secrets under the various methods of the Universal Civilizations. However, the Arcane Church had various preventive measures up their sleeves, and these spies did not know the exact locations of Sagman and the others. They only headed to a certain location at a certain time, and some of these messages were there as a smokescreen for the dynasty. The amount of useful information was extremely little.

When the Arcane Church decided to make use of their spies in the Shattered Star Ring, they were prepared to lose them.

Apart from the Shattered Star Ring, the Crimson Dynasty and Arcane Church were not idle in the other Star Fields. Plenty of skirmishes had broken out between the two over the past three months, and the relationship between the two was extremely tense.

In summary, the Crimson Dynasty ferociously sought an explanation, but the Arcane Church refused to give in. The way the outside world saw it, war was about to break out.

But as upper echelons of the dynasty, Han Xiao and the others received inside news from Tarrokov. The Arcane Church had privately contacted the Crimson Dynasty, and both parties were already discussing how to settle this matter. The two parties were only putting on a show for the outside world and would not actually end up fighting.

The Arcane Church also had no choice but to give in. Two of their Beyond Grade As had been captured by the dynasty, and they had to find a way to get them back. If not, none of their allies would be willing to fight for them in the future. The party that the Arcane Church hated the most was not the Crimson Dynasty but the Federation of Light.

The actions of the Federation of Light in the Shattered Star Ring couldn't be hidden from the Arcane Church. The Federation of Light tried to hit them when they were down and even aided the dynasty in searching for Sagman and the others. Although the cooperation between both parties was only limited to the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, the Arcane Church was still furious.

The Shattered Star Ring was the Federation of Light's territory, and they had deep foundations. Their intervention had resulted in many of the Arcane Church's spies being exposed.

The conflicts between the civilizations were mainly for benefits, and supporting Beyond Grade As was also for this reason. The Arcane Church hoped to use diplomacy to resolve this problem and pay a ransom for Dylan and Mercer.

The army and various weapons were the basic strength of a civilization, and a Beyond Grade A was like a special weapon that served as a powerful deterrent. In the exploration era, the Beyond Grade As that were captured would either be converted to their own use or executed.

However, the Galaxy Calendar era was more peaceful than before, and the galactic civilizations were currently in a state of peace. No one was capable of shaking the position of the three Universal Civilizations, and the military activities of the past gradually became diplomacy.

Thus, it was not impossible to pay a ransom. As long as one was willing to pay a sufficient price, everything could be discussed. The three Universal Civilizations would see their Beyond Grade As fall into enemy hands from time to time, and there was thus a tacit agreement between the three civilizations and also an unspoken rule. However, this unspoken rule was only restricted to the three Universal Civilizations. The Super Star Cluster Civilizations did not have such a privilege.

Han Xiao could not be bothered with that. He had already received his Contribution Points, and since he handed the captive over, the dynasty could choose to do whatever they wanted.

He had remained within the headquarters of the Black Star Army during the past three months, and even if he was summoned by the dynasty, he would only send Psionic Prime and his mechanical army out.

Maximiler was the same as him and also sent out his long-distance troops. The best advantage of this was that he could slack at home.

Maximiler was a Mechanic that belonged to the Energy Branch, and he chose to stay at the Black Star Army so that he can have an exchange with Han Xiao. Both parties had a good conversation with each other over the past three months and became much closer.

Han Xiao originally thought that Ames would come and look for him, but Ames returned to Floating Dragon Island after destroying the stargate and did not mention the matter again. She had a carefree attitude.

What a reliable ally.

Over the past few months, Han Xiao had spent most of his time crafting new machines. With his new [Endless Material Combination] knowledge, he was able to create many baffling materials to increase the attributes of his machines. The strength of his mechanical army would be increased this way, and he would also pose a greater threat to Beyond Grade A Supers.

Manison was able to deal with Beyond Grade As even with his long-distance troops, and he could fight many different Beyond Grade As at different locations. That was the true battle tactic of a Mechanic, and Han Xiao was still lacking in this respect. However, he still had a long time to accumulate his strength. After all, he had only been a Beyond Grade A Super for around a year.

After the Planet Lighthouse battle, the damage to his mechanical army was not small. If not for his mechanical army restraining the enemy, they would all have been in danger for sure. Thus, Han Xiao made use of this opportunity to create a new batch of machines.

The endless stream of Enas from exploring the Flickering World came into Han Xiao's pockets, so Han Xiao was extremely wealthy. One of the reasons he had created such a large organization was so that he would not need to worry about the cost of constructing machines.

The three new Apostle Weapon slots were given to Silver Flash, Giant King Kong, and Mad Sky Hunter, who each had their own weapons and special attributes.

Silver Flash's long-distance attack was improved, and his weapon was a transformable Planetary Obliteration Cannon called [Spreader of Destruction].

Giant King Kong was like a main tank meat shield with his weapon being strengthened armor. It could be taken off like ordinary armor and could even be transformed into a gigantic shield. It also had the ability to repair itself and was called [Divine Giant Armor].

Mad Sky Hunter was a beast-shaped Mechanical Life, and his body structure was different compared to the others. He had a pair of wings stuck on his back, which had a length of ten meters when fully opened, and he looked like the combination of a leopard, wolf, eagle, and dragon. His weapon was a strengthened hyperdrive module which gave him the ability to flicker and was called [Hunting Module].

Han Xiao gave the slots of the Apostle Weapon to the Mechanical Lives that were created earlier on. They had grown for a period of time already and were more reliable. Furthermore, he tried to give the slots to the different models of Mechanical Lives so that his Apostle Weapons would have a greater variety.

Over the past three months, Han Xiao had released a faction mission that got many of the players to look around the Shattered Star Ring.

An unexplored Star Field would not have as much activity as the discovered universe. After staying in the Flickering World for such a long time, the players could truly feel the silence of the vast universe. They would usually travel for a few Star Zones without seeing anybody, and it was easy for them to feel just how small they were in the universe. They could have a change of pace after returning to the Shattered Star Ring, and many of the players gradually became energetic again.

Exploring a new Star Field naturally had its own benefits, and the players knew that the Flickering World was definitely a huge event. However, after exploring the Flickering World for some time, the sense of novelty was gone, and a portion of them preferred to remain in the Shattered Star Ring. There were numerous NPCs in the Shattered Star Ring with plenty of different things to do.

Han Xiao would not force the players to do anything. Although he always joked that the players were laborers, he was extremely clear about the players' personality. Sometimes, their benefits would have to give way to their interests, and this was what the majority of players chased after.

He would not restrict the players' freedom and would only issue a mission and the relevant reward. As for whether or not the players wanted to complete the mission, it did not have anything to do with him. After all, they players still did not know that the Flickering World would become the most exciting place in the universe during the next version.

On the forums, Bun-Hit-Dog transformed the battle on Planet Lighthouse into a video to let all the players who were not present watch it to their heart's content.

All the players were extremely curious and shocked after watching the video. This was the battle between eleven Beyond Grade As, and it was the first time the players had witnessed such a scene.

Something worth mentioning was that Han Xiao began selling the Dungeon Crystal in the faction store after the battle. Although the dungeon was not one that the players could complete at their current level, he was certain that the players' curiosity would overcome them, and this was a good business opportunity.

Indeed, the sales of the Dungeon Crystal were extremely high, and the average survival time of the players was about forty-seven seconds.

The players were all curious about the strength of a Beyond Grade A and wanted to know the true strength of their captain. The players now had a deep understanding of this.

The ordinary cannon fodder mechanical soldiers that had the boost of the Mechanical Force was like a boss-level monster to the players. They could easily dice the players up like vegetables, and the players did not even have the ability to fight back.

Looking at the battlefield, there were millions of such mechanical soldiers...

After going through this bitter journey, the players were clear about Han Xiao's strength.

Ever since Version 1.0, Black Star's danger level had always been 'Fatally Dangerous' because the highest danger level had been limited to 'Fatally Dangerous'.

Knock! Knock!

Someone knocked on the door of the machinery modification room, and Han Xiao, who was currently adjusting his assembly line, stopped working.

Phillip opened the door, and Lagi and a Forbidden Sorcerer clad in red robes walked in.

"Paying my respects to Your Excellency Black Star." The Forbidden Sorcerer bowed. "Master Austin sent me to collect the materials."

"Alright, I have already prepared them. Wait a moment. I will get some men to help you carry it onto your spaceship."

Han Xiao then waved his hands and got Phillip to contact the logistics department to prepare a few cartons of amber balls for the other party.

This was one of the conditions that he and Austin had agreed upon. Since the darn old man had kept his promise, he would not go back on his word.

The Forbidden Sorcerer then bowed and took his leave.

Han Xiao was about to get back to work but realized that Lagi was still standing by the side without the intention to leave.

"Why are you still here?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"You despise me?" Upon hearing that, Lagi spoke with a bitter expression. "Indeed, someone like me will never be liked no matter where I go. Even my boss doesn't like me. I'd better jump ship..."

"Nonsense. Since when did I despise you?"

Han Xiao felt his head ache and said with exasperation, "Just what do you have to tell me? Go back to slacking off if you don't have anything and stop disturbing me."

"Sigh, you didn't use to have such an attitude. You were so respectful back when you asked me for an enchantment," Lagi said with sorrow. "Indeed, you no longer think highly of me..."

Just what is with this insecure attitude of his today‽

Han Xiao restrained the urge to punch Lagi and said, "Say whatever's on your mind. Don't disturb me if there's nothing!"

Lagi then shook his head and said, "I am actually here to make a suggestion."

Han Xiao's eyes immediately widened in shock the moment these words were said.

Just what is going on? Wasn't my vice commander just for show‽

Since when did he learn how to give suggestions?

Did the sun rise from the wrong side today? Wait, an artificial sun can rise from any direction.

"What suggestions do you have?" Han Xiao asked carefully. He was like a hunter that had met a deer in the forest, afraid that he may scare his prey away.

"I heard from His Excellency Milizaus that all of you failed to find anything over the last few months."

"And then?" Han Xiao nodded. Milizaus was a Mage and seemed to like Lagi for some reason.

As the vice commander of the army, Lagi was also an individual with status. He had encountered Milizaus frequently in recent times and sought advice from Milizaus. Even if it was for Han Xiao's sake, Milizaus would not reject Lagi.

"With the Shattered Star Ring being so large, it will be impossible for us to find a Beyond Grade A if he wants to hide. I think that we should give up the search and let the Crimson Dynasty find them on their own. There's no need to waste our manpower and resources," Lagi said.

"How strange. Why do you suddenly care about such a matter? Did you eat Emerald Grass' medicine by accident?" Han Xiao asked with doubt.

"As the vice commander of the army, it is only normal for me to bother about the development of the army," Lagi said with a bitter expression. "In your heart, it seems like..."

"Stop!"

Han Xiao felt his head ache upon hearing Lagi's words.

In fact, most people would have such a reaction after spending enough time with Lagi, and Han Xiao decided to call this symptom 'Lagi Syndrome'.

Han Xiao smiled and tried to say with patience, "Alright, I heard your advice and will make a decision based on the circumstances. Can you leave now?"

"... You indeed despise me."

"Scram!"

In some large, neutral space harbor, Taylor and Sagman were hiding within the crowd on the street. Both of them had currently disguised themselves with magic into two ordinary looking civilians of the Aso Clan. This was a type of human-shaped living being with blue skin, purple eyes, and three fingers on their hands.

They walked into the harbor and had their identities checked. Their status as galactic residents was verified with a card, and they successfully passed through the checks.

Their current disguise came from the Arcane Church's spies that they had met not too long ago, and their identities had truly existed. They had also obtained tens of other identities that they could easily switch into.

Entering the harbor, they looked around and noticed a few suspicious individuals at the corners. They were sizing up the passersby and had an extraordinary aura.

Upon seeing that, they communicated with their consciousness.

"Spies who are here to search for us."

"There are even spies over here. The dynasty has truly exhausted a great deal of resources in order to find us."

"Who knows how Ninjia is doing..."

After escaping from the Flickering World, the four of them split up into three groups. Ninjia escaped alone with the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, Sagman and Taylor travelled together, and Psyker travelled alone by borrowing the strength of the Star Pupil Holy Race.

During this period, the Crimson Dynasty and Federation of Light spies were scattered all around the Shattered Star Ring. Sagman and Taylor felt every step of the way to be extremely precarious, but thankfully, they received aid from the Arcane Church's spies.

They were both extremely frustrated in their hearts. As Beyond Grade A Supers, they would be respected wherever they went. Despite having such strength, they had to avoid these weak spies and hide like mice. It was truly too frustrating!

They had switched between plenty of spaceships. They had arrived at this harbor not too long ago, and a new spaceship was waiting for them in the harbor.

As they walked, some commotion could be heard from the pier, and this little commotion did not escape their senses.

Turning around to take a look, they saw a group of galactic warriors walking in their direction with the Black Star Army insignia on their chest.

The crowd immediately let out a path for them and stared at the Black Star Army warriors with awe.

As a new Beyond Grade A organization, the members of the Black Star Army had such special privileges.

Sagman frowned. "They are from the Black Star Army."

"The subordinates of Black Star are all extremely queer. Avoid them."

They changed directions.

At the same time, the group of Black Star Army warriors casually looked around.

Right at that moment, a member of the group looked in the direction of Sagman and Taylor and nudged his teammate.

"Strange, I saw two red names just now, and they disappeared in a flash. I wonder if I saw wrongly."

"This is a neutral harbor, so could they be galactic pirates?"

"Shall we go over to take a look?"

"Er, alright. Since we are here to hand in the mission, we can fight some pirates and earn a quick buck."

Chapter 864: Whereabouts Exposed

Amid the bustle of the neutral space harbor, the duo headed toward the storehouse while planning their route of escape.

"We have a few plans. Two of the most stable plans are to borrow the aid of the spies and escape through the stargate or continue hiding out identity and slowly travel through the Shattered Star Ring."

"Both plans have their risks. If we want to travel through the Star Field, the Seoul Star Cluster and Colton Star Cluster are regions that we must avoid."

"There is another method that would be to try our luck. There is a wormhole cluster in the middle of the Shattered Star Ring, and we can make use of the unstable wormholes to escape into another Star Field."

Just when they were discussing the matter, they suddenly felt people following them from behind. Their footsteps paused, and they turned around to take a look, only to see the few Black Star Army members that they had spotted earlier following behind them.

Taylor was stunned for a moment. "Why are the members of the Black Star Army eyeing us?"

"Don't make a commotion and see what they want to do. It may just be a misunderstanding..." Sagman frowned and pretended that he did not spot anything.

After going down a few split paths, the number of people in the surroundings decreased, but the Black Star Army members were still following them. Only then did they confirm that these Black Star Army members had their eyes on them. It seemed as though they wanted to find where their spaceship was docked.

The duo looked at each other.

"What should we do? Did they recognize us?"

"Doesn't seem that way... but we should get rid of them just to be safe. We can then change into another disguise."

"This is a neutral harbor. Don't make too big a commotion or let others notice that we are the culprits."

"Alright. I will make them disappear without a trace."

On the other side, the players were following behind and chatting in their party chat.

"Both of the red names are Fatally Dangerous. Will we be able to win?"

"It's alright. The army will give us the bounty for catching the pirates, but we can also request aid from the nearby members of the army."

These players had already used their detection skill on Sagman and Taylor, but their names were not revealed. Instead, their disguised names appeared. However, the other party were red names from a hostile faction.

It was not too strange for them to meet a red-named monster out in the galaxy. The majority of them were galactic pirates or scavengers. Thus, these players only thought that they were galactic pirates. It was not that they could not talk to the red-named characters, but it would be extremely easy for them to be attacked since the other party was hostile toward them.

The Black Star Army was in the same camp as the Crimson Dynasty. With the Crimson Dynasty being in open confrontation with the Arcane Church, all members of the Arcane Church became red names for the players in the Black Star Army.

Just when the players wanted to continue tailing the two, their bodies disappeared, and they were suddenly waiting to be revived.

"Eh? Why did I die?"

"Me too. Why didn't we even see the attack?"

The players were all taken aback and hurriedly opened the interface to see the battle notification. Although they were not able to see how the enemy attacked, the interface would show the damage that they took and the attacker's name. It was one of the two red named characters, and he seemed to have used a mental attack to one-shot all the players.

It would not be much if this was the case. However, what truly shocked the players was that they suffered 84,000 damage points!

They almost thought that they had read an additional zero!

Just what kind of strength was this?

Just what was the level of the red-named character who attacked them? Was he a Calamity Grade‽

The players were all extremely curious.

"We seem to have met a fantastic character."

"This is a large fish. Coming into contact with them will definitely trigger a hidden storyline, right?"

Just as they were discussing, one of the players suddenly asked, "For them to easily deal 84,000 damage... do you remember the Planet Lighthouse dungeon we fought yesterday?"

"Wait... I think I understand something!"

The players came to a realization. This party did not join in the Flickering World exploration mission and had been performing missions for the Mercenary League in the Shattered Star Ring. Thus, they had immediately seized the chance to experience the battle the moment the dungeon was released. They still had a vivid memory of how they died an unknown death at the hands of a Beyond Grade A.

Furthermore, damage of such a level seemed to be at the Beyond Grade A level in the dungeon!

This meant that the two Fatally Dangerous red-named characters might not be just Calamity Grade Supers but Beyond Grade A!

Thinking about the mission recently issued by the army to find the Arcane Church's Beyond Grade As...

The players suddenly realized that they might have met the targets.

After using a spell to get rid of the Black Star Army members, Sagman and Taylor found the warehouse and flew out from one of the docks.

They purchased an extremely common model that could be found anywhere.

Following that, they looked toward the neutral harbor and heaved a sigh of relief when they saw that there were no Black Star Army fleets pursuing them.

Taylor began to relax.

With the large difference in strength between both parties, they had been able to get rid of the few Black Star Army warriors without anyone noticing. It seemed like their identities would not be exposed.

In order to be safe, they decided to change into their next set of identity and purchased a new spaceship again.

However, they just could not understand why the Black Star Army members would suddenly follow them.

Indeed, all the subordinates of Black Star were extremely strange.

Ka ka ka!

In Han Xiao's workshop, a few mechanical arms were currently assembling a human-shaped machine, and it was gradually being formed.

The robot that left the furnace was burning hot, and it was quickly cooled down by the coolants being sprayed on it from the sides.

This step was completed extremely quickly, and the next step would be to apply a coat of paint.

Han Xiao waved his hands and said, "Phillip, conduct a test."

"Understood, hum... RX001 generation mechanical body. Nickname 'mammoth'. Conducting the first test..."

The nanoparticles then flowed around the body of the robot.

The test was very quickly concluded, and the data from the test was presented to Han Xiao.

Han Xiao looked through the numbers of the test and nodded with satisfaction.

He was not creating a mechanical soldier this time but a host for his [Lord's Descent] skill.

Han Xiao had already tested the effect of the [Lord's Descent] skill. During his tests, he realized that there was a difference when he used the different mechanical soldiers as a host. The difference was largely due to the attributes of the mechanical soldier and the materials used to craft it.

He realized that mechanical soldiers were not the best hosts, and using [Lord's Descent] on Mechanical Life was not ideal. A Mechanical Life had its own consciousness, and it would be counterproductive to have two consciousnesses in a single body. Furthermore, the consciousness of the body might be damaged if he sent out too much energy.

Thus, after a series of calculations, Han Xiao decided to create a special mechanical container to serve as the host of the [Lord's Descent] skill to fully maximize the effect of this skill.

At the same time, if he used [Lord's Descent] on the same target multiple times, there was a chance to have a soul connection, which would probably strengthen the effect of the skill. He was not prepared to treat this container as a disposable product but a long-term host.

This host was created from many precious materials, including a new material that he had forged with [Endless Material Combination] called 'First Generation Black Star Alloy'. It was able to endure high energy, temperature, and pressure and also had the ability to repair itself. It was able to absorb various types of materials and could take a heavy load. These were the conditions required to endure [Lord's Descent].

Han Xiao then knocked on the outer armor of the 'Mammoth' host, but not a single sound was given out as though all the vibrations had been absorbed by the alloy.

"Not bad. It has the ability to absorb energy and repair itself. Only then will it be able to enjoy my energy conversion and cell regrowth talents during Lord's Descent."

Just as he was about to test the actual effect, Phillip's voice rang in his head.

"Master, hum... a member of the army would like to report to you their whereabouts of the Arcane Church Beyond Grade As. According to the priority system that you set, I skipped past Sylvia and reported the matter directly to you."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled and said, "Oh? Someone actually managed to find a clue? Quickly let me take a look."

The next moment, a report from the players could be seen in front of his eyes.

Although they were not able to reveal information like 'red-named characters' and were only able to give a vague description about them being killed, Han Xiao was extremely clear about the players' characters and did not doubt the player's advantage when it came to information.

"There is a large chance that they are the Arcane Church's Beyond Grade As. Since there are only two of them, it means that they must have split up. Hmm, these two fellows have changed their identities, and this will not be their only identity. Now that the players have alerted them, they will probably switch to another identity. However, this information can also help us achieve a breakthrough."

Han Xiao was extremely excited. The biggest difficulty of the dynasty was that they were unable to lock onto the whereabouts of the four and could only search blindly.

Although the players had alerted the two and were unable to tail them, it had at least narrowed their location down to a specific region and would be extremely helpful to the dynasty. They dynasty would not have to search blindly and could narrow their search.

"In this respect, the players seem to have an advantage. Hmm, I know..."

After thinking for a while, Han Xiao opened the interface and issued a mission to the players.

The Crimson Dynasty Search Operation: Region Investigation

Mission Introduction: The Black Star Army has received clues that the Arcane Church's Beyond Grade As have appeared in the Fleur Star Cluster, Three Wood Star System, Star Zone 9, Furnace Neutral Harbor. The members of the army should head over to the region and report any new clues to the Army Commander, Black Star.

Mission Requirements: Search the region and find the target.

Tip: The target is in disguise, so you should pay close attention to Red Named characters that are Fatally Dangerous. If they are moving as a pair, it is very likely for them to be the targets.

This will be a Prize-Pool Mission. Accepting the mission will require 200 Experience, and those who discover clues can split the Prize Pool.

Prize Pool: 10,000,000 Experience, 3,000,000 Enas.

Accumulated Reward: 0

After checking that there was nothing wrong with the mission, Han Xiao issued it to the players.

He was currently a wealthy tycoon. In the past, he needed to risk his life for a few hundred thousand Enas, but he could now give out a few million Enas without even batting an eye.

The Black Star Army had extremely deep pockets. There were many financial groups who wanted to help the Black Star Army become listed on the market, but he had rejected them all temporarily.

As for the players who provided the intelligence, Han Xiao was not stingy and gave them rich rewards through the interface.

"Right, duplicate a copy of this intelligence and send it to Tarrokov."

"Roger, hum..."

Following which, Han Xiao asked, "Is the battleship of those members still present in that neutral harbor?"

"Yes, hum..."

Han Xiao raised his brows and entered the quantum network.

"Alright. Phillip, infiltrate the database of the harbor."

Phillip was able to easily access the database of many different locations.

Asking the players to help him was only one approach. Han Xiao was also prepared to use his Virtual Intrusion to check the records of the harbor and find information about the disguises that the two had on. He would then dig through the history of those two individuals, and he might be able to find more useful information.

The galaxy was in the quantum network era, and every galactic resident would leave some traces on the net—where they were born, where they worked, where they went, and so on. Everything was recorded, and there was no such thing as privacy before a Virtual Mechanic.

Although the four from the Arcane Church were Beyond Grade As, there was no Mechanic among them, and it would be impossible for them to use Virtual Technology skills to clean up their traces in the quantum network.

This gave Han Xiao a chance.

"Perhaps they will change their identities, but I doubt they will switch spaceships halfway during the flight. I should be able to locate them based on the records of the spaceship."

Han Xiao nodded in his head.

As long as the targets exposed themselves, it would not be so simple to escape from the hands of a Virtual Mechanic like him.

Thinking about the advice that Lagi had given not too long ago, Han Xiao had a strange look on his face.

That was truly some sh*tty advice...

Chapter 865: Falling into the Trap

Following the data link channel that was built by Phillip, Han Xiao's consciousness warped through the quantum network, and the nodes appeared in front of him.

Sweeping through, Han Xiao confirmed his target and entered one of the databases.

The defenses of the artificial intelligence within such interstellar nodes were practically nonexistent before one who had grasped the Beyond Grade A Mechanic knowledge [Virtual Creator].

Under his control, Phillip easily entered the back door of the harbor's database, copied the relevant data, and quickly found the disguised identities of Sagman and Taylor. He found the two in the wide area quantum network, as well as the record of all activities of the identity so far.

"The two of them are unassuming galactic residents, and the last time they appeared on the log was..."

Browsing through the information, he saw that their record was seamless and estimated that they should indeed be real people. The actual owners should have died in outer space, and their identity was then collected by the Arcane Church's spies.

Since there were countless interstellar travelers who died within the universe each year, it provided the gray forces with a large number of fake identities. Han Xiao remembered that there were large-scale sales of this identity by intelligence organizations on the black market.

"If not for the fact that the players had noticed it, no one would notice two ordinary people with such innocuous resumes in the vast universe." Han Xiao shook his head as he smiled.

Upon checking the ID of the spaceship that the two people used, he discovered that it was still docked within one of the lots, which meant that the spaceship should have been abandoned. The two of them had probably gotten on a new one after reaching this central port, and Han Xiao had to trace the new ID of the spaceship they used.

"Since they bought a new spaceship, then there has to be transaction records of them within the port... but the accounts of the people they impersonated did not show any movement of funds, so it is likely that they used a different account... Phillip, check which supplier the spaceship originated from. They could have made a transaction there. From there, we can trace it to their secret account."

"Master, hum... there's no information about the origin of the spacecraft in the port database. This information is generally stored separately in the shipyard's independent database."

"Oh... then mark all the network nodes of the shipyard, ship market, and black market in this port."

"Marking complete. There are 1,374 nodes, hum..."

"Hack into all of them." Han Xiao waved carelessly.

The moment the command was given, Phillip immediately mobilized huge computing power, and the more than a thousand quantum network nodes were invaded one by one. The colors changed from a peaceful white to green with control authority, akin to a virus infection. Han Xiao's control range within the port expanded rapidly.

Before long, Han Xiao had gained control of the more than a thousand databases. and all the backdoors were opened by him while the other party knew nothing about it.

With his current Virtual Technology expertise, so long as he could establish a link, he could easily spread his control over a whole planet's network, taking over the entire planet remotely.

Phillip's processing system had been strengthened countless times by Han Xiao, and his computing power was now extremely strong. In a few moments, he had completed the data search and discovered the origin of the spaceship as well as Sagman's purchase history, together with his spending accounts.

In this way, they gained an additional tracking clue. If this secret account was utilized elsewhere, even if they changed their disguise, they would be exposed.

However, Han Xiao was still unsatisfied. He wanted to trace the early transfer records of this anonymous account, as he was sure that the money had been sent through the Arcane Church. From this, he would be able to latch onto their other spies and secret accounts. As long as he continued to follow the trail, there would be more clues.

From this small breakthrough, he might be able to lock onto a portion of the Arcane Church's identities.

...

The moment the mission [The Crimson Dynasty Search Operation: Region Investigation] was released, it received the attention of the enthusiastic players. Millions of them accepted this prize pool task and gathered from all directions to move toward this area.

Initially, they were akin to headless flies and could only blindly search due to the lack of knowledge. Thus, some people went off to perform other missions.

But the situation had changed. With a mission area demarcated, the chance of completion would be greatly increased, so countless players flocked over.

The prize pool of ten million experience was no small sum, but what drove the players was the prize money of three million Enas. When they took one normal mission, the amount received would not be more than a hundred thousand Enas.

To have such a big sum of money in front of them, three million, they could not resist the temptation!

There were even players fantasizing. If they completed the objective alone, would they not gain the whole reward?

The requirement to enter this mission was only two hundred experience. With such low investments and high potential returns, the players did not think too much, and the crazy accumulation of experience in the prize-pool became the factor that pulled in even more players.

For a period of time, the players poured into the area, and the probability of interstellar citizens meeting members of the Black Star Army increased significantly.

...

Within the interrogation room of a dynasty battleship, a group of captured Arcane Church spies were firmly tied to a chair, and the dynasty soldiers guarded the entrance to the room with guns.

This group had been captured based on the intelligence of Black Star. He had dug out some information from the secret accounts of Sagman, and the dynasty had been able to select new targets.

Shua!

The door to the interrogation room opened, and a man with a smile on his face strolled in. He wore the trench coat of a dynasty officer and black gloves.

Standing in front of the captives, he softly laughed.

"Let me introduce myself. I'm a psychic, one of the Senior Officers of the Crimson Dynasty's Intelligence Department. My name is... heh heh, there's no need to tell you guys. Anyways, we'd better hurry up. I'll be digging some information from your brains today. Please cooperate, else you will burn out your brains, and I won't be responsible for that."

As he spoke, he walked up to one of the captives, placing his palm on the head of said captive.

Boom!

The captive began to struggle violently, as though suffering from epilepsy.

A few seconds passed, and trails of blood leaked out from all seven orifices on his head. The captive's mouth was slack, and tears, snot, and saliva mixed with the fresh blood dripped onto the ground. He looked miserable as he continued to convulse.

"Thank you for your cooperation." The smile of the Intelligence officer got even wider, and he walked toward the next person.

Looking at him approach, the rest had expressions of horror, as though saying, Don't come over!

Screams of misery sounded out. "Argh!"

Looking at this scene, the guards at the door subconsciously tightened their grips on their weapons.

Very quickly, the intelligence officer's job was completed. He took off his gloves, placing them in his pocket before leaving.

As he was walking out, he tapped one of the soldiers' shoulders and jerked his head toward one of the captive spies who was foaming at the mouth.

"Don't clean up the scene. There's still some use for them. I require their genetic code to verify their identities as spies."

"Un... understood." The guard swallowed with difficulty.

The officer then took out his communicator, reporting to Tarrokov.

"There're a few of them who have come into contact with Beyond Grade As, and we have confirmed that they were Taylor and Sagman. I've confirmed that all of them match with the identities of spies from the Arcane Church, as well as the tasks entrusted to them.

Tarrokov shook his head. "Are there any you suspect to be true personnel that personally received the instructions?"

"Yes."

The espionage was based off the command from the Arcane Church, and the missions they received were all different. A large portion of them were giving misleading or false information, and only a small portion were really in contact with Sagman.

Because Han Xiao had locked onto the area where the two of them were, the dynasty could rule out many of the misleading locations, and the spy with a mission location around where the two of them were located was thus the suspected actual personnel, so they could also narrow down their scope of operations even further.

Only when they discovered the actual personnel involved could Tarrokov then implement a plan, which was to impersonate the espionage agent of the Arcane Church. Because Sagman was in contact with the Arcane Church, they would not trust anyone other than the person who was actually in charge of this mission.

Impersonating was difficult but not impossible, as long as they caught the person in charge. Even if the Arcane Church were to discover it later, it would be too late.

...

Following the search of the Black Star Army, Sagman and Taylor found many irregularities, as though they had been grasped in the palm of someone.

They immediately took all sorts of measures, but it was as though a large net had been spread toward them, trapping them before being slowly tightened.

Their every move seemed to be monitored, as if an assassin was hiding behind them.

While they did not know where the problem lay, but when they thought about it carefully, they realised it was most likely the fact that Black Star was following them through the quantum network, and their spaceship and purchases had likely been tracked.

Thus, the two of them decided to abandon their spaceship, float around in the universe with their fleshly bodies for a period of time. When they had left their spaceship at a distance, they then transferred to another spaceship operated by their spies, and donned on a new disguise.

The situation improved for a period of time, and Sagman as well as Taylor both thought that they had shaken Black Star off.

But they were unaware that the dynasty had already completely locked their position and quietly started to tighten the circle, following them. When the Beyond Grade As of the dynasty arrived, that would be the time to reel in the net.

...

Within the wormholes of the Shattered Star Ring, the Fallen Ark fleet led by EsGod was roaming about.

On the flagship, Fakisen spoke to the main body of EsGod. "Your Excellency EsGod, are you sure we are leaving the Shattered Star Ring through this method?"

"And if we don't?" EsGod laughed. "Who will lend us their stargate?"

At this moment, EsGod had already completed his evolution and was full of vitality. Fakisen could feel a deeper level of pressure from him, coming from a higher life form.

EsGod, who possessed information from the Evolutionary Civilization, had gained a lot from the evolutionary energy, and no one could tell how much he had improved.

Fallen Ark had only established a temporary stargate between the desolate universe belt and the Flickering World, and there were also no stargates present in the Shattered Star Ring. Furthermore, they had borrowed the Arcane Church's stargate to travel from the Central Galaxy to the Flickering World, and they naturally could not use the same gate when returning.

From the beginning, EsGod had been prepared to leave the star field through the wormhole group of the Shattered Star Ring, one of the reasons being that it was where he had first discovered a certain fortuitous encounter.

"The transmission locations of these unstable wormholes are completely randomized, and we don't know where we'll be thrown. The risk is too great. We can just slowly proceed along the desolate universe belt, avoiding the crowd for a period of them." Fakisen tried to dissuade him.

EsGod turned a deaf ear, looking at the unstable wormholes constantly emerging and disappearing outside the porthole. "Just look at how disorderly and chaotic this scene is. This is the true meaning of the universe, and only in this disorderly state can it contain endless possibilities."

EsGod then turned to Fakisen, casually asking, "Any intelligence on the remaining Beyond Grade As from the Arcane Church?"

Fakisen nodded. "The dynasty is pursuing the remaining four with all their might and did not put much energy into chasing us. The Black Star Army, Bloodshed Land, and Klent Kingdom are also the heads of the Shattered Star Ring, so the dynasty will probably catch one of two of them."

"It seems like the Arcane Church will suffer great losses this time." EsGod blandly eyed Fakisen. "Are you happy?"

"Of course." Fakisen laughed. "The moment they contacted me, I was already picturing this scene."

"Ah, I'm afraid it is not just this reason..." EsGod laughed but did not pursue the exact reason. He then turned back to face the wormhole, leisurely commanding, "Let's enter."

The Fallen Ark fleet slowly traversed into the wormhole and vanished.

...

A stream of light shot through the universe. It was Sagman and Taylor's spaceship.

"There are only seven more hours before we reach the next public stargate. We're nearing the border of Shattered Star Ring. The dynasty has little control over the next star cluster. The spies are also already in place and are waiting to assemble the stargate. The moment we move to a different area, the dynasty will not be able to find us so easily anymore," Sagman said.

Taylor nodded, his expression finally easing a little.

They had hidden high and low for almost three months, and this sort of life was stifling for them. Finally, they had hope of escaping unscathed.

Sagman sighed. "It's a pity that Mercer and Dylan were captured. Out of six of us, only four of us can return... no, maybe only three. Psyker's base is within the Shattered Star Ring, and sooner or later, he will have to come back and face the pressure from Black Star and Heber."

At this point, neither was in the mood to talk further. Their mission that they were so confident in had actually put them in such a sorry situation.

At this point, the artificial intelligence of the spaceship suddenly sounded, and it was a familiar voice.

"If you have the time to be concerned about others, you'd be better off using that time to worry about yourselves."

The duo jumped, their expressions changing.

This voice... Black Star‽

The next moment, the spaceship suddenly shuddered, and the artificial intelligence of the spaceship killed the hyperdrive function, causing the spaceship to come out from hyperdrive.

Even the ordinary engine was turned off, so the spaceship simply floated in the universe.

The magic interference traps that Milizaus and Ravenlaude had placed in the void in advance completely enveloped this area. All spacetime abilities were blocked.

Streams of light shot out from eight directions, wrapping around Sagman and Taylor's spaceship.

Milizaus as well as the Beyond Grade As from the dynasty were all on the scene, and each occupied a position, staring at them like tigers toward prey.

"We're surrounded!" Taylor's face drained of color.

Sagman's face twitched violently, his expression mixed with incredulity and fury. He suddenly noticed a mechanical army blocking their path ahead.

Standing at the front were the four Apostle Weapons lined up in a row—Psionic Prime with a crown and a spear, Giant King Kong with its hulking body, Silver Flash with its gleaming hand-cannons, and Mad Sky Hunter with its arrogant bearing.

Standing in front of them was a figure, but it was not Han Xiao. It was the mechanical host, codenamed 'Mammoth'. At this moment, Han Xiao was utilizing [Lord's Descent] to project his consciousness and will into this mechanical host. Its tough mechanical body looked dazzling with the blue-gold Mechanical Force arcing around it.

This mechanical host had seemingly transformed into Han Xiao's avatar, sharing his attributes, skills, and expertise. It practically possessed a Beyond Grade A combat power at this moment.

"Surrender." Two dark streams of energy flowed from Milizaus' nostrils, who was in his dragon form.

While he was unwilling to chase and fight so hard, the dynasty had already locked onto the enemy, and he and the rest of the Beyond Grade As could not openly defy the dynasty's orders.

Sagman's eyeballs darted around before finally landing on Han Xiao's machinery.

After being played by Han Xiao a few times, he had already gone beyond the point of anger.

Seeing this, Han Xiao leisurely replied, "In this situation, your odds of escape are close to none. We just want to capture you guys alive. How about surrendering?"

Sagman breathed out loudly before suddenly smiling. However, his smile was full of viciousness.

"When did you hear that a Beyond Grade A does not fight and just surrenders?"

"Maybe today?" Han Xiao's brows rose.

While he said that, his posture slightly lowered, preparing for battle. Several other Beyond Grade As were also prepared to move, ready to follow Han Xiao's lead at any time.

With his gaze fixed to the front, Sagman suddenly spoke to Taylor. "I'll try to hold all of them back; you look for an opportunity to escape. They only want to capture one of us. If one more of us can escape, that will be a bonus."

"Don't be stupid. They came prepared. I can't run." Taylor let out a bitter laugh before taking out his staff. "I'm better off staying and fighting with you. Even if we can't change the result, I can't let myself be caught without dignity."

Sagman nodded before murmuring, "After this battle, I don't know when we'll next be free."

They then looked at each other.

Boom!

The next instant, the spaceship shattered, and the duo rushed out toward the Supers of the dynasty.

...

Galaxy Chronicles (Official Revised Edition)

In the Year 705, on the 27th Day of the 9th Month on the Galaxy Calendar, the Arcane Church and Fallen Ark teamed up to launch a surprise attack on Planet Lighthouse within the Flickering World. Their goal was to snatch the Evolution Cube and kill the Beyond Grade A allies of the Crimson Dynasty—Beyoni, Black Star, and Milizaus.

'Magus' Austin intervened in this battle, and the Arcane Church used the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter to hit Milizaus, but it was later countered with some special sealing means by Black Star.

Black Star later captured the Beyond Grade A Super of the Arcane Church, Dylan, netting great achievements. The Arcane Church was forced to retreat and entered an escape phase, where the dynasty began hunting them down.

In the same year, on the 3rd Day of the 10th Month, just as the Arcane Church's fleet left the Flickering World, fleet commander Rogue and Mercer were captured.

In the Year 706, on the 21st Day of the 1st Month, with the assistance of the Federation of Light, the Bloodshed Land, Black Star Army, Klent Kingdom, Purple Crystal, and more, the Crimson Dynasty finally successfully intercepted the Beyond Grade As Sagman and Taylor in the Shattered Star Ring. After a bloody battle, they were both captured by the Crimson Dynasty.

At this point, the pursuit from the dynasty came to an end, and the fleet of Arcane Church was completely annihilated. Four Beyond Grade As were captured, and only two escaped. This became known in history as 'The Battle of Planet Lighthouse' and 'The Attack of the Arcane Church'.

Chapter 866: The Curtains Close

The Arcane Church had a foreign embassy on the mother planet of the Crimson Dynasty, and its ambassador paid a visit to the political core of the dynasty, Tarunamir Palace, to discuss the remuneration regarding Mercer and Dylan.

The negotiations had already been going for several months. Before this, the officials of the dynasty were initially adamant on not releasing them, but now they were becoming more open to certain conditions.

"With regard to Article 53 of the remuneration, my side still has something to add..."

As the ambassador continued to talk, the officials of the dynasty nodded, occasionally interrupting. Regarding this matter, they did not have any veto power, and they were actually just the spokespersons for the upper echelons. Their attitudes were the attitudes of the upper echelons themselves.

After a while, the communicator of one of the dynasty officials rang, indicating that there was a message. The ambassador paused and waved to the official to read the message before he continued.

The official in question opened the communicator, but after glancing at the news, they immediately put the communicator down.

Seeing this, the ambassador was about to continue but was suddenly halted by a hand from that official.

"Let's stop here for today. As for the previous terms and conditions, please return and make a new set."

The ambassador jumped up. "Didn't we already discuss the terms? Why the sudden..."

He was cut by the official's wave. The official stood up, looking down at the ambassador with a smile that revealed some complacency and superiority to the ambassador.

"Go back and wait for the news from your upper echelons, or you can take a look at today's news. You'll naturally understand."

...

After three months, the Crimson Dynasty and the Arcane Church had some new developments.

On this day, the dynasty issued a new piece of news to the entire universe, announcing that they had succeeded in capturing the two Beyond Grade As of the Arcane Church, which meant that they now had four captives.

The counterattack of the dynasty was as fast as lightning, causing many of the organizations in the universe to feel awed. Seeing the heavy bleeding of the Arcane Church this time, some people felt schadenfreude, some rejoiced, and some felt the bitter hatred against common enemies.

This news caused a sensation in over a dozen star fields. In the eyes of countless interstellar citizens, the Beyond Grade A Supers were akin to deities that were only spoken of in legends. However, there were actually four of them who were knocked down to the earth and turned into prisoners.

This sort of capturing of Beyond Grade A had not happened for a long time. Countless citizens felt that they were observing a piece of history that would be passed down in time.

But on the forums, the players were focused on another matter.

Now that the search and capture mission had ended, the players received their reward. Within the army communications system, Phillip issued a general message, praising their contribution, which proved that their contribution was not small in allowing the dynasty to capture the Beyond Grade As.

The few players that first discovered Sagman and Taylor publicized their reward on the forums, and this allowed the other players to understand that the trend of this big event plot was inadvertently changed by them participating.

From Version 1.0 to Version 3.0, the players gradually found that they were having more and more influence on events, and they were becoming more involved in Galaxy. Generally, the players only felt their existence when challenging the storyline during the time when they were on the beginner planets.

However, this time, what they had re-written was a galactic war between two Universal Civilizations, of which the scale was much larger and grander.

The feeling of involvement was more memorable and rewarding compared to just purely receiving the mission reward.

This event was also recorded by the players into the Shattered Star Ring chronicles.

Every player was given the right to edit the chronicle, which caused no small headache for the officials. Thus, the officials would filter the events and organize them, and the trivial matters would be placed within the appendix. Only events that were worth mentioning would be placed within the main post. The players who wrote entries could sign their names on it and receive rewards in return, which was a glorious accomplishment.

...

Within another star cluster in the Shattered Star Ring, spaceships that snaked like a serpent were lined up in front of a stargate. Among them was an ordinary, unassuming spaceship.

Within that spaceship, the virtual screen was showing the news—the dynasty announcing the results of the pursuit operation, in which two Beyond Grade As were captured alive.

Beep!

The virtual screen was switched off.

Ninjia put down the remote, holding his forehead with one hand. His expression was complicated.

"Sagman and the rest have all been captured by the dynasty..."

Among the four that escaped from the Flickering World, two of them had already been caught. Psyker's situation was also terrible, so he was technically the only one who could safely make it out of the Shattered Star Ring. A sense of sorrow permeated Ninjia.

When he thought back to their departure, the six of them had been full of confidence. To think that in the blink of an eye, their entire force had collapsed, and the majority had even been captured. What a tragic end.

He had heard that the upper echelons of the Arcane Church were originally discussing the ransom payment with the Crimson Dynasty, but now that the latter had two more chips in hand, the price offered by the church would have to be increased. Furthermore, the Crimson Dynasty would definitely not allow the Arcane Church to redeem all of them, so there would be someone who experienced a long period of time within the prison.

"At least... I managed to bring the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter back..."

Ninjia slightly shook his head. Now that things had come to such a point, he could only use this to comfort himself and the church.

...

"Thank goodness it was Ninjia who held onto the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. He did not let the dynasty take that away as well..."

In the Arcane Church's meeting of Bishops, many of them sat there with bitter expressions. One of them tried to comfort the rest, but he only received looks of helplessness.

One of the bishops spoke up. "We activated our espionage network in the Shattered Star Ring, yet they failed to bring all of them back. The price we paid this time far outweighs the benefits obtained. Even Sagman and Taylor have fallen into the dynasty's hands, adding to their chips. We need to offer a large ransom payment now because the dynasty will definitely not be polite to us."

The ransom payments demanded between universal civilizations would not just simply be money but included political, military, and economic conditions.

The bishops were enveloped in sorrows during this meeting. None of them had any time to feel anger.

Dylan, Mercer, Sagman, and Taylor did not just represent themselves, for they had their own Beyond Grade A organizations with immense influence. The strong were plenty there, and with their leaders being captured, these Beyond Grade A organizations would definitely go into turmoil and panic. In order to stabilize their allies, the church had to withstand no small pressure.

In addition, because of the attention paid by the other Beyond Grade As, the Arcane Church not only had to redeem them but had to redeem them quickly, before their Beyond Grade A allies lost faith in them. If their allies lost faith, it would cause their recruitment of Beyond Grade As in the future to be much more difficult.

After all, the older Beyond Grade As would die, and new Beyond Grade As would always be born. Because of the long period of time that a civilization could exist, the Beyond Grade As under them would constantly undergo a shuffle. From a long-term perspective, the reputation and credibility of a civilization was important.

As for the newer generation of Beyond Grade As, the Crimson Dynasty had an overwhelming advantage...

As the record holder for the fastest time taken to reach the Beyond Grade A stage, Black Star undoubtedly had potential to go further. Furthermore, in the last battle, he had shown off his edge, much sooner than the observing forces had expected.

One could see that the strength shown by Black Star would definitely become one of the strengths relied on by the dynasty in the near future. The most frightening part was his age. Among all the Beyond Grade As, he was the youngest, which was enough for him to serve the dynasty for hundreds or even thousands of years.

In other words, for a few hundred years, they probably would have to constantly see this wretched guy's face.

The moment they thought of how the Crimson Dynasty had gotten their hands on such valuable stocks, the envy of the Arcane Church rose so high they seemed to have reached the heavens.

They also wanted to kill Black Star, but their attempt this time had left them with tragic losses, and thus, the Arcane Church had decided to temporarily give up on the Evolution Cube.

Before eliminating the impact that this storm caused, the Arcane Church did not intend to make trouble for Black Star. In fact, they did not even wish to see him.

The Arcane Church admitted that they had flopped this time.

This debt would be written down and remembered by them to be collected later.

There was still time!

...

"Sagman and the rest were caught."

In a dimly lit room, the Beyond Grade As of the Arcane Church were gathered through remote projection. Around the table were six empty spots.

Because of the matter this time, the Beyond Grade As of the Arcane Church had gathered to discuss the resultant waves caused by the news.

"Initially, when the Arcane Church came to me to take on this task, they only saw the disparity of combat power and thought that it was impossible to fail. However, I felt that there was some danger, so I rejected it, and they had Mercer take my place. Now that I look at it, it was good I did not accept the mission." One of them could not help but attempt to be wise after the incident.

"It's a pity that I'm being watched by too many organizations and am unable to even move in secret. If I had taken part in this mission, the results would not have been the same," another said blandly.

The Arcane Church also had Beyond Grade As on the level of the three pillars of the Crimson Dynasty, but their strongest Supers did not participate in the operation this time. Because they were too strong, the surveillance on them was naturally higher, and any movement from them would have attracted the attention of many eyes. Furthermore, the Arcane Church had thought that the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter would be enough to handle them and only approached Sagman and rest, whose strength was lower compared to the strongest few.

"However, no matter how we put it, Sagman had the numerical advantage, yet they were still unable to snatch the Evolution Cube. Black Star's ability could be considered an unexpected factor this time, and it seems like we have yet another strong opponent."

"Hmm... in another decade or so, the three pillars of the dynasty might just turn into the four pillars..."

With his allies in the same camp having suffered at Black Star's hands, the impressions of the Beyond Grade As present toward Black Star had become even stronger than before.

"How about it? What ideas do we have? Are we going to wait for the Arcane Church to redeem them, or do we try to save them?"

"Let's maintain silence and wait. If the Arcane Church can solve the problem, there's no need for us to complicate matters. Furthermore, from the intelligence provided by the Arcane Church, Black Star seems to be able to seal up Beyond Grade As. Although I don't know what sort of Universal Treasure that is, it is something that cannot be broken so easily."

Everyone nodded. They were still feeling trepidation toward Han Xiao's second mysterious Universal Treasure.

Based on normal procedures, the dynasty would bring the four captives back, and to save them, the most important thing would be coordination.

However, intelligence from Arcane Church said that Black Star was able to seal up Beyond Grade As. With the intelligence capabilities of the church, this would not be an unfounded rumor.

Without coordination to break out the prisoners from both inside and outside, the operation would become a lot more difficult.

While the Beyond Grade As were friends with Sagman and the rest, they were not so close that they would willingly brave hell and high seas for them.

...

A pale blue vortex appeared, and a huge fleet of spaceships slowly appeared from within the vortex, emblazoned with the logo of the dynasty. They slowly left the stargate, leaving behind traces of flames from their tail as they flew, and within them, there was a battleship shaped like a huge dragon.

The light from the stargate illuminated the bodies of the battleships, leaving mottled spots of light and shadow on their angular hulls. They revealed a series of armor cracks and depressions, as well as varying degrees of damage to the outer armor.

Several spaceships from the Black Star Army were suspended near the stargate and slowly faced the heavily armed main flagship of the fleet. The damage suffered by the main flagship was particularly terrible, with a large portion of its armored plates torn out. The holes filled with nano-repair materials showcased the intensity of the battle.

The spaceships docked with the main flagship, and the mechanical structures around their doors locked with each other to complete the link.

Whoosh!

The cabin door slid open, and Han Xiao walked into the flagship. Escorted by the dynasty soldiers, he arrived at the heavily guarded imprisonment zone, where two restraint cabins were placed.

The inner wall of the restraint cabin was made up of an extremely tough alloy, which made it difficult to escape from the inside. The internal structure also automatically adjusted to the prisoner's body shape before fixing in that position. In the middle layer were devices to provide high voltage and electromagnetic fields to restrain the captive and weaken transmission of energy. Right now, they were holding Sagman and Taylor.

While the restraint cabin could not totally restrict the Beyond Grade As, the duo were suffering from heavy injuries and had no strength to struggle free. Furthermore, Heber and Beyoni were on watch.

Han Xiao went there in person because he wanted to utilize the Spacetime Amber, sealing both parties up.

"Lord." The Apostle Weapons walked over.

"You did well." Han Xiao nodded before recalling the mechanical host.

Because he had utilized [Lord's Descent] on the mechanical host to engage Sagman and Taylor, it had suffered quite a bit of damage and would require some degree of repair.

The duo had nowhere to run and gave it their all. This was especially so for Sagman, as the destruction he wrought while going all out dealt some degree of damage to almost everyone there. He was eventually pinned down by the Beyond Grade A Supers of the dynasty.

Tarrokov's long distance projection came up and greeted him. "You've come. We were waiting."

"Let them out." Han Xiao commanded the dynasty soldiers to unlock the restraint cabin, and taking out the Spacetime Amber, he sealed Sagman and Taylor.

"This is a lot safer, with no risk of getting into trouble." Tarrokov tapped the amber ball in satisfaction.

Ravenlaude could not help but look at Han Xiao. He realized that the Spacetime Amber was effective, and his expression sank in envy.

Tarrokov then commanded the two soldiers to take the amber balls away while he led Han Xiao and the rest to the conference room.

After they had taken their seats, he looked toward Han Xiao. "Her Excellency is extremely pleased with our progress. Upon learning of Black Star's accomplishments this time round, she arranged a special award."

Han Xiao nodded. He had spent quite the bit of effort during this pursuit operation and provided a lot of intelligence. After capturing the two, he had received a notification saying that he had obtained 4,500 Dynasty Contribution Points.

It did not end there. Tarrokov had told him in private that his accomplishments would allow the dynasty to be biased toward him when dividing the territory of the Flickering World, allowing him to claim bigger swathes of land.

This emergency was not only neutralized but turned from danger into an opportunity, so the upper echelons had an extremely good impression of Han Xiao.

"The operation has ended, and the spies of the Arcane Church will also be hunted down, but this job will be taken over by the Intelligence Bureau as the dynasty has another task for you," Tarrokov said. "Next, the dynasty requires all of you to escort the four captives back to the Constellation Corridor, to prevent the Arcane Church from intercepting them along the way."

Everyone nodded. They had to be cautious and not lose these chips because of their carelessness.

"However, that does not include Black Star and the Tyrant."

Everyone turned over, and even Han Xiao and Heber looked surprised.

"What do you need us for?" Heber asked in a deep voice.

Tarrokov opened the star map, magnifying it, before stopping at the territory of the Star Pupil Holy Race.

"I need you two to take a portion of the dynasty fleet and head toward the Star Pupil Holy Race."

"Capture Psyker?" Heber frowned.

"No, you guys are going there to demonstrate dominance and pressure them." Tarrokov shook his head in response. "Psyker's situation is different because he is the leader of a civilization, and his camp is based in the Shattered Star Ring. Initially, the dynasty planned to deal with him, but now that we've caught Sagman and Taylor, the Ruler cancelled this plan. Just treat it as leaving some face for them."

"Oh, that's not too bad," Maximiler said. "We already have four captives, and Psyker has nowhere to run. If we continue to hammer at them, this might backfire on the dynasty."

The rest of the Beyond Grade As captured did not have any roots in the Shattered Star Ring, so they could only blame their bad luck. But Psyker could run but not hide since his base was in that area. If the dynasty forcefully tried to drag away a civilization's leader, this would result in a backfire, and the Arcane Church would also not watch blindly as that happened, or else they would lose the trust of their allies.

The dynasty was originally not afraid of such a consequence, but now that they had new captives, there was no need to poke the hornet's nest. Thus, they decided to wrap up while the going was good.

Of course, not capturing Psyker did not mean that they would condone his actions. There was still a need to suppress the development of the Star Pupil Holy Race, and if they could even chase this Arcane Church allied force out of the Star Field, that would be best.

The Crimson Dynasty had mobilized millions of battleships to pioneer the Flickering World, and now they were transferring part of its fleet to the Shattered Star Ring. The armed forces available in this Shattered Star Ring long exceed that of the other two universal civilizations, and even if the Federation of Light was the nominal ruling power here, all was useless before strength.

A pity. Han Xiao's brows furrowed. He felt it a regret not to be able to capture the other party, as he was interested in Psyker's body structure. However, every time he saw Psyker, he just wanted to poke the guy's eyes.

However, since he had taken away the national treasure of the Star Pupil Holy Race, both parties were like fire and water. Now that he still had to go over to the other party's territory and swagger, this attitude seemed to be bordering on arrogance.

Seems like I'd better bring more people, in case I get beaten up...

Chapter 867: Demonstration

The action plan was finalized. The dynasty troops would split into three sections; Milizaus and his group would take the captives back, Tarrokov would remain to command the fleet, and Han Xiao and Heber would clean up any loose ends by going to the Star Pupil Holy Race together.

Watching the dynasty's fleet leave, Han Xiao turned to look at Heber on the virtual screen of his spaceship and smiled.

"We're going to be partners again this time. When we arrive at the Star Pupil Holy Race, I hope you can live up to your namesake and be more tyrannical."

"Humph."

The virtual screen turned dark as Heber cut the connection, not deigning to speak with him. From the porthole, one could see the Bloodshed Land's troops turn and leave, morphing into rays of light.

Han Xiao clicked his tongue before calling Sylvia.

"Get Herlous to send a fleet to this meeting point. I've gotten Phillip to transfer the coordinates over to you."

"Roger that."

With this simple conversation over, Han Xiao cut the call. He realized that Sylvia was getting more and more capable, with him practically not needing to worry any longer.

"It feels as though I'm becoming more and more like Ames, turning into a arm-flinging shopkeeper[1]..."

As he played with his communicator, he could not resist bursting into laughter. He realized that if he were to turn into Ames, then Sylvia would become his Jenny.

To think that the heroic Mechanical Lady Knight of his past life had turned into an army affairs officer and head secretary. He did not know which the players would find more attractive, though he knew that Sylvia's favorability within the players was currently quite high.

This moment, Mad Sky Hunter took the initiative to lean over to Han Xiao, nudging him with its head. Han Xiao's mouth curled, and he proceeded to stroke the brain portion of Mad Sky Hunter, causing it to let out happy noises as it lowered its head, just like an actual pet getting petted.

Mad Sky Hunter would only behave like this in front of Han Xiao, its creator. As a beast-type Mechanical Life, its mannerisms had deviated a little from the norm. Upon accessing its web records, Han Xiao discovered that other than the combat resources, it had also downloaded dozens of pet videos from the internet. Most likely, it was attempting to learn how to behave like a pet, but its actions coupled with its sleek, glossy demeanor only served to give Han Xiao goosebumps.

If he really did pet it, the feeling he would get from his hands would be just plain weird. However, if he did not pet it, it would seem like he was not showing respect to its hard work.

Silver Flash stood coldly by the side, secretly showing disdain.

Humph, boot-licker!

Thinking about it, Han Xiao dialed Ames, and her elegant face soon appeared in front of his eyes.

"What do you want?"

"I have a mission here, which is to go to the Star Pupil Holy Race to bully Psyker. Are you interested?"

Ames supported her chin with her right hand, and her sleeves dropped down, revealing dazzling white skin. She blinked.

"I've realized that you seldom chat with me these days unless you have some business."

"Are you coming or not?"

"Let me check my schedule." Ames lifted her eyes, gazing past the screen toward someone by the side. She slowly asked, "Jenny, is there anything on Floating Dragon that I need to do?"

It took a long while before a brittle voice coupled with grinding teeth sounded.

"There is... but have you ever done it?"

Hearing this, Ames directly waved her hand. Han Xiao could not see what happened, but Jenny's voice seemed to have disappeared. Maybe... she got attacked by Ames' force field.

"Looks like I'm free. I'll head over." Ames looked like she was smiling yet not smiling, as though nothing had happened on her side.

"Sure." Han Xiao nodded his hand, choosing to ignore whatever had just happened.

"This is the mission assigned by the dynasty, so I believe it won't be just you."

"Yeah, Heber is involved this time, together with a few dynasty fleets."

"Heber is going too?" Ames narrowed her eyes. "Humph, I don't want to even see him. I'm not going. You can have fun with him."

Ames immediately cut the call off.

Han Xiao blinked in surprise, staring at the black screen in confusion.

Does she have that great a misgiving toward Heber, to just go back on her word like that‽

It seemed like he had underestimated how badly Heber failed in his attempt to use an iron-blooded man's method of courtship.

While the Crimson Dynasty was ferrying the four captives back, and their prestige was sweeping across the universe, the Star Pupil Holy Race within the Eternal Night Star System greeted an unexpected visitor.

Psyker held the highest authority here, and the Cabinet of ministers assisted him in managing government affairs. Some of the key personnel were high-levelled officials who held real power. This system obviously had drawbacks, but this was not a problem for Psyker. His strength and prestige granted him the right to speak, and because of his psychic ability, he was able to differentiate between thoughts and emotions, so no one could override him.

During this time, Psyker was not within the government, so the cabinet was in charge of daily matters. However, the two parties did not completely cut off their connection. While Psyker was on the run, he kept monitoring the affairs of his race. It was just that he was not at home, nor was he able to reveal his face openly. However, the public opinion surrounding him recently let many of the citizens in the Star Pupil Holy Race feel trepidation.

In particular, the dynasty catching Sagman and Taylor had attracted the worry of the Star Pupil Holy Race. They were afraid that their leader would also be snatched away and frightened that the Crimson Dynasty would turn toward the Star Pupil Holy Race for revenge.

Filled with all kinds of worries, a minority of people were secretly cursing Psyker.

Were you so free that you had to go and muddy the waters, making it so messy now!

This public opinion had been widely circulated among the Star Pupil Holy Race. A small group of people faced threats to their own security, so they were dissatisfied with their leader, Psyker. As for Psyker's past credits, it did not make a difference in their judgement because people tended to take things that were given to them for granted. It was a pity that Psyker did not succeed, or else the direction of public opinion would have been the opposite, praising him.

However, the extreme views of the minority would not be able to affect the stability of the civilization. Psyker's control over his race was not just made up of glue, and even if the future was unknown, the government was still operating.

The cabinet set down instructions to let people preach online that Psyker was in this situation in order to recapture their clan treasure, in order to shape Psyker's image of taking risks personally for the dignity of their race. This severely suppressed a batch of dissatisfied remarks.

At this moment, in the main hall of the cabinet, many key officials were discussing whether to enter a higher level of wartime emergency, inviting Psyker back and using troops to protect him.

A great number of senior military officials were participating in this meeting, each holding their own opinions and arguing fiercely.

At this moment, one of the officials received an intelligence report and suddenly had a change in expression, slamming the table as he read out the report.

"Border Post 17 has detected a large dynasty fleet with tens of millions of battleships, including Black Star Army and Bloodshed Land troops.

"What‽"

All the members present were shocked and horrified.

Did the worst situation happen, and the dynasty troops had really chosen to kill their way over?

Before they could react, the second report arrived.

"The other party has stopped at the border and did not forcibly intrude. They are now negotiating with the border officer. Black Star and Tyrant are commanding this fleet, and their intentions are unknown."

The hearts that were in the cabinet members' throats slowly fell back down. They stared at the officer with grudging eyes.

Could you not speak in such an emotional tone? You nearly scared us to death!

After their shock subsided, everyone's senses came back online.

"That's right. With such tens of millions of battleships, it doesn't seem like they came here to declare war."

"What's their intentions? Could it be that they're going to force us to hand over our leader?"

"This... What do we do then? Won't we still clash with them that way?"

All the people present had on difficult expressions.

Very quickly, the third report was sent over.

"Black Star and the Tyrant have said that they came over to visit the Star Pupil Holy Race, and they wish to talk to Psyker."

The cabinet members looked at each other.

With such a mighty army, they're saying that they've come here for a visit. Do they think we're fools?

The fleet clearly did not come with good intentions.

"If we reject their request, do you think they will wait outside the border, or will they resort to violence?" one of the cabinet members asked.

Everyone simply stared at the person wordlessly.

Do you think that the troops and Beyond Grade As sent out by the dynasty are here for sightseeing? Giving them the cold shoulder is akin to refusing a toast and choosing the forfeit instead. How could they possibly take it lying down?

Brother, how did you get into the cabinet? Did you pull strings?

"This matter is already out of our scope of authority. Report to Leader Psyker and let him decide."

The cabinet then contacted the escaping Psyker.

Not long after, the communication was linked.

Surveying the scene, Psyker noticed their heavy expressions and asked, "What's happened?"

"Leader, the Crimson Dynasty has come to pressure us..." One of the officers explained the matter once more.

After he finished, the room was so quiet you could hear a pin drop. Everyone was waiting for his response.

Psyker took a deep breath, closing his eyes. After a while, he slowly opened them.

"Receive them. I'll rush back right now."

"But they are targeting you!"

A few of the people had panicked expressions, but they secretly heaved sighs of relief.

If Psyker had chosen to run and not come out to take responsibility for this matter, there would have been no way for them to clear up this mess.

"Their method of doing so is just to force me to return. Black Star and Heber understand me. They know that I would not leave my race and escape." Psyker's expression turned calm. "There's no point in running, and I have to face them sooner or later. This is the price of failure."

Those present all revealed faces of indignation.

"Don't worry, the dynasty already has four captives. Them visiting the Star Pupil Holy Race might not be to capture me." Psyker shook his head.

He did not dare return, other than to observe the situation, because he expected the dynasty not to take the risk to violate the Peace Treaty. While his base was situated there, the dynasty would definitely not go head to head against him just to capture him. He just did not wish to put his race in danger, so he was not willing to accept the protection of his civilization's troops. However, to prevent any problems, he did not move too far away and had always been hovering near his territory.

"Understood. We'll open the border and escort them to one of the planets," one of the commanders solemnly replied.

The security of one's territory was important, but they also had to take the initiative to open the border and meet with more aggressive guests. The dynasty's faction was undoubtedly exerting pressure, and everyone was placed in a state of unease.

Before long, the Star Pupil Holy Race sent troops over to the border to welcome them, and other than a large portion of the Crimson Dynasty troops remaining at the border, Han Xiao and Heber brought some troops and followed the Star Pupil Holy Race troops to a colonial planet.

The Star Pupil Holy Race evidently did not want to let too many people discover this matter, so the spaceships stopped directly within the inner administrative area of the planet. Before the emissary that was qualified to receive the two arrived, the local lord of the colonial planet performed the reception work himself.

After disembarking from the spaceship, Han Xiao and Heber were led to the reception room. Following from behind, Han Xiao could see that they were on edge, and beads of sweat could be seen trickling down his neck.

The surrounding soldiers were also nervous and alert, staring at Han Xiao and Heber with a death gaze while gripping their weapons tightly.

Heber was used to such fear coming from people and took large steps with his Vanguard Officials following close behind. This group often gave off a strange impression, as though they were going to shout out "Fitness is key!" at any given moment.

On Han Xiao's side, he was observing the architectural style of the Star Pupil Holy Race casually, with Hila, his Black Star Guards, and the four Apostle Weapons behind him.

They both had brought their own Calamity Grade elites, as well as many officers from the Crimson Dynasty.

Upon arriving, everyone took their seats, and the local lord wiped his sweat, carefully saying, "The Emissary is on his way. Please hold on for a moment."

Heber was akin to a tiny mountain as he sat on the sofa. He had a pressuring aura, his arms folded as he asked, "When will Psyker return?"

"This... this... I do not know..."

The local lord was pressured by his momentum to the point his throat was locked in place. He barely managed to speak, his sweat beginning to flow again like a waterfall.

Han Xiao casually picked up one of the fruits on the table, which looked like a melon that was dyed blue. He bit into it and chewed a few times, before wiping his mouth and flicking it toward Heber.

"I've tried it. There's no poison, so you can eat in peace."

Heber's face twitched.

I'm over here trying to posture, yet you threw me the fruit. You're totally spoiling this atmosphere!

Furthermore, I'm a pugilist. Why would I need a mechanic like you to test for poison‽

The fruit was already thrown over, and it would not be good to let it drop on the ground. Thus, Heber could only catch it and then fling it to one of his Vanguard Officials behind him.

This time, Heber could not be bothered to speak and only closed his eyes. Han Xiao did not press the issue either, half closing his eyes as he enjoyed the feeling of Aurora massaging his temples.

The atmosphere thus quieted down.

While the surrounding guards were at the ready, after seeing the nonchalant attitudes of the duo, they had to suppress their rage.

Atrocious, these people are not showing the Star Pupil Holy Race the slightest respect!

Especially Black Star, this evildoer. Not only did he steal our clan treasure, he actually dared run over to our territory. How arrogant!

The guards held onto the weapons tight, almost wanting to shoot at Han Xiao. However, their reasoning stopped them.

The situation was more important than the people. The dynasty was going whatever they wanted in the Shattered Star Ring, and their backer, the Arcane Church, had also suffered losses, so they naturally would not dare make any rash moves.

Very soon, the surrounding guards swapped shifts, and Calamity Grades took over as the guards. They stared unceasingly at Han Xiao and Heber as though meeting their mortal enemies.

After a period of time, hurried footsteps could be heard from the door, and an emissary soon walked in with a few of his subordinates.

"Your Excellency Black Star, Your Excellency Heber, Crimson Dynasty emissaries, I'm the person in charge of welcoming you. You may refer to me as Jed."

Jed slightly bowered, but his tone was neither arrogant nor humble.

Heber opened his eyes again and again asked, "When will Psyker arrive?"

"We're not too sure ourselves. The leader has his own schedule and may take as little as several days to half a month. Please wait for a while. We'll provide accommodation if both of you wish to stay," Jed blandly replied.

Boom!

The pressure around Heber's body intensified, and the room seemed as though a formless hurricane had been born within it.

He coldly stared at Jed as he spoke,

"Don't try to play dumb. Psyker has always been hovering around the Star Pupil Holy Race and will not be too far away. I'll give you three days. If I do not see him in person, you can handle the consequences yourself."

Jed only felt his breathing become labored. He was pressured to the point he could hardly breathe and could only nod with difficulty. "I'll convey your intentions to the upper echelons..."

At this time, Han Xiao opened his eyes, gesturing for Aurora to stop, before looking interestedly at Jed.

"I just took a gander around your network and realized that your side seems to be very keen to block off the news. Not many of them know that we came over for a visit."

Upon thinking of Han Xiao's ability, Jed's expression changed. "What do you intend to do?"

"It's no good to withhold information like that. Let me help you guys."

Han Xiao smiled, and with a thought, the data packet that Phillip had prepared was immediately sent to the major media channels of the Star Pupil Holy Race and forcibly promoted.

It could be roughly summarized as...

'The dynasty fleet comes to settle accounts, Star Pupil Holy Race trembles in fear!'

'Black Star and the Tyrant show up, but Psyker dares not meet them!'

'Psyker flees due to his crimes, leaving behind his race!'

All of the articles showed the Star Pupil Holy Race in a cowardly light and how Psyker did not dare take responsibility, which made the citizens of the race feel suffocated, cracking the prestige of Psyker.

With his current Virtual Technology skills, this news instantly broke the barriers of public opinion that were silenced and swept through the entire network of the Star Pupil Holy Race.

Psyker had brought him a huge crisis this time, and now that he had come over on behalf of the dynasty to apply pressure, Han Xiao would naturally not be polite. Only when Psyker showed himself would he then command Phillip to stop.

Jed walked to the side, and after exchanging a few sentences with the upper echelons, he approached Han Xiao with a strict expression.

"Your Excellency Black Star, please stop such behavior, or else..."

Bang!

Before he could finish, Jed's head was captured by a large hand and ruthlessly slammed on the table.

The entire table cracked!

The person holding onto his head was a Vanguard Official of Bloodshed Land, Fosters. He coldly commented, "Watch your attitude when you speak to us. If there's a next time, I'll break your head apart."

The moment the grip was released, Jed stumbled and retreated, a furious expression on his face.

However, he had no choice but to swallow this injustice. He took out his handkerchief to wipe off the blue blood flowing down his head.

When the Calamity Grades saw them being so arrogant, their faces got uglier, and the rage smoldered within their hearts. However, because this impacted the entire race, they chose not to move, instead keeping the resentment within their hearts.

Han Xiao raised his eyebrows as he gestured at Heber. He seemed to be saying, If you compare viciousness, you're still more vicious.

Look at how much bullsh*t you have to say, Heber seemed to reply with a look.

Meanwhile, the news caused a sensation on the internet. Countless citizens burst into anger, some scolding the dynasty for taking advantage and others smearing the name of their leader. Some of them were also worried that Psyker would never return. There were innumerable emotions.

Countless people wished to recapture their national treasure, so the hatred the Star Pupil Holy Race had toward Han Xiao was not light. Han Xiao did not care about the hostility, though, as the more hostile they were, the more it meant that Psyker's prestige was affected.

Jed did not speak, but one of the guards could not take it any longer and suddenly lashed out at Han Xiao.

"Don't you have a conscience! After stealing our clan treasure, you dare come here and flaunt it!"

After this sentence was spoken, everyone turned over.

A chilling gaze passed through Hila's eyes, and she was just about to move. However, Han Xiao gestured for her to hold back and turned to look at the guard.

"What's your name?"

"Lalem!" The guard was obviously out of control and extremely emotional.

"Hmm, ok, then what would you have me do?"

"Of course, you should return our national treasure!"

"Okay." Han Xiao nodded, taking out the Evolution Cube and throwing it into the guard's hands. "Catch."

Everyone from the Star Pupil Holy Race was stunned, staring incredulously at the Evolution Cube.

"You, you..."

"Didn't you say you wanted it? Now it's in your hands." Han Xiao smiled. "However, I have to warn you. If you walk out of this room, it means that you have snatched the Evolution Cube, and that would mean that the dynasty would send their expeditionary fleet over. Are you ready to handle that?"

The guard's face turned purple in anger and humiliation.

"You're just relying on your backer! Do you have any morality in your heart‽"

Lifting his hand, Han Xiao retrieved the Evolutionary Cube, shaking his head as he spoke. "You all claim that it's your national treasure, but this thing was not created by you. Just by using it for a long period of time, it becomes yours, huh? This is the inheritance of the Evolutionary Civilization, and you guys are the same in that you picked it up, holding on through strength. It never belonged to you, yet you call it your 'national treasure'... There's also another point. I did not snatch your Evolutionary Cube. It was you guys who lost it, and I picked it up. I merely refused to hand it over to others, just like you guys so many years ago. This question of stance should not be used as an excuse for morality. That would be so meaningless."

"Bullsh*t. We've used the Evolution Cube for so long and can be considered its owner. Leader Psyker has always been connected to the Evolution Cube, so of course it's ours!" the guard raged.

"This does make sense, but since you guys failed to guard your belongings, it was stolen by EsGod. I didn't steal it; I merely chose not to return it. Furthermore, because this item was not the creation of your civilization, I have no mental burden toward withholding it for myself... If you guys can snatch it back from me, I can't do anything about it, but your strength is insufficient, so anything else you say is meaningless. I gave you a chance, but you didn't dare take it away. Let's just forget about it."

Han Xiao shook his head. He had never been a kind person, and he had another motive here, which was to resolve the hidden danger of the Evolution Cube once and for all. He planned to use pressure to force the citizens and Psyker to lift their psychic link with it!

As for right or wrong... Psyker had endangered his life many times. Now that things had gotten to this point, there was no need to worry about this issue.

"You, leave." Jed waved toward the guard. While he was also furious about losing the 'national treasure', he was more realistic and knew that the dynasty had come to pressure them. It would be a pipe dream to make them hand over the Evolution Cube.

Having witnessed this little spat, Heber threw a glance over to Han Xiao.

"You're not too bad at being evil yourself."

"As to you."

Han Xiao rolled his eyes in response.

One needed to be more arrogant when posturing to apply pressure. For someone like him, who was used to being low-key, this was difficult to do.

[1] He's referring to a leader that only delegates work but never does any Back

Chapter 868: Lock On Removed

The Star Pupil Holy Race fleet in the surroundings immediately gathered toward the planet and awaited their orders. At the same time, the defensive fleet at the border was also strengthened.

After waiting for two days, Psyker finally reached the border.

"Your Excellencies, Leader Psyker has already reached the border and will be here soon."

Jed heaved a sigh of relief.

His appearance was much frailer than before. Over the past two days, he had stayed in the room together with Han Xiao and Heber. He had suggested that the two go to a guest room, but Heber and Han Xiao did not even reply to him. Furthermore, they did not allow him to leave either, so Jed could only accompany the two in the room over the past two days. He did not even dare sleep, and his mental state was already on the brink of collapse.

To a Beyond Grade A Super, two days was no big deal at all. They could easily close their eyes, and two days would be over in a flash. Furthermore, the guards of the Star Pupil Holy Race present were all in the Calamity Grade and would not be affected too greatly. Only someone like Jed who was an envoy from the government would feel fatigue.

If they went to the guest room, the pressure that both of them had accumulated would be gone. As such, they chose to sit here for two days to increase the pressure on the Star Pupil Holy Race.

After waiting a while longer, a commotion could be heard on the outside, and both of them could feel a powerful energy source approaching them.

Heber opened his eyes and nodded. "He's here."

The door opened, and Psyker walked into the room slowly. Everyone's gaze was then focused on him.

The guards present all heaved sighs of relief and stood up straight as though they had found their backbone.

"Eh, isn't this Little Psy-Psy? The hero has finally appeared," Han Xiao teased.

Psyker walked over to the two. Jed, who was originally seated, immediately gave up his seat for Psyker.

"Didn't both of you want to meet me? I'm back. Get straight to the point," Psyker said with a deep voice.

The next second, Han Xiao's arm suddenly transformed into a mechanical arm, and he swung it out toward Psyker.

The table and sofa in front of him was pushed away, and his palm sent Psyker flying into the wall.

Bang!

The entire room erupted!

"What did you do‽"

The faces of the guards all changed, and they wanted to take action to help their leader.

Right at this moment, Hila and the other Black Star Guards also sent their auras toward the guards in the surrounding with the intention to warn them. The Bloodshed Land's Vanguard Officials did the same.

Just when the situation was about to erupt, Psyker's voice sounded from under the mechanical arm.

"Don't move."

The mechanical arm was retracted, and Psyker dislodged himself from the alloy wall with his Psychic energy. He then looked at Han Xiao without any intention of fighting back.

"I almost took your life. Do you have any issues?" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

"... No."

Psyker took a deep breath and knew that Han Xiao wanted to take him down a notch. He then told his subordinates not to act recklessly and got them to bring a new table in.

The members of the Star Pupil Holy Race in the surroundings clenched their fists with aggrieved expressions.

They were able to understand why Psyker chose to give in but could not help but feel disappointed. On one hand, they were enraged at their own weakness, and on the other hand, they felt humiliated on behalf of their race.

Although all of them knew that the dynasty was there to seek an answer from them, they were all hoping that Psyker would be able to deal with such a situation and turn the tides. However, the unacceptable truth was that their leader was there to suffer humiliation.

The Crimson Dynasty emissary, who had not said a word so far, then said calmly, "You participated in the attack on Planet Lighthouse, and four of the six Beyond Grade As who participated have already been caught. The dynasty needs you and the Star Pupil Holy Race to give us an explanation."

"What kind of explanation?" Psyker asked.

The dynasty's emissary then tapped his bracelet, and a holographic screen appeared. A contract appeared on the holographic screen.

"You have to give a public apology and sign this compensation contract to prove your sincerity. The details of the contract are all within it. If you don't agree, please follow us to accept your judgement in the dynasty or wait for the Arcane Church to pay a ransom."

"Compensation and apology?" Psyker murmured under his breath. He had not been idle over the past two days and had been thinking of what the dynasty's intention would be. This was not out of his expectations at all.

The dynasty emissary did not bother keeping the matter a secret and read the entire contract out. There were many outrageous demands, and the members of the Star Pupil Holy Race watching by the side became more and more enraged.

There were only two options placed before Psyker at the moment. First, apologize and pay compensation. Second, become a captive. Of course, there was a third option, which was to fight back. However, the dynasty would not show him any face if he chooses the third option.

The dynasty did not necessarily need that little compensation but needed the enemy to give in.

After listening to all the terms, Psyker nodded and said, "I accept the contract. I will make a public apology for my actions."

He was not too bothered about the astronomical compensation. He was working for the Arcane Church, and although he had failed, the Arcane Church would not let him suffer the cost of the compensation. If they did not do that much, nobody would want to help them in the future. Thus, the compensation would be paid by the Arcane Church, so there was no need for the Star Pupil Holy Race to spend money.

As for a public apology, this was also something that the Arcane Church would want to see. The Arcane Church would never apologize to the dynasty, but since they wanted to redeem their people, they would have to give in somehow. Thus, the Star Pupil Holy Race giving in would be a representation of the Arcane Church's attitude.

Even if the Arcane Church was the backer of the Star Pupil Holy Race, the Crimson Dynasty was also a Universal Civilization. With both parties in conflict with each other, the Star Pupil Holy Race definitely had to give an explanation.

Psyker understood this clearly, but most members of his race did not.

In the eyes of the others, their leader had accepted such humiliating conditions without any hesitation. This made the faces of all those present turn ugly, and the look in their eyes became complicated.

The way they saw it, Psyker seemed to be protecting himself and betraying the benefits of the race without any hesitation. Of course, they knew that this was far from the truth, but they could not help but think that way.

Although they knew that Psyker did not make a mistake in his decision, many of them could not help but feel anger and humiliation.

Right at this moment, Heber said, "Psyker, leave the Shattered Star Ring together with your people. You know that we and the dynasty will not allow you to develop. Your best option is to leave."

Having one less Beyond Grade A in the Shattered Star Ring would benefit everyone else. Heber and the dynasty had the same thought.

Psyker shook his head and said, "Regardless of how tough the situation is, we will not leave our homeland as long as we can overcome it."

"Humph." Heber did not say anything else upon hearing that.

At this moment, Han Xiao piped up. "The following matter will be between us. You have given an explanation to the dynasty, but you also need to give an explanation to the victim."

Psyker turned around and asked, "What do you want?"

Han Xiao smiled.

"I want the Evolution Cube."

Everyone was stunned.

"Haven't you snatched it already?" Psyker asked doubtfully.

"No, you misunderstood me," Han Xiao said calmly. "I want you to get rid of the psychic connection that you have with the Evolution Cube and announce to the universe that you have given it to me."

Psyker's expression changed abruptly.

He finally understood what Black Star's intention was!

The members of the Star Pupil Holy Race originally thought that Black Star had stolen their national treasure, so if he publicly announced that he had given the item to Black Star, he would no longer have any right to criticize the other party. At that time, the members of his race would divert their humiliation to their leader and vent all their anger on him. His status as a leader would also fall greatly.

"You b*stard..." Psyker gritted his teeth.

"Because of the Evolution Cube, you tried to deal with me time and time again," Han Xiao said. "The ambush this time was also because of the Evolution Cube. If I do not make you give up on the Evolution Cube, something like this will happen again. I haven't settled the score regarding the Avitan Souls trying to blow up Planet Aquamarine yet. Take a look at this video first."

Han Xiao then summoned a holographic screen, and the scene of the guard called Lalem criticizing him was played. Phillip had recorded the entire scene.

Psyker's face became extremely ugly after the video was completed.

Han Xiao raised his brows and said, "She provoked a Beyond Grade A, but I wasn't too calculative with her. I don't wish to hear bullsh*t like that again, so I decided to make use of a solution to settle this matter once and for all. What do you think?"

Psyker suppressed his anger. "What if I disagree?"

"You can also choose to disagree." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and released his aura. "However, are you still my opponent? Have you ever thought about what would happen to your Star Pupil Holy Race without you as their leader?"

At this instant, Psyker realized that the Black Star in front of him was no longer the one who had fought him to a draw. He then thought about the scene of Han Xiao capturing Dylan and felt a trace of fear.

However, he was still reluctant to give up the Evolution Cube. He had formed a Soul Connection with the Evolution Cube, and his psychic energy was strengthened as a result. Without the Universal Treasure, his own combat strength would fall, and his status would also be lowered in the Arcane Church.

The dynasty emissary then said calmly, "Black Star's intention is the dynasty's intention. If you don't agree, we can add it into the contract."

Han Xiao had not discussed this matter with the dynasty yet, but this matter was not disadvantageous to the dynasty at all. Thus, the emissary's support was extremely normal.

Upon hearing that, Psyker's clenched fists loosened, and he said softly, "... I agree."

Bang!

A Calamity Grade Star Pupil Holy Race guard finally could not restrain his anger any further and hammered down on the wall.

The other guards were angered to the point their bodies were trembling. Han Xiao and the others had completely ignored them.

Han Xiao nodded and took out the Evolution Cube. The silver cube floated in midair and attracted everyone's attention.

Heber's throat also twitched slightly, but his subordinates did not notice.

"Then, please show your sincerity and undo your psychic connection."

Psyker shut his eyes and released his psychic energy to come into contact with the Evolution Cube. Gritting his teeth, he cut off the connection with the Evolution Cube.

The next moment, his body trembled, and his mind could clearly feel that the bridge between him and the Evolution Cube had been broken.

The ability to locate the cube had also disappeared.

"It's done," Psyker said with a soft tone and tried to conceal his sadness.

Han Xiao retrieved the Evolution Cube. The senses of a Beyond Grade A were extremely sharp, and he could clearly feel the aura latched onto the Evolution Cube disappearing.

I finally got rid of this hidden threat... Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief. Although the Spacetime Amber had a similar effect, he would still have to use the Evolution Cube from time to time, and this would get rid of all troubles for good.

However, he still passed the cube over to Feidin to take a look. Although Feidin was only a Calamity Grade, his luck was unrivaled.

"Don't worry, your dynasty also has Beyond Grade A Psychics, so it will be extremely easy to tell. You don't have to worry that I will leave anything behind," Psyker said with a depressed tone. "I have fulfilled your conditions already. Do you have anything else? Please leave the territory of the Star Pupil Holy Race if there's nothing else."

The dynasty emissary then stood up and said, "Alright, we shall not disturb you any further. The dynasty will be watching you and waiting for your announcement."

Psyker gnashed his teeth but did not say anything.

"Don't blame me." Han Xiao also stood up. "You have to pay the price for failing. At least you are still alive."

"I will not always fail," Psyker said.

"You also won't be alive all the time." Heber then walked out of the room with the dynasty emissary behind him.

Walking out of the door, Han Xiao turned around to look at Psyker. "Rather than being angry at us, you should take care of all your troubles."

Psyker ignored those words and asked, "How is Dylan?"

"You still have the time to care about others? It seems like you have a pretty good relationship with him." Han Xiao smirked. "Don't worry, he is safe... very safe."

Han Xiao then waved his hands and left.

A while later, Psyker received a report that Han Xiao and the others had left the planet.

After a long while, Psyker raised his head and sighed.

"Get the government to hold a press conference. I will make a personal appearance."

Jed hesitated for a while before reminding him, "Black Star used his Virtual Technology skills and infiltrated many of our media websites, posting many rumors about you. Should we deal with that first?"

"That isn't necessary. Black Star will stop after he leaves. Although he is a vicious individual, he won't always play such petty tricks," Psyker replied. "After I make an announcement, all of you will know that these rumors aren't considered anything."

Upon thinking about the effect of his announcement, Psyker could not help but feel depressed.

However, he did not have a choice. Even if he approached his backer, they would not come into conflict with the dynasty because of Psyker's reputation.

His personal reputation was not at the top of the Arcane Church's priority list.

Chapter 869: Federation of Light, Do You Think I'm Invisible?

Their spaceships left the Star Pupil Holy Race territory and met up together with the dynasty's fleet before disappearing into space.

The dynasty emissary turned around to look at the two beside him and smiled.

"Psyker has been extremely cooperative, and the mission has been a success."

Heber waved his hands with an expressionless face to indicate that this was a small matter.

He was also able to increase his prestige by flaunting his might before another Beyond Grade A. Furthermore, since the Star Pupil Holy Race had agreed to apologize and pay compensation, this matter would definitely be recorded in history, and his name would be included. This was a pretty good reward for him.

"Psyker lost big this time. He will probably remain stagnant for a long time." Han Xiao smiled.

With the hidden trouble of the Evolution Cube gone, he was in a good mood.

"That's right. Psyker will have to deal with the aftermath of this event and the other competing Star Cluster Civilizations. He will have to remain low profile for the next few decades for sure," the dynasty emissary added. "I have to report my success to Zoel. Your Excellencies, let's say goodbye here."

Heber and Han Xiao nodded. After recording the number of this emissary, they both returned to their spaceships and left.

"I will also be leaving." Heber sent Han Xiao a message before leaving with his Bloodshed Land troops. He was prepared to return to the Flickering World and overlook the exploration mission.

The wedge between them had not been resolved, and it would be difficult for them to have a good relationship. But after experiencing this incident together, the relationship between the allies of the dynasty had improved.

Han Xiao put his communicator away and ordered Phillip, "Return to the Black Star Army headquarters."

"Roger, hum..."

The Black Star Army battleship then sped up and entered warp-speed hyperdrive.

It was time to handle the Evolution Cube slots that he had promised the civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring. The dynasty would also send a batch of new elites for the Evolution Cube. Han Xiao was planning to take care of these matters before continuing the exploration of the Flickering World.

The influence of this event was truly large, and he had a battle record of capturing another Beyond Grade A. His personal prestige was increased to the next level, and for a long period of time, there should not be anyone making trouble for him. This should continue until the end of Version 3.0.

The only hidden trouble that worried him was EsGod.

The space coordinates of the World Tree Civilization were like a time bomb. An advanced civilization who grasped the coordinates would know how to test waters and protect themselves. However, it was impossible to predict what someone like EsGod would do.

It was a pity that EsGod managed to receive the evolution energy this round and become stronger. Without finding some companions, it would be truly difficult to deal with EsGod.

To the Crimson Dynasty, the Arcane Church was their true competitor that they needed to pay close attention to. They would only deal with EsGod after reaching an agreement with each other.

It was not easy to deal with EsGod. If they sent too few experts, they would not be able to win. If they sent too many experts, the other party would just escape. The dynasty had tried to deal with EsGod many times before but were not able to kill him. This time, they probably only intended to get rid of EsGod's comrades.

Furthermore, the intelligence of the dynasty showed that EsGod had left the Star Field through a wormhole, and his whereabouts were currently unknown. Thus, it was pointless to think about dealing with EsGod at this moment.

Han Xiao decided to wait for the experience penalty period to be over before increasing his level. He would only have a greater chance of success if he could increase his strength.

"There is less than half a year until the penalty is over..."

Han Xiao greatly anticipated that moment.

A few days later, Psyker finally appeared publicly within his race and called for a press conference.

With the recent rumors, the citizens of the Star Pupil Holy Race were extremely anxious, and they all stayed in front of the television to watch the news.

Time seemed to pass extremely slowly.

It was finally the time for the life broadcast, and everyone felt their heart tighten up.

Psyker's figure appeared on the screen, and he said with a solemn voice, "Citizens of the Star Pupil Holy Race, my colleagues of the government, I am Psyker. I shall give an official explanation regarding the recent storm...

"In the past few months, news about me has been spreading throughout the universe.

"First, I have to express my deepest apology to everyone. It was because of a mistake that resulted in me being trapped in a dilemma and dragging the race down. I am guilty and embarrassed by this, but a mistake is a mistake, and I shall not defend myself.

"A few days ago, the Crimson Dynasty paid a visit and sought an explanation from me. I did not escape like the rumors on the net but rushed back immediately to negotiate with the Crimson Dynasty's emissary. Both parties have already arrived at an initial agreement.

"On behalf of the Star Pupil Holy Race and myself, I will apologize to the Crimson Dynasty for the recent event and adhere to the compensation terms as follows..."

Psyker then read out a list of compensation terms before continuing.

"I also apologize sincerely to the victim Black Star and am willing to give compensation because of this event.

"There is a fact that cannot be avoided. The Evolution Cube is the item of another civilization and not one that belongs solely to the Star Pupil Holy Race. Because of some unexpected reasons, we lost the Evolution Cube, and the one who should be blamed is EsGod, not Black Star. We have already enjoyed the benefits of the Evolution Cube. I will let go of all rights to the Evolution Cube here and transfer it to Black Star as compensation.

"My citizens, our Star Pupil Holy Race has experienced phenomenal economic, cultural, and other forms of achievements. We have fallen into a valley, but there will always be new opportunities to greet us after every calamity. I hope that everyone will continue working together and maintain your optimism to go through this tough period together.

"I hope that everyone can understand our choice and not forget our humiliation today.

"Finally, I wish everyone a happy life."

As his speech was finished, the screen darkened.

An intense eruption exploded from every corner of the Star Pupil Holy Race.

Many individuals were thoroughly shocked by the press conference!

A civilization had to give in publicly and even pay compensation. They could not help but feel a sense of humiliation.

Furthermore, this disaster was a result of Psyker's mistake, and the entire race had been dragged down by him.

Furthermore, Psyker had even openly abandoned their national treasure and given it to the demon Black Star?

The way they saw it, this was akin to them giving away the Evolution Cube because they were not able to snatch it back!

Such humiliation!

The press conference immediately created a huge sensation, and every corner of the Star Pupil Holy Race was filled with curses toward Psyker. The prestige that he had built up over the many years had gone down the drain, with some even calling him a disgrace to their race.

All the close aides of Psyker stood before him with ugly expressions.

"Your Excellency Psyker, should we really not control the negative public opinion on the web?"

Psyker shook his head and said, "That isn't necessary. The citizens need an avenue to vent the humiliation and anger in their hearts. When they are done venting it, they will remember the contributions that I have made, and we can guide the public opinion back in the right direction subtly when the time comes."

"This isn't beneficial to your prestige," someone said with concern.

"There will definitely be a rebound effect when it reaches the peak." Psyker sighed. "Regardless of worship or hatred, it will definitely slide in the other direction when it reaches the peak. When public opinion reaches the peak, there will be more and more people speaking up for me. That will be far more effective than trying to manage the situation now."

"Is this really good?"

"There isn't anything bad about it." Psyker let out a long sigh. "My previous contributions cannot be an excuse for my mistake. The greater my radiance, the greater the shadow. My mistakes have naturally been highlighted. I do not want everyone to praise my good deeds. This humiliation will be motivation for our citizens."

"We are only afraid that you will be disappointed in us," one of his aides said.

Psyker was the leader of the Star Pupil Holy Race, but after becoming a Beyond Grade A, Psyker himself was no longer part of the Star Pupil Holy Race. This was a shadow in the hearts of many.

"Don't worry. I will never forget my mother clan."

Psyker shook his head. As a Beyond Grade A, his ideals would not be so easily shaken.

"The world is complicated, and I will never judge the world by looking at a small corner of it. The words of a small group cannot represent the entire race. At the very end, all these people will realize that regardless of how they curse, I will still be their leader, and this is something that they are unable to change.

"As for the current storm now..."

As Psyker spoke with a smile, a trace of fatigue could be seen in his eyes.

"Fire will burn out, and the storm will end eventually. We just need to do our job and wait for it to cease naturally."

"The Star Pupil Holy Race has given in."

On the mother planet of the Arcane Church, Psyker's press conference was displayed in the conference room. The Bishops then fell into a moment of silence.

After a long while, one of the bishops said with a hoarse tone, "This way, the dynasty's attitude should ease up slightly, right?"

Psyker had cut off his connection to the Evolution Cube and lost the ability to locate it. The Arcane Church had also decided to give up on the Evolution Cube for good.

"How is the discussion with the dynasty coming along?"

"The dynasty only agreed to allow us to ransom Mercer and Dylan. Their price is extremely high."

"Hmm, pay the ransom for both of them first. This will satisfy the allies who are watching. As for Taylor and Sagman, the dynasty will not allow us to ransom them back too quickly, but our allies will understand."

"Where is Ninjia?"

"He has already escaped through a secret stargate set up by our spies. He will be back soon."

"Thankfully, the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is with him."

The Bishops then heaved a sigh of relief.

Of the six Beyond Grade As that they had sent out, four had been caught, one did not have anywhere to run, and only one managed to return to the Central Galaxy. Thankfully, the only one who returned was the one with the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter.

The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was even more important than a Beyond Grade A in the eyes of the upper echelons. New Beyond Grade As would be born over time, but every Universal Treasure was unique.

Not losing the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was their biggest consolation.

Because the Crimson Dynasty was searching the entire Shattered Star Ring, the spy could only construct the secret stargate in a desolate universe belt near the Shattered Star Ring.

A spaceship was currently rushing toward the stargate with Ninjia inside.

The stargate appeared within his sights, and Ninjia heaved a sigh of relief.

After entering this stargate, he would be able to skip past a few Star Fields and return to the Central Galaxy. After running for his life for such a long time, he could no longer endure such a life.

Hum!

Right at this moment, the spaceship trembled, and the engine of his spaceship was suddenly turned off.

"What's going on?"

Ninjia was startled, and he tried to control the spaceship. However, all his orders were completely useless, and the spaceship did not react at all.

The body of the spaceship suddenly shook.

Rumble!

A gigantic pressure crushed down from all directions, and the spaceship was reduced to a pile of scrap metal.

Bang!

A spherical protective shield then appeared from within the wreckage of the spaceship. Ninjia covered himself with a magical shield and held onto the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter while observing his surroundings carefully.

Could it be that the dynasty had discovered the stargate and set up an ambush‽

Right at this moment, a voice rang in his head.

"It truly wasn't easy to find you, 'Divine Spell' Ninjia. Hand over the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, and I can let you go."

As the voice sounded, the universe around him lit up with the light of hyperdrive, and many silhouettes appeared before him, filling the entire region.

Many pairs of expressionless eyes were fixed on Ninjia.

At the very front was a tall figure with his entire body shining with electrical bolts. The engravings on his body showed that this was a mechanical host.

Ninjia's expression changed abruptly upon seeing the person before him.

"Manison‽"

Chapter 870: Manison's Interest

Blood trickled down in rivulets, flowing on the metallic surface like crimson snakes and converging into a pool of blood.

Ninjia was sprawled on the ground, covered with bruises and bloodstains. Underneath him was a huge mechanical suction cup in the shape of a triangle, lit with a faint blue light. It was this huge gravitational force that fixed him to the ground.

His hands, feet, and torso were also bound by heavy-looking black alloy rings. This was a special mechanical shackle. With a strong interference field attached and through the use of spatial conversion technology, it could disperse the energy released by the target.

At the same time, four pipes protruded from the ground on both sides, inserting into his spine and injecting nano worms that interfered with his pneumatic operations, causing his nervous system to go haywire, affecting his control.

Ninjia could only barely lift his neck. His vision was blurred but was fixed toward an area full of mechanical limbs, where a dense number of mechanical soldiers were surrounding him.

Both parties were currently on the surface of a steel fortress, a mobile base brought by Manison, and there were marks of battle and broken mechanical parts scattered everywhere.

Because space was locked by Manison's spatial stabilizer equipment, along with magic jamming to render teleportation invalid, Ninjia could only fight.

However, with the numerous equipment and machinery he had with him other than the host he utilized for [Lord's Descent], there were still four other Apostle Weapons, which made it such that Ninjia was not his opponent.

"I was waiting for you to utilize the scepter, but you did not. Now I can see why..."

Manison caressed the amber sealing the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, feeling the energy insulation properties and letting out sounds of praise.

"To dare snatch even our Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, Manison, are you not afraid of angering my Arcane Church‽" Ninjia gritted his teeth.

"Don't be mistaken. I'm not interested in the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter; I'm just doing the Federation of Light a favor."

Manison eyed Ninjia before waving his hand.

A silver Apostle Weapon walked over, its body as smooth as a mirror without any sort of mechanical seams.

The Apostle Weapon squatted down, turned its fingers into spikes, and inserted them into Ninjia's body. After which, its entire body turned liquid and flowed into his body through the wounds.

Next, Manison released the shackles. However, the Apostle Weapon within Ninjia's body suppressed his ability to control his body, and he could only glare at Manison.

"What do you want to do to me‽"

"The Federation of Light allowed me to kill you and destroy the evidence. However, your body is still useful to me."

Manison threw out a compressed orb, which transformed into a restraint cabin, locking Ninjia within.

After confirming that he could not escape, Manison turned his head, gazing at the amber-sealed Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. An interested look appeared in his eyes.

"Oh, what a special new material, and it seems like Black Star has mastered the manufacturing method... I'll find an opportunity to contact him."

...

"Lost contact? Explain to me, what does it mean by lost contact‽"

The upper echelons of Arcane Church quickly received the news that Ninjia, who was supposed to pass through the stargate a while ago, had lost contact with them!

This gave the Bishops a big scare. They had thought that Ninjia had gotten away from danger and could successfully bring the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter back. To think that an accident had occurred.

Since they could not contact Ninjia, the worst possibility was that he had been ambushed and killed.

But even if he was attacked, he should have been able to send news back, or the Arcane Church should have discovered some abnormalities.

There was only one explanation for this... The attacking party had a Virtual Mechanic who was able to tamper with the data and prevent any communication.

The first suspect that the Arcane Church thought of was Black Star.

However, Han Xiao had been at the Star Pupil Holy Race not too long ago and was still en route to his headquarters. There was an alibi... but they did not forget that Han Xiao could command troops from a distance to complete the attack.

"If Black Star is the murderer, is he being supported by the dynasty? They have already captured four of our people and forced Psyker to apologize. Is this not enough?" someone wondered out loud.

"The possibility is not high. Both sides are in negotiations, and we have reached a preliminary conclusion. The dynasty knows that it is not beneficial to continue chasing and fighting them. If they take away our Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, it will force us to flip the table. I'm afraid it is not worth it for them."

"Could it be that Black Star wants the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter and decided to move on his own?"

"But... if we think about it closely, this will give Black Star more problems than benefits. He has already obtained a huge benefit from this matter, and there is no need for him to also steal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. He will not be able to use it either, and just having it with him will cause numerous problems. The only way would be to give it to the dynasty. However, what we've checked about Black Star shows that he is not someone who enjoys taking risks, and he is still in his honeymoon period with the Dynasty. He would not do such a thing behind the back of the dynasty."

The Bishops frowned. Everything pointed to the fact that Black Star was not involved.

Could it be that there were people who wanted to fish in muddy waters?

To be able to attack Ninjia, one had to fulfil two criteria. One was a strong enough intelligence network to be able to track Ninjia, and the second was to possess the ability of a Beyond Grade A Mechanic to be able to silently kill him off.

Thinking about this, a plausible answer floated up.

The Bishops present all lurched.

"Could it be... the Federation of Light‽"

The Shattered Star Ring was still their territory, and while it looked like they did not care, it would be careless for them to ignore their intelligence system. After operating for so many years, their network would naturally be seamless, and their intelligence gathering would trump the dynasty's, who were newcomers in the region.

While the Crimson Dynasty did not spot Ninjia's traces, the Federation of Light did. This explained everything.

The faces of the Bishops were green. The more they thought about it, the more it felt as though the Federation of Light was the culprit.

From the start, when they loaned out the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, that bunch of robbers had intended to fish in muddy waters.

This time, not only did the Arcane Church lose a lot of their Beyond Grade A combat power, they had also strained their relationship with the Crimson Dynasty. To the Federation of Light, this was their best chance.

The Bishops realized that this meant that their entire expedition had been captured and annihilated, and they almost spat blood.

Federation of Light, f*ck your mom!

At this time, the virtual screen on the conference table appeared, showing the command of the pope.

"Stabilize the situation with the Crimson Dynasty and redeem our allies... We'll settle the scores with the Federation of Light at a later point."

The Bishops exchanged glances, and within each gaze, they could see depression and helplessness.

Yesterday, they thought that at least the scepter was returning. Today, they once again received bad news. This feeling of falling from heaven to hell made them extremely uncomfortable.

It was a total loss.

Without evidence, the Federation of Light would never admit it. After all, both sides were of the same strength, so they would not be threatened.

They could only take things one step at a time.

...

On the mother planet of the Federation of Light, President Bader put down the communicator, smiling at the elders present.

"Manison has achieved the objective. The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is ours."

At his words, everyone revealed smiles of success.

The Chief Elder fiddled with his cane, praising, "Indeed worthy of being one of the strongest Ancient Ones. The Mechanic Empire is still as reliable as ever."

Bader nodded with a smile. Manison was an ally whom he deeply valued, not because of his frightening power but because of their ability to appear at long distances and wipe out all evidence, perfectly completing secret operations.

"The Arcane Church will suspect the Crimson Dynasty and may even suspect us, but they have no evidence. Besides, they will not tell the world about theft of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter."

"According to our intelligence, the usage of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is simple. It's just that we do not have the necessary skills to repair it. However, we can use it as a trump card with limited uses, as it can greatly damage a Beyond Grade A... Cough cough, just don't use it in front of Black Star."

"While it may infuriate the Arcane Church, we've earned big by obtaining the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. This is also a chip to deal with the Arcane Church in the future."

Many of the elders revealed smiles as they discussed their success.

"Manison said that the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter is sealed by the special material. When he returns, I'll have the research team crack it."

Bader's tone was confident; he did not doubt that the seal could be removed at all.

Chapter 871: Business Snatching Mid-Version

The little secret between the Arcane Church and Federation of Light was not made known to Han Xiao.

After leaving the star system of the Star Pupil Holy Race, Han Xiao's fleet did not stop, returning to the headquarters of the Black Star Army.

In the previous gathering that the Tyrant hosted, Han Xiao had signed a few agreements with a large number of civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring and had also publicly sold access to the Evolution Cube in exchange for cooperation with the major civilizations.

This year was the first year of cooperation, and because Han Xiao would remain in the Shattered Star Ring for this period, he prepared to handle the slots purchased by the various civilizations this year and complete them.

In the past years, the civilizations had conducted numerous internal selections, confirming the list of elites who would undergo evolution, and had been waiting for this day. Upon receiving the notice, the teams were dispatched, and many elites from each civilization gathered at the Black Star Army headquarters.

Using the Evolution Cube as a bridge to reach better relationships with multiple star cluster and star system level civilizations was a key step in the expansion plan for the Black Star Army.

In Han Xiao's blueprint, maintaining this sort of cooperation network for a long period would form a large network using the Black Star Army as a transit point. By that time, the power and influence of the Black Star Army would truly cover the entire star field, so Han Xiao paid a lot of attention to the cooperation in the first year.

Furthermore, there was an additional benefit. The people picked by the civilizations would all be elites, and there would definitely be well-known characters or protagonists within.

Letting them take the initiative to gather was better than him looking for all of them himself.

This is probably the alternate reality version of keeping the talents in the world for my own usage... Han Xiao mused to himself.

Spaceships of different styles landed at the Black Star Army headquarters, and elites of all races poured out as the hatches opened. They were led to the accommodation area under the guidance of the reception robots, causing the dock to be extremely lively.

These elites were all leaders back in their respective civilizations, and the majority were either Calamity Grades, military officers, potential Calamity Grades, or scientific researchers. All of them sized up the other elites as they disembarked, their expressions wary.

"This is the Black Star Army talked of in legends."

Pamela opened her three large, watery eyes as she curiously took in her surroundings. She hailed from a star system level plant-based civilization, with her race called the Flower Sprite Tribe. Her body was covered with a layer of green leaf-like epidermal tissue, and she exuded a strange fragrance. It was said that every individual had a unique fragrance, just like how humans were differentiated by fingerprints. Body fragrance, appearance, and physique were the aesthetic standards for this race.

According to their aesthetics, Pamela would be a rare beauty, and at the same time, she was an elite researcher who was chosen to undergo evolution.

As Pamela and her party observed the dock, a small hovering robot flew in front of them, speaking in Phillip's voice.

"Welcome, everyone, to the Black Star Army, hum... Our Commander is still en route. I'll be responsible for escorting you and arranging your accommodation. In the meantime, if you have any needs, please contact me directly, hum..."

The leader of the Flower Sprite Tribe was a Calamity Grade, and he calmly nodded. "Understood."

"Please follow me."

The reception robot flew through the huge crowd, leading the way.

The group followed close behind, looking around on the way and discussing in a low voice.

"People of all civilizations have come. I even saw a few Star Cluster level Civilizations."

"All of them are elites of their races. This is a grand event. Let's go pay a visit to some others. After all, it's a rare chance to socialize."

Hearing the discussions coming from behind, the reception robot turned around and addressed them. "During this waiting period, I'll take you to visit the headquarters, hold banquets, and provide a platform for everyone to communicate with each other, so please don't worry about not having a chance."

"This looks a little like the Tyrant's Party... but the people here are not representatives of a few civilizations but rather a large number of elites..." The eyes of the Calamity Grade leading the team moved around, and they seemed to understand something.

Pamela hesitated before asking, "So, so... will we have a chance to converse with His Excellency Black Star?"

"There will be a banquet for everyone to celebrate after the evolution process is completed. If you're willing to stay, then you'll be able to converse with our Army Commander," the robot replied.

"That's... that's great." Pamela's skin color turned green, which was the same as humans blushing. She looked expectant.

"Yo, shy because you're about to see your idol?" One of her colleagues teased.

Pamela did not reply, her face so green that it was turning indigo.

Every Beyond Grade A would have a few fans in the universe, even those infamous thugs such as EsGod.

The deeds of Black Star were widely circulated in the universe. As a native of a planetary civilization, he had established the Black Star Army from scratch and rewritten the fate of his homeland by himself. Such a legendary existence had attracted a large number of admirers within the Shattered Star Ring, and Pamela was one of those who were impressed with his deeds.

"I don't know what sort of spouse Black Star likes..." Pamela appeared a bit dazed.

"Hello, are you being serious? Do you not know about reproductive isolation?" Her colleague was surprised.

"I'm a biological genetic engineer. Do I need your reminder?" Pamela snapped back in resignation.

The Calamity Grade leader frowned and turned back to say, "Don't forget our purpose here, and don't provoke His Excellency."

"Can't I have expectations?" Pamela grumpily replied.

She did not know, however, that the reception robot was recording every word they spoke and passing it on to Sylvia.

In her office, Sylvia received the report, and after sweeping over it, she coldly snorted.

"Number 237..."

After which, she put a mark on the file before throwing it into a folder labelled 'Banquet Seating Arrangement (Corner List)'.

Way before the date that Han Xiao set, all the civilizations that were supposed to undergo evolution had arrived. Except for Klent, the other Shattered Star Ring civilizations were there. Not only were civilizations belonging to the Shattered Star Ring there—even a new batch of elites from the Crimson Dynasty had arrived.

While waiting, these organizations did not just idle but took this rare chance to network and exchange contacts. The atmosphere quickly became friendly.

All the elites present could see that Han Xiao was taking advantage of the situation to gather all the influential people in Shattered Star Ring and start his own banquet. In other words, he was trying to snatch the Tyrant Heber's businesses, using the Evolution Cube as a cover to form his own 'party', in order to expand his influence!

Although everyone understood this, no one had any issues with it. They were also willing to communicate with other races for their needs.

As for Black Star and the Tyrant's competition, no one dared breathe a word. Both sides were not good to provoke, and it was better to just go with the flow.

A few days passed, and Han Xiao finally arrived back at the headquarters. After resting for a few hours, he informed everyone to gather to proceed with the ceremony.

Following batch after batch of people, the clean and gleaming main hall quickly became packed. Reynold received the news and took the mechanics of the logistics department to widen the hall on the spot so that it would not be overcrowded.

The space fluctuated slightly, and Han Xiao stepped out of the void dimension, suspending himself above everyone's head. The Evolution Cube slowly rotated around him.

Everyone looked up at the floating Han Xiao, and there was a small commotion as everyone broke out in whispers.

"Black Star is here."

"This is the first time I've seen a Beyond Grade A from up close. The energy contained within his body is just terrifying. I started sweating when I felt it."

"The thing beside him is probably the Evolution Cube. Not too long ago, I heard that Psyker relinquished his control over this Universal Treasure... Such a small thing was actually the source of so much trouble, and even a few Beyond Grade As from the Arcane Church were captured."

"Black Star does have the ability to keep this Universal Treasure. A year ago, I thought that his Evolution Cube would be snatched away quickly, but it turns out that I was wrong."

The elites of the various races all had awe in their eyes. No matter how proud they were normally, in front of Han Xiao, they did not have the ability to be confident.

Before Han Xiao rose up, other than the Purple Crystal Civilization, the other Star Cluster civilizations had tried to suppress Han Xiao, but at the Tyrant's Party, all of them could not help but lower their heads to seek cooperation.

Just because Han Xiao had recently reached Beyond Grade A, everyone had entertained a brief thought of suppressing him.

However, the recent matters had proven Black Star's ability, consolidating his position in the universe. This dispelled the last bit of hostility the star cluster civilizations had. They completely gave up on their fantasy. Now that Black Star had completely taken off, playing small tricks were useless.

Looking at the gazes below of respect and admiration, Han Xiao secretly nodded to himself.

The recent storm had brought him benefits in that he was able to successfully launch this program to create a consortium of interests. This had saved him a lot of time.

On his way back, Han Xiao had briefly scanned through the name list of the elites as well. Not out of his expectations, there were a few well-known personalities of various civilizations from his previous life.

However, this was not the time to come into contact. After completing their evolution, Han Xiao then intended to befriend these 'old acquaintances' during the specially organized banquet.

Most likely, these people all had some kind of storyline. While he might not need them, the players needed them...

In short, these elites were walking bags of fertilizer.

Various thoughts flashed by as Han Xiao surveyed the scene. He smiled before speaking in an interested voice.

"Before we begin, there's something I need to do... Heber, there's no need to hide. I know you're in there."

The moment this sentence was spoken, everybody jumped. They stared left and right but did not discover him.

The Tyrant's here too?

Everyone fidgeted, but no one stepped forward. Seeing this, Han Xiao's brows furrowed. "Stop lying to yourself. I've already discovered you. Since you won't come out, do you want me to drag you out? You will only lose face."

The commotion got louder, but still, no one stepped up.

Han Xiao looked over everyone with narrowed eyes before suddenly bursting into laughter. "Hehe, it seems like Heber really didn't sneak in. Then we can begin."

Hearing this, everyone's expression stiffened.

"He was actually joking..." Countless people's mouths twitched.

Is it really good to ridicule the Tyrant like this, even guarding against him coming over? That guy is after all a Beyond Grade A! He wouldn't do something so low class... right?

Perhaps Black Star and Tyrant have a good relationship now, so they can ridicule each other...

Everyone could only think this way.

Han Xiao then activated the Evolution Cube, and with a thought, the black evolutionary energy spewed out, enveloping the entire room. The elites present all turned into black cocoons.

"It's done." Han Xiao clapped his hands and instructed Phillip, "Monitor their evolutions. Remember to invite them to stay for the banquet later."

"Roger, hum..."

Han Xiao did not wish to wait there for nothing. He stored the Evolution Cube and left the hall full of black cocoons, returning to his room.

He was going to change his clothes. He awaited the banquet that was to come next.

On the way, Han Xiao casually read through the forums.

Now that the matters of the Arcane Church had drawn to a close, the long-term gains from this event would gradually manifest over time, such as Urranrell's appreciation of him and his importance to the dynasty.

The situation was already settled. What happened next would be between the Crimson Dynasty and Arcane Church, which was not his concern.

In the short term, no trouble would come looking for him, so Han Xiao had the capacity to focus on the players.

From the perspective of the players, Version 3.0 had been going for about a year and a half, which was the mid-version phase.

In this year and a half, the players had experienced the secret war, the Crimson Tide, the rise of Black Star, the Flickering World, and the Battle of Planet Lighthouse, which were all major events. More and more players at the level cap of 120 had appeared, and more and more players would continue to reach this goal as time passed.

During the mid-version phase, the new Pro League would be released. There was still some time before the opening, so players had time to upgrade, learn new skills, and change equipment. However, on the forums, the league officials had already begun the preparations, advertising widely and attracting the players' attention.

From his memory, Version 3.0 was particularly spectacular.

Players would possess the strength of Grade Bs in this version, and the Mechanic profession would also slowly start to rise. A large number of newcomers would emerge, including Maple Moon, as professional players, causing a new injection into the pro scene.

The ratio of Mechanics in the Shattered Star Ring was the highest among all the other star fields, and the Black Star Army also sold the highest number of machines as well as blueprints. With the bonuses offered throughout the version, Han Xiao believed that the Shattered Star Ring's Mechanics would bring great glory in the Pro League this time.

To him, the best benefit would be that it would attract more people to take the Mechanic profession or allow the older players to create Mechanic smurfs.

If that was the case, he would generate more income as the 'mentor' of the Mechanic profession.

"What a pity. With three versions out, the good days are almost over." Han Xiao shook his head with some emotion.

Based on his experience from his previous life, Version 3.0 was a watershed. It symbolized that players had formally entered the mid-stage of the universe, and it was where their influence truly began to manifest and expand.

The nicknames 'Cancer of the Universe' as well as 'The Fourth Calamity' were tagged toward the players after Version 3.0!

It was also the source of Han Xiao's psychological shadow.

For now, the players were in a period of imminent transformation. After this version, the players' strength would exceed a certain point, and the more things they could do, the more they would be inclined to cause chaos. This was inevitable!

Version 3.0 was the last stage where players could be easily controlled.

Thus, Han Xiao placed his bets on the Flickering World. He might be able to use it to gain some advantage during the faction wars in the next version.

Just as Han Xiao was about to proceed with the banquet, on the other side of the star cluster, Heber also received some news.

As a competitor, he was always paying attention to the moves of the Black Star Army.

Heber thus discovered Han Xiao's sinister intentions.

"Relying on the Evolution Cube, Black Star is building a platform for the elites to converse. He's trying to take away the influence of the Tyrant's Party and gain even greater influence in the Shattered Star Ring..."

As he read the intelligence, Heber grew visibly annoyed.

The Tyrant's Party was the byproduct of his many years of effort. Now that Han Xiao had come out to compete with him, he was furious yet unable to stop it.

Furthermore, upon realizing that Han Xiao had mocked him in front of all the various civilization elites, Heber's mind finally blew.

Dammit, why!

Are we even on good terms?

To ridicule me like that in public, smearing my brave warrior image, this is pure evil!

You're taking advantage of me!

One of these days, I'm going to make sure you can't even defend yourself!

Chapter 872: Banquet and Request

The duration of everyone's evolution process differed. As the cocoons slowly broke one after another, people groggily woke up, sensing the changes within themselves.

The Evolution Cube raised one's life level, and the normal people were unlike players in that they could not get used to their new changes immediately. Their way to improvement was through long hours of extended practice, where many streams flowed to form a river. It was usually only when they broke through to a new realm that such a drastic change occurred.

Thus, most of the people present were satisfied with the effect of the Evolution Cube, especially the Calamity Grade Supers. The stronger their body, the better the effect of using the Evolution Cube.

"What a novel experience." Pamela curiously observed the changes in her body. As a biological genetic engineer, she could feel the process more acutely, and her professionalism surfaced. "This is a pure evolution at the genetic level, not environmentally induced mutation but rather optimization. One's original racial characteristics amplify the advantages of the genes, and their strengths are strengthened. If there are no sequelae, it is practically perfect.

"The source of this power is unknown. It's like a divine blessing... The cells seemed to have received some sort of radiation. Is the essence of evolutionary energy a special kind of radiation?"

While she was muttering, the reception robot came up to her and said, "Congratulations. In order to celebrate your evolution, the Black Star Army will be holding a banquet tomorrow. The Army Commander and the officers will attend, and you're welcome to participate, hum..."

Every race that had completed their evolution would receive an invite from the reception robots. The Flower Sprite Tribe leader suppressed his excitement and nodded. "We will be there."

"The invite has been sent. On it is the time and place. I'll remind you again closer to the time. Also, please remember to dress formally."

"Understood." Everyone else nodded in agreement.

The purpose of their trip was completed, and everyone in the room was in a good mood. Practically all the elites accepted the invitation, opting to stay and attend the banquet.

It was to be held the next day, so everyone proceeded back to their accommodation.

After resting for a day, the elites took off their battle suits and armor, donning the formal attire of their respective civilizations, and proceeded to the banquet venue.

In the commander's room, Han Xiao also donned a suit, looking at himself in the mirror.

The man in the mirror was tall and well-built, wearing a compressed orb necklace and a thick black cloak with white borders on his shoulders. The emblem of the Black Star Army was embroidered on his back, lined with the dark-red fur of a rare beast. The neckline of the cloak had three silver magnetic clasps that could be joined to wrap around the body. It matched with the black top and pants provided.

Han Xiao could not help but comment, "I would like to know who designed this suit. Is the person treating me like a crow?"

"I designed it based on your usual attire, hum..."

"It seems like I will need to modify the data collection algorithm," Han Xiao muttered to himself.

After washing his face, Han Xiao opened his door to find all his officers outside in their formal attire waiting for him.

Sweeping his eyes over them, he looked at everyone's designs.

Han Xiao interestedly sized up everyone. "All of you look pretty good."

"It's been a while since I wore my robes. It's a little awkward." Feidin adjusted his neckline, looking a little helpless.

Because Han Xiao normally did not host such events, few of them had seen each other in formal attire.

Hila frowned. "You know I have no interest in these activities. If I have time to attend a banquet, I'd rather be training."

"Just training itself wouldn't help. You need to rest and relax at times." Han Xiao waved his hands. "Recently, because of the problem with the Arcane Church, my nerves have been stretched out, and now that this problem has finally been solved, I can relax for today. Don't think about training anymore."

"I don't like conversing with strangers." Hila shook her head.

"Uh... these people are all the elites of their civilizations. They're probably formidable characters, and if you get to know them, you could organize a spar."

"That sounds good." Hila's eyes flickered.

Han Xiao chatted with his entourage while he walked, all the way until they arrived at the banquet. There were already a lot of people within, and it was boisterous.

The banquet hall was a special hall designed for this purpose, and its decorations were opulent. Tables were filled with full, and innumerable delicacies were delivered like flowing water. The foods were complex and catered toward the tastes of different races.

The elites of all races were present, and various styles and designs of clothing were on full display, dazzling the eyes. It fully demonstrated the diversity of the interstellar society.

Han Xiao led his people to the front, where he attracted all gazes.

"Ahem, on behalf of the Black Star Army, welcome to the evening banquet..."

Clearing his throat, Han Xiao smiled as he spoke. As the host, he had to give some pleasantries before the banquet could formally begin.

After giving a brief speech, the atmosphere at the banquet grew much warmer. Many people took the initiative to approach Han Xiao and chat with him enthusiastically.

The majority of people had stayed behind in order to converse with Han Xiao. It was not every day that one had the means to come into contact with a Beyond Grade A.

Very quickly, a crowd was surrounding Han Xiao. With a smile on his face, and seemingly not bored of the small talk, he continued to access everyone present.

In just this short period, he had seen many of the 'acquaintances' he knew in his past life. All of these people were famed personalities that the players from Shattered Star Ring had met in various regions while adventuring.

Some of them were very cheerful and sociable, while some wore hooded cloaks as though they were trying to hide themselves. One of them was even mumbling to himself, as though he was neurotic.

While, in front of Han Xiao, these characters' fame was not worth mentioning, in front of the players, they were all big-shot characters.

As for all the elites that came to talk, Han Xiao collected all their contact details. This gave them a pleasant surprise because they did not expect a Beyond Grade A to be so easy to approach.

Collecting their contact information was akin to collecting their potential storyline missions for Han Xiao. In addition, these elites all had considerable power in the respective civilizations, which could be regarded as networking.

While conversing, Han Xiao heard someone calling him from behind in a shy tone.

"Your... Your Excellency Black Star, I'm Pamela from the Flower Sprite Tribe, a biological genetic engineer."

Han Xiao turned back and smiled. "Is there anything you need?"

"I... I'm one of your admirers. I would like to know you. Could you accept my communicator number?" Pamela looked excited. She had watched him from the side for a while and realized that Han Xiao did not reject such requests. Thus, she had gathered up her courage to talk to him and exchange contact information.

Feeling her impure gaze on him, Han Xiao laughed dumbly.

Am I being picked up now?

What a rare occasion.

"Ok. Send it to me." Han Xiao did not reject her. A biological genetic engineer was worth him befriending.

Although it was impossible for these elites to jump ship, he could still recruit them if he ran into some special situations in the future or request their aid.

"Thank you!" After exchanging contact details, Pamela behaved as though she had just obtained his autograph, her face full of joy as she hugged her communicator close to her chest.

Not far away, Sylvia saw this entire scene and lightly snorted. "Humph, airhead."

As the banquet progressed, the guests became more absorbed in the atmosphere and relaxed more.

Batch after batch of guests exchanged their contact information with Han Xiao before being content enough to retreat. Han Xiao finally managed to get a breather and sighed in relief as he grabbed one of the alcoholic beverages from a floating tray. He drained half the cocktail, which held a blue gradient, to moisten his throat.

The cooling yet spicy alcohol flowed into his throat, and there was an aftertaste of sweetness. Han Xiao felt rejuvenated and smiled.

Walking to a corner, he slowly drank whilst surveying the scene.

After working for so many years, the Black Star Army had finally reached its current scale, which gave Han Xiao mixed feelings.

"What are you reminiscing about?" Hila carried a deep red cocktail as she walked over.

"How did you know?" Han Xiao raised a brow.

"I've known you for so long. How could I not understand? Seeing your eyes, I know that you're recalling something," Hila blandly replied.

"Speaking of, I just recalled something. Twenty years ago, back on Planet Aquamarine, when I just... cough, just lost my memories, you were the first friend I met, and the earliest."

"That's right. In the blink of an eye, it's been so many years." Hila followed Han Xiao's gaze and looked around the entire venue. "Those years, I struggled in despair and never thought that I would step into the universe one day and have such a future. Now, looking back, it seems like those days on Planet Aquamarine belonged to a past life."

"Thinking back, I endured for a good half a year in the Germinal Organization base. It was lucky that you left the base once in a while, or else I would never have escaped."

"It's good that you know this." The corners of Hila's mouth curled up.

Han Xiao laughed as he reminisced, but suddenly, his laughter stopped, and he shook his head. "There are so many things that happened after. You felt that you owed me, so you always chose to fight for me. However, your ability is not only at this level, and you have the potential to reach Beyond Grade A. One day, you will obtain this power, and at that time, will you still fight shoulder to shoulder with me?"

Hila hesitated for a while before shaking her head. "I don't know."

"An honest answer. Promises are the most unreliable thing. Who can predict the future properly?" Han Xiao shrugged and raised his glass. "At least, you're still by my side now. To our friendship, cheers."

"You sound so old fashioned."

"Please, we're already in our forties... although if we look from the perspective of our life spans, we're just little brats."

"You're the little brat."

Hila's expression was disdainful, but a smile still hung on her lips as she raised her glass to clink Han Xiao's.

"Cheers."

They both took a sip of their drinks.

Han Xiao wiped his mouth. He was about to say something else, but a guest suddenly walked over, as though he wished to talk, yet there was a hesitant look.

Seeing someone approached, they both stopped talking, and Han Xiao took the initiative to ask, "Is there something?"

"Your Excellency Black Star, I'm Ceselin from the Gulal Civilization. I have a matter that I would like to discuss privately."

Gulal Civilization? Han Xiao quickly searched on his quantum network.

This was a Star Cluster Civilization that seemed to have been embroiled in civil strife for a long time. Their internal issues were serious and had evolved to the point of military division.

This Ceselin was a Calamity Grade elite belonging to the current ruling party of the civilization. Not only was he one of the strongest guardians but also an army commander with high power.

"What do you want to talk in private for?" Han Xiao raised his brow. "Can't we talk here?"

Ceselin shook his head. "It's not suitable in a public venue."

"You must at least tell me your intentions."

Ceselin paused for a moment before solemnly saying, "This is a request. Please believe me. I come with sincerity."

Han Xiao stroked his chin, smelling the possibility of a mission.

To have a mission bring itself to me, it's quite worthwhile to listen to it...

As he thought of this, Han Xiao passed his glass to Hila before turning to walk toward a side entrance. There were private conference rooms located along the corridor there.

"Follow me."

Chapter 873: S Grade War Hire

Both of them left through the side entrance, walking along the hallway to a conference room. Phillip locked the door as they entered. The soundproofing system here was good, completely isolating the noises from the banquet.

They sat down facing each other, and Han Xiao snapped his fingers. The simulated mechanical waiter stepped forward to pour two glasses of amber mead for them, adding a few cubes of ice before placing the glasses on the table in front of them.

"We can speak now." Han Xiao swirled his glass, and the fragrance of the liquor wafted out from the mouth of the glass.

Now that he was a great character within the Shattered Star Ring, no longer did he need to actively search for missions. People would naturally come knocking to request his aid.

This phenomenon was not only limited to himself. Players could also achieve this if they managed to carve out a name for themselves within a certain star system. NPCs would then also seek help from them from time to time.

"It's like this. My request is about the future of the Gulal Civilization..." Ceselin sat on the edge.

I guessed it. If it wasn't something of that magnitude, who would come and disturb a Beyond Grade A? Han Xiao's expression, however, remained unchanged, and he lifted his hand, gesturing for him to continue.

"Before this, please allow me to briefly explain the current situation of my civilization." Ceselin solemnly spoke. "The Gulal Civilization has always been in a state of military division, and the three main parties have formed their own military regions and are opposed to each other. They are the Ancient Emperor Party, the Pioneer Party, and the Descendant Party. The current ruling party representing the Gulal Civilization government is the Ancient Emperor Party, and my teammates and I are members of this party."

As one of the edges of the explored universe, the Shattered Star Ring had a complicated situation due to the lack of control. Some civilizations were stable and peaceful, whilst some faced external and internal problems. The situation of internal military division such as the Gulal Civilization would be considered quite serious.

"Okay, I understand. So, what is your request?" Han Xiao asked.

"I beg the Black Star Army to lend the war efforts and end the split of the Gulal Civilization, letting us find peace."

"I understand. You wish to apply for war employment and have my people assist the current ruling party to suppress the other two, right?" Han Xiao raised a brow.

However, Ceselin shook his head and gave an unexpected answer.

"No, I hope for Black Star Army to assist the Pioneer Party in overthrowing the Ancient Emperor Party and suppressing the Descendant Party."

This was getting more interesting. Han Xiao sized Ceselin up. "You're someone of the Ancient Emperor Party, yet you are helping the Pioneer Party to speak. Are you a spy?"

Ceselin shook his head. "That's not the case. I was born on a colonial planet of the Ancient Emperor Party and even joined their army. I've never joined another party."

"Then, why? For benefits? Did the Pioneer Party give you any advantages?"

"That's not true either. My position in the Ancient Emperor Party is high, and I'm even a War Hero. The Pioneer Party would not try to pull hardcore members like me over, and whatever they can give me, the Ancient Emperor Party can do so as well."

"Then why?"

"Ideals," Ceselin gravely replied. "I'm more inclined toward the ideology and beliefs of the Pioneer Party. The Ancient Emperor Party is decaying, and only the Pioneer Party will be able to lead the civilization to greater hope."

"I get it." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. "You're a traitor. The Ancient Emperor Party has given you both authority and standing, even allowing you to obtain the power of the Evolution Cube, yet you decide to stab them in the back and overthrow them?"

"From their viewpoint, I'm indeed a traitor, but from the viewpoint of the Pioneer Party, I'm someone who has thrown away the darkness and embraced the light. One's perception is based on their viewpoint, so I'm only looking at this objectively and not caring about one's judgement," Ceselin replied in a low voice. "Back when I was young, I was also passionate and wanted to serve the nation. However, my thoughts were not mature, and like many others, I was just keen to maintain the orthodox Ancient Emperor Party. Since I was born on the colonial planet, my position was largely determined from birth... but after so many years, I've become skeptical of their ideals and behavior, and my beliefs have become more and more shaken."

Han Xiao looked at him silently. Before Phillip presented him with the complete information on Gulal Civilization, he would not just take anyone's words at face value.

This time, Ceselin's tone became more animated, and it even hid some anger.

"Due to its position, the Ancient Emperor Party wanted a totalitarian rule and has done many bloody things under wraps to our people. I've participated in many of them and have seen the darkness of politics, the bloodshed of domination, and the confinement of thought. My house is filled with medals awarded by the party, and I used to like to look at the past glories. However, when I stare at them now, my nose fills with the sickening smell of blood."

Han Xiao stroked his chin. "So, you decided to betray the party that groomed you?"

"To be specific, it was only after I began to doubt myself that I finally freed myself from the shackles." Ceselin took a sip of his drink and sighed. "I've always been bound by my identity, and when I woke up, I realized that the three parties were only the standpoints of internal division of our civilization. The so-called opposition is meaningless, and what we should be concerned with is the future of our entire civilization. Whoever can bring prosperity should be supported. I chose to follow the idea of freedom and the judgement of my heart, so I chose the Pioneer Party, which the majority of citizens support. They will be able to bring Gulal Civilization further."

"So, in this way, you believe yourself to be noble?" Han Xiao raised his brow.

"I never thought of myself that way." Ceselin shook his head.

"... Regarding your choice, I cannot give any comment because I'm an outsider," Han Xiao slowly said. "I just want to know. You mentioned that you have never joined the other parties. So, on what basis can the Pioneer Party talk to me about cooperation?"

"I'm not representing the Pioneer Party. I'm just making a request to you personally."

Han Xiao laughed at this. "What makes you think you can persuade me to intervene in a civil strife that I do not care about? You haven't even reached a consensus with the Pioneer Party, and let's not talk about whether the other party wishes for me to intervene. Just how are you even going to afford the war employment wages? Why should I kick aside the Ancient Emperor Party that I'm working with now to help you? What can you bring me?"

"I know that it's very abrupt to bring this up as an individual, but I have no choice," Ceselin replied. "The Ancient Emperor Party has assigned me the mission of applying to you for war employment. They are ready to use force to eradicate the other two parties and take back all the divided land."

"So, it's like that." Han Xiao understood it.

The Ancient Emperor Party wanted to resolve the strife once and for all, but they did not wish to be controlled by an advanced civilization. Thus, instead of asking for help from the Star Cluster civilizations, they planned to hire foreign aid in the form of interstellar mercenaries. In the Shattered Star Ring, the most representative of the mercenaries were the Mercenary League, Bloodshed Land, and Black Star Army.

Since the Black Star Army was also the head of the Mercenary League and an ally of the dynasty together with Bloodshed Land, as long as the Black Star Army was hired, the mercenaries of Shattered Star Ring would not be employed by people wishing to oppose the Black Star Army. After all, with the current might of the army, no one wished to send themselves to die, and mercenaries that are cooperating with each other would not send their people to opposing sides.

In the mercenary world within the Shattered Star Ring, the Black Star Army had already reached the highest level of influence and reputation.

As the ruling party, the Ancient Emperor Party had already attached themselves to the Black Star Army. As long as aid was received, the Pioneer Party that Ceselin looked upon fondly would be destroyed, so he could only brave this risk and boldly make this request of Han Xiao.

Man, of all the people you chose to be the emissary, you chose an emissary that is a backstabber... Han Xiao's mouth twitched. Could this be the legendary plot of 'I didn't choose this, but now I wish to be on the good side?'

Han Xiao shook his head. "Let's be practical. Which party is in power has no impact on me. Since the Ancient Emperor Party is cooperating with the Black Star Army, they will definitely offer a good price. And since you came here in a rush to find me, that means nothing is set in stone on your side... Forget it. I don't wish to say any more unpleasant words. Let's consider this conversation over."

Han Xiao put down his glass and stood up, walking toward the door with a dissatisfied mood.

While the words from Ceselin were nice to hear, it was true that he could not bring out any substantial remuneration. Han Xiao did not care about the struggle of a party in an unfamiliar civilization. The Black Star Army had retained its mercenary business after the transformation and did not change into a charity overnight.

Violation of professional standards was a behavior without any professional ethics. Without practical benefits, he wished to use only his mouth to influence a Beyond Grade A?

If he had such a fantasy, he should just die in that fantasy!

"Please wait." Ceselin immediately stood up. "Just as you mentioned, whichever party it is has no influence toward you. The Pioneer Party can also maintain a cooperative relationship with you. I hope that you will help the Pioneer Party. The Gulal Civilization can also become stronger, which will be more rewarding for you. The Ancient Emperor Party has decayed, and the Pioneer Party is the only righteous one now."

"What does your righteousness have to do with me?" Han Xiao did not bother turning back. Waving this so-called banner of justice was useless in front of others.

His kindness only existed to people he knew. Toward strangers, this was greatly limited. His coldness was created with the times, and with all the matters experienced, he would not easily allow people to sway him.

"Please help the Gulal Civilization!"

Dong!

A weird sound was heard, and when Han Xiao turned back, he saw Ceselin prostrating on the ground. A Calamity Grade actually begged him for help.

However, glancing at him, Han Xiao remained indifferent and prepared to push open the door.

At this moment, a mission notification appeared on his interface.

You have triggered an S-ranked Mission (Gulal Civilization: The Flames of Pioneer!).

Mission Introduction: The Gulal Civilization is a galactic civilization that has been plagued with internal strife. The civilization has not progressed for many years and has even deteriorated. In order to break this deadlock, Ceselin, who is an upper echelon of the Ancient Emperor Party, has decided to support the Pioneer Party and has made a request to you.

Mission Requirements: Overthrow the rule of the Ancient Emperor Party, eradicate the Descendant Party, and support the Pioneer Party to become the new rulers of the Gulal Civilization

Failure Condition: The destruction of the Pioneer Party

Reward: After completion of the task, the reward will be determined by the Mission Rating.

S-ranked mission? Han Xiao's footsteps paused. A coup d'état of a galactic civilization was as good as engaging in total war. It was indeed deserving of its S-rank difficulty, as players would find it difficult to control the direction of an internal war.

Of course, it was different for him. The influence of the Black Star Army was huge, so he was naturally qualified to intervene in this war. This mission was not difficult for him.

But while thinking about it, Han Xiao did not stop there and walked out of the room, leaving Ceselin in the room looking lost.

The S-ranked mission was indeed attractive, but it was unreasonable to aid the Pioneer Party just because of the mission. It was unreasonable to assume that the Ancient Emperor Party would not have a mission, as Han Xiao immediately saw with his experience that this would be a series of missions.

Han Xiao was prepared to speak with all the upper echelons of the Gulal Civilization and activate the missions of each party before deciding.

He was never the kind that had an obsessive compulsion to complete every mission that he saw.

An S-ranked mission's war employment was no trivial matter. While the Black Star Army had a certain level of strength, it did not mean that they could just ignore the resources of a galactic civilization.

Han Xiao was clear that although their status was high, it was mainly because of him. After all, the development time of the army was limited, and its military force, while able to participate in a star system level war, was still far from being able to control a star cluster level war.

Han Xiao did not really require the mission reward and did not care for the remuneration of a star system civilization. Toward this, his main concern was the players.

Such a war employment task naturally was not his to interfere—a Beyond Grade A joining a star system level war was being too much of a bully and was also incongruent to his name and reputation. Furthermore, he planned to quietly stay at the headquarters and construct more machinery while biding his time for the experience penalty to pass. Thus, this mission would definitely be given to the players.

Players were the most suited for such missions since they would reduce the casualties of his mercenaries.

Since the battle in Planet Lighthouse had just ended, there would not be any big events for a period of time. The players could only do side missions, and while the Flickering World had its benefits, it was too boring for the players. Thus, he planned to create an event for the players to fill up their spare time, catering to the players in the army.

In addition, this would give the players more rewards before the Pro League, as the rewards from an S-ranked mission would be richer than the norm.

By helping the players grow faster, it would attract more people to his faction. Han Xiao had always done it this way.

At this moment, Phillip started bubbling in the quantum network.

"Master, hum... I've found the information on the Ancient Emperor Party you requested."

Han Xiao's consciousness entered the quantum network to read the intelligence.

In this regard, Ceselin did not lie. The Ancient Emperor Party was indeed unpopular, and its government was rotten. The people were suppressed by them and did not dare speak.

The Descendant Party was also not any better; in fact, they were worse. However, the Pioneer Party was not as good as Ceselin made out. Still, compared to the other two, it was the most acceptable.

After reading, Han Xiao nodded to himself.

Now that he had seen the truth, with actual information, he had an idea in his heart.

Chapter 874: Isolation

Han Xiao did not contact the Gulal Civilization immediately. The banquet was still ongoing, and it would be rude to ignore the guests.

Returning to the banquet, Han Xiao collected more communication numbers. The relaxing time passed in a flash, and the banquet quickly approached the end. The guests all bade their farewells and left the venue.

Han Xiao saw Ceselin among the throng of people leaving, his footsteps hurried but nothing strange from his expression. His display toward Han Xiao this time had brought nothing but ruin.

However, Han Xiao did not intend to snitch someone to such a small star system civilization. He was a Beyond Grade A and had no obligation to report to such people.

As the guests left, the mechanical waiters appeared to clear up the messy venue.

This was the first year of holding the evolutionary banquet, and both the scale and influence were limited. It would need a few more years before its reputation would sound in the Shattered Star Ring and become a practice.

After leaving the venue, Han Xiao did not idle but met up with the elites of the Crimson Dynasty separately. These people were more important, so they received special treatment. They did not talk about business but rather just chatted idly to improve their relationship.

All these people in the Crimson Dynasty had varying levels of influence, and making more contacts would allow him to help expand his network in the dynasty, as well as his speaking rights.

Because of the battle at Planet Lighthouse, Han Xiao's fame and status in the Crimson Dynasty had increased, and he found that the elites' attitude was now even more awed than the previous batch; they no longer treated him as a normal Beyond Grade A ally.

Everyone had a great chat, and only after Han Xiao sent them off did he return to his room and got Phillip to contact the upper echelons of the Gulal Civilization.

He did not disclose Ceselin's backstabbing but indicated that Ceselin had offered him war employment and completed his mission, leading him to call to discuss this matter.

The Ancient Emperor Party did not suspect anything and offered a price for his war employment efforts, including remuneration, military supplies, machinery materials, and long-term mining rights for their resource rich planets.

Normal mercenary groups would only obtain remuneration, military factory borrowing rights, procurement channels, and other rewards, but due to the nature of the Black Star Army being vastly different, they were able to obtain resources such as mining rights.

Unsurprisingly, the Gulal Civilization civil strife turned out to be a mission series. After he contacted the Ancient Emperor Party, a similar S-ranked mission appeared, the only difference being the name of the mission titled 'Protect the Orthodoxy'. The mission objective was to aid the Ancient Emperor Party in suppressing the other two parties and reclaim their territories.

Without giving the Ancient Emperor Party confirmation, Han Xiao cut the call, stroking his chin as he contemplated.

"Both are S-ranked missions, so the reward should be the same... Oh, there should be some minute differences. Because the Ancient Emperor Party is the strongest, suppressing the other two will be the easier option. If I help a weaker party ascend, the reward should also be higher."

After thinking about it, Han Xiao had Phillip search for the leader of the Pioneer Party's number. Ceselin was just an unexpected factor, and Han Xiao was prepared to just leapfrog ranks and talk straight to the leader.

With the military division within the Gulal Civilization, the Pioneer Party had a clear territory, so it was easy to find the required number.

The call was quickly connected.

"Hello, may I know who you..." The leader's secretary appeared on the screen, but in mid speech, the person exclaimed upon seeing Han Xiao's face. "Black Star‽"

With Han Xiao's current fame, only bumpkins would not recognize him. As someone who was an official of a star system civilization, they would not fail to recognize this face.

"Connect me to your leader." Han Xiao calmly spoke.

"Oh oh, I'll divert the call now, you... no, sir, please hold on," the secretary stammered. While they were not the ruling party, the leader of the Pioneer Party was not someone that any Tom, Dick, and Harry could meet as and when they liked. However, Black Star was obviously an exception.

Not long later, the leader came online. He found it difficult to hide the surprise in his eyes. He was waiting for an important call, but he suddenly received news that Black Star was on the line, which gave him quite the shock.

How come Black Star, who had never had any dealings with them, suddenly called and asked to speak with him?

"Your Excellency Black Star, may I ask... what business do you have with me?"

"I've heard about the situation in your Gulal Civilization, and not too long ago, the Ancient Emperor Party requested me for a war employment, wishing to borrow my strength to annihilate the other two parties. Are you aware of this?"

"Is this true‽" The leader's expression changed. While he did not know this, he had been waiting for a report from his spy, who had reported some movements from the side of the Ancient Emperor Party. He had guessed that they would seek aid, but this report was now directly confirmed by Black Star.

The Pioneer Party leader also knew the importance of such a matter and immediately panicked. He quickly recovered though. If Black Star had accepted the employment, then there would have been no need to inform them. Black Star must have a reason for calling them.

In a flash, the leader understood Black Star's thinking. "Your Excellency Black Star, no matter what price the Ancient Emperor Party offers, we'll double it and will not go back on our word."

Since the other party had already made his intentions clear, there was no need for pleasantries. The Pioneer Party immediately gave his offer. In fact, he also wished to receive the aid from the Black Star Army, but it was nigh impossible since the Ancient Emperor Party had long forged a connection with the Black Star Army through their business dealings.

What a good fellow, he actually treated me like a warmonger... Han Xiao's brows twitched, but from the perspective of the Pioneer Party, this was natural since he did not know about Ceselin.

After thinking about it, Han Xiao did not choose to reveal the existence of Ceselin. After all, he had provided him with this mission. Before he took the initiative to jump over, his merits and fame would be hidden.

After pondering for a while, he nodded to the nervous expression of the Pioneer Party leader.

"Good, then it's settled. When the time comes, I'll look for someone to allow you to sign the employment contract."

He ended the call.

Staring at the darkened screen, the leader of the Pioneer Party slumped in his chair, looking out of sorts, as though he had just woken up from a dream.

Without any warning, he suddenly obtained the help of the Black Star Army, such a behemoth?

"Could it be that Black Star is really trying to be a warmonger? He doesn't have to do this." A seed of suspicion bloomed in the leader's mind.

But Black Star clearly had no dealings with his Pioneer Party, so why did he choose them?

"There must be some underlying factor..."

The expression of the Pioneer Party leader flickered.

It was just that Black Star did not reveal anything, and it was not a good time for him to ask. However, the Pioneer Party leader did not wish to be kept in the dark. He decided to slowly dig out the reason. There had to be someone involved that had made Black Star seek employment from him.

On the other side, Han Xiao put his communicator away. His part had come to an end; he only needed to send someone to get the contract finalized before sending out the mission to his faction. The rest would be completed by the players and his members, which did not require his concern.

He had chosen to help the Pioneer Party, not because it had any relation with Ceselin, but because it was indeed the best among the three. Only when he could protect his own interests would he think about sowing good karma. This had always been his work ethic.

On the other hand, the Pioneer Party looked more righteous. Many players loved such a scenario, so it would satisfy their emotional and ethical needs.

Thus, after considering all these factors, he had chosen to give up on the Ancient Emperor Party and Descendant Party, and help the 'righteous' Pioneer Party. This would be conducive to enhancing the players' sense of identification with the army.

...

A few days later, the elites left the Black Star Army headquarters.

The Gulal Civilization's spaceship also left the port, heading into the universe. Ceselin looked back at the Black Star Army headquarters disappearing, his crestfallen expression hard to hide.

Two days prior, the Ancient Emperor Party's leader had contacted him, praising him for his effort and explaining that Black Star had contacted them. They were expecting the Black Star Army's aid soon.

"I didn't manage to convince Black Star... The Pioneer Party..." Ceselin was depressed, and he did not think that he alone could reverse the current plight of the Pioneer Party.

At this moment, his teammate suddenly held out the communicator and exclaimed, "Guys, come look! The Pioneer Party just announced that they've employed the Black Star Army and are formally launching an offensive!"

"What‽"

Everyone was stunned and took out their communicators as well, Ceselin included. The more he read, the more emotional he got.

This... this... what happened‽ Did my words... really have an impact‽

Ceselin was so moved that he found it difficult to restrain himself. His actions had really ushered in a turning point, causing Black Star to make a different choice. If he did not take the risk this time, Black Star would most likely have agreed after the Ancient Emperor Party made their request.

No matter what conditions the Pioneer Party had offered Black Star or how he thought, there was still the fact that he had played a part in this.

Just like the split in train tracks, he was the one who pulled the wrench and steered fate away from its original track.

Ceselin turned back to look in the direction of the Black Star Army, and while he knew that Black Star did not need his gratitude, he still revealed a thankful expression.

He was not aware if Black Star had revealed his identity or chosen to bury this issue. He only thought that he was doing the right thing and did not think to claim credit from the Pioneer Party.

...

Within the machinery factory, Han Xiao released the faction mission that he had on hand before opening the forums to have a look.

The players were already used to such war employments, and since it was such a large-scale collective action each time, they had always welcomed such big events.

While this time was a star system level war, helping a party to destroy its competitors, being able to have their own teammates, and not facing against the entire star system civilization made the difficulty more manageable for the players. The players in the army were excitedly signing up and calling for more support through the forums.

After a few glances, he confirmed that the players' reactions would not have problems and closed the forums. The matters afterward would be settled by the players, so he did not need to worry.

This war employment would likely last until the late to end stages of the version, which gave the players a lot of stuff to do.

This way, I'll have more time to construct my mechanical army.

Han Xiao let out a deep breath.

He had to tide past the experience penalty period, as well as face off against EsGod, sealing his mouth for good. This was the important matter. Because of that, Han Xiao decided to isolate himself in the factory and no longer paid attention to the matters outside.

EsGod was already strong enough. Since he had even obtained an evolution, his combat ability would be off the charts.

Thinking of this, Han Xiao could not help but feel pressure.

To kill this fellow, he had to put in a lot of effort.

Chapter 875: Unable to crack

Half a month later, within the President's Office of the Federation of Light, Bader alone. In front of him was a projection of a normal galaxy human, of moderate height and wearing a large white robe. He had lots of wrinkles on his face. Despite his apparent age, however, he looked spry. His eyes especially were glowing like two luminous stellar bodies. His beard stretched down to his chest, and his hair was also kept very long, tied up with silvery magnetic bands.

This projection was the true appearance of the Mechanic Empire's Manison. His expression was calm, and he was conversing with Bader.

"My troops have sent the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter to the designated scientific research station and completed the handover." Manison's voice was old but full of 'magnetism'.

"Many thanks." Bader was smiling and nodded. "The promised reward will be sent to your Mechanical Race."

As long-term allies, Manison's strength and his achievements had granted him a high position in the Federation of Light. Bader was full of respect toward Manison and had always been serious in ensuring that both parties had a good relationship.

After all, Manison had already assisted several Presidents of the Federation of Light before Bader. Of course, there were also reasons for that; compared to the Arcane Church and the Crimson Dynasty, their rate of change for leaders was much higher.

Manison nodded and changed the topic. "There's another matter."

"Please speak."

"When you decide to come into contact with Black Star, remember to call me."

Bader lurched.

What's this curveball? Why do you think that we'll contact Black Star?

After this incident, Bader did not dare look down on Han Xiao. However, he was also not prepared to send emissaries over to contact Black Star. The latter was allied to the Crimson Dynasty, and unless there was a special reason, a Beyond Grade A would not jump ship. Thus, Bader had no intention of contacting him.

After thinking about it, Bader just thought that Manison was interested in Black Star and agreed. Being Beyond Grade A Mechanics, they would naturally have topics to discuss. It was nothing strange.

"If there's nothing else, I'm hanging up." Manison nodded and cut the connection.

Seeing this, Bader waited for another ten seconds or so before contacting the Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanic under their employment.

"Any abnormalities in the data quantum network?"

"No."

Hearing this, Bader relaxed. While he trusted Manison, he still had to take precautions. After all, Manison was not directly under the Federation of Light but rather an ally from the Ancient Ones. He might be the strongest mechanic alive in this era, so every time he connected remotely, Bader would have Virtual Mechanics monitor the network so that Manison would not open some backdoor.

At the same time, in the distant Primeval Star River, Manison opened his eyes as his consciousness retreated from the quantum network. He smiled.

"The material sealing the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter has reached the level of a Space Wonder. The Federation of Light... is going to have a headache."

When Manison took up the task, he knew that he would come into contact with the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, so he had taken along some research equipment to study the material while en route.

However, this Spacetime Amber isolated all forms of energy, and even detecting its parameters was impossible to achieve. It appeared as 'non-existent' on a lot of his research equipment, and only when utilizing his space research equipment did he then discover that the spatial and temporal coordinates of the Spacetime Amber were weirdly distorted, fixed at a constant value.

He had tried to break apart the amber by disturbing the spacetime coordinates, but the Spacetime Amber also isolated any influence toward its surrounding spacetime coordinates.

Manison had not managed to discover the material structure of this amber. It appeared to be a physical object, yet when observed under a microscope, it appeared as a universe of its own, an area without any movement.

Since there was no particle movement, and time seemed to not exist, which was the theory behind freezing.

Manison thought of the past, during the time of the exploration era where the three Universal Civilizations had changed the physical constraints of the universe near their mother stars, forming a closed and safe area. The Spacetime Amber seemed to be of a similar principle, only stranger. It was as though this material was a condensed secondary space independent of the universe.

Due to his knowledge, he concluded that this was a material on the level of a space wonder.

After his research, he had ruled out the possibility that the Spacetime Amber was a technological advancement. He did not think that Han Xiao would have such an ability at the moment, so he became interested in the treasure that could create such a material.

Other than Black Star, it was unlikely that anyone could break this.

Thus, Manison was sure that the Federation of Light would try to contact Black Star, and it would also not be long from now.

"At that time, I can take the opportunity to know him. Oh, he seems to have bullied my people some time ago."

Manison narrowed his eyes, and it was unknown what he was thinking.

Not too long ago, Manison had sent the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter to one of the Federation of Light's research bases, and it was currently being fixed in a huge machinery cabin. Outside was a pile of research instruments, and many researchers were fully concentrated on the task.

This was an all-in-one material analyzer, which was able to analyze the various parameters of the object without destroying it. This was a standard product used by researchers from advanced civilizations, and the Federation of Light's would naturally be even more advanced. So long as it was an object, its components could be easily analyzed.

The research head stood by the side, his eyes never leaving the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter.

Bader had set down an order that they had to crack the seal for the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. The research team head knew the seriousness of this job and thus had personally gone to supervise it.

Being in charge of a research base, the head would not be any ordinary person. He was one of the bigwigs in the Federation of Light's top research institute and had made many various major scientific research contributions. He had even been awarded the Medal of Honor by the President.

"Reporting! The equipment has been calibrated, and the substance analyzer is ready. Permission to begin?"

"Let's begin." The head nodded.

The researcher pressed a button, and the substance analyzer started to operate, letting out a droning noise. Everyone watched the screen carefully, where the data was changing rapidly.

After a few moments, the artificial intelligence came to a startling conclusion.

"Data error. Substance is unable to be analyzed. The target has energy insulating properties, and the detection rays cannot penetrate it."

The substance analyzer was rendered useless? The head was a little surprised, but such incidents were not unseen. This meant that what they had on hand was a problematic object.

The research facility would naturally not only have one type of analyzer. The head ordered the amber to be run through all the tests, and the number of analyzers that could pick up the Spacetime Amber was pitifully low, which left them still clueless about it.

Since Manison was able to discover the anomaly within the spacetime coordinates, they naturally could deduce the same. Both sides came to the same conclusion—there was no method to crack it.

If even a normal analysis did not work, why talk about cracking it?

The research head got more and more mystified, and his head began to hurt. All conventional methods were ineffective, and he did not know where to start.

Just what sort of toy was this‽

As a researcher, he was full of curiosity and had a mentality of challenging the unknown. However, interest was one thing; his mission was another.

Thinking about Bader's request, the head groaned.

He had a premonition... the president's hopes would soon be dashed.

This object had completely exceeded all their imaginations.

Chapter 876: Great Mechanic Han in Seclusion, Do Not Disturb

"Can't be broken‽"

In the president's office, Bader received a detailed report from the research department, and a look of disbelief could be seen on his face.

He had never doubted the technological skills of the Federation of Light and felt that breaking the seal of the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter would be a piece of cake. He could not have imagined the research department giving him such a 'surprise'.

"Space Wonder grade material that seems to have the ability to solidify space..." Bader read the report again in detail.

He suddenly thought about something, and he immediately entered the intranet of the federation to pull out a secret document. This file was 'Grade 16', and it belonged to the secret category in the Federation of Light. In the Federation of Light, there were a total of twenty different grades.

Grades 1 to 5 contained information that could be revealed to the public such as annual reports. Grades 6 to 10 were restricted documents that most government officials could view. Grades 11 to 15 were confidential documents where a log of who viewed them would be recorded with some details being removed if the viewer did not have enough security clearance. Grades 16 to 19 were secret documents that only the upper echelons could view. Finally, Grade 20 contained top secret documents that would almost never be revealed to the public.

"Confirming your identity... Welcome, President. You have Grade 19.5 authority and have the right to view the entire document."

Bader then began to read the document.

Spacetime Freezer!

This Primordial One had worked for the Federation of Light during the exploration era, and the Federation of Light had kept a file on him, which included a lot of detailed information about him and a breakdown of his Esper Ability. After Bader read the report of the Spacetime Amber, he immediately thought about this Primordial One as their abilities were similar.

The leader of a Universal Civilization had received special training and would be extremely familiar with their own civilization's history, confidential documents, and technological skills. Thus, Bader was able to easily remember the existence of the Spacetime Freezer.

"[Spacetime Freezer] Frogo has the ability to freeze spacetime, and his ability can be ranked as a [Super High Risk Esper Ability]. He can freeze time and space at a set location or target and create a huge influence for Beyond Grade As. The effects of his ability far exceed a Mage's spacetime spells, and there was once an incident of an entire planet being frozen [See Appendix B-004]. There were many records of him freezing the enemy battleship fleet, resulting in the enemy being unable to fight back, and he turned the tides of a few hundred battles [See Appendix B-027]...

"According to our investigations, Frogo needs to exhaust his energy to maintain the spacetime freeze on a region [See Appendix A-001 for the exact breakdown of numbers]. If the supply of energy is broken, the spacetime seal will disappear. The usage of the Esper Ability can be adjusted, and Frogo can freeze the space around him for defense. It can provide defense against most energy and physical attacks, but it is unable to block mental or soul attacks. After further testing, although his Esper Ability can seal a soul, it cannot prevent a soul from moving, and this proves that Frogo's Esper Ability isn't perfect.

"Frogo sacrificed himself in the battle of Planet Millennium [See Appendix B-1940], and his body disappeared."

Bader frowned and thought to himself, Their abilities are extremely similar indeed. Could there be a link between the two? However, even Frogo himself didn't have the ability to manifest the frozen spacetime into a physical object. Just what is going on?

He naturally did not know that the Spacetime Amber had been floating around in the universe for many years and had absorbed the radiation from the universe to mutate into a different object. Mutation happened because of the change in gene structure of an individual. Frogo's Esper Ability was not perfect, and although it was able to freeze spacetime, he could not defend against mental attacks. However, the mutated Spacetime Amber did not have this weakness, and even a mental attack would not be able to pierce the amber that it created.

After thinking for a while, Bader decided to send a copy of this information to the research head and hope that it would be helpful.

Breaking the seal of the Spacetime Amber was far more difficult than he had imagined. Bader had chosen to snatch the Arcane Church's trump card, but they were not able to use it despite snatching it for themselves. It was no more than an ornament for them.

Thinking back, it seemed as though the Arcane Church would not have been able to break the seal even if they retrieved it.

This should have been a problem for the Arcane Church to have a headache over, but it is now our turn to suffer. I thought that we would offend the Arcane Church greatly, but we only snatched something that the other party wouldn't even be able to use...

Just what was the point of us snatching this item ‽

It seems as though we've suffered a loss!

Bader was truly in a terrible mood.

No wonder, Manison thought that I would send someone to meet Black Star. He also noticed that this item is extremely weird. It seems like I must find an opportunity to contact Black Star.

Bader shook his head. He was not willing to treat the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter as just an ornament.

At the same time, he could also allow the descendants of the Spacetime Freezer to be the emissary. As members from the same race, they might be able to detect some clues and find out if the Universal Treasure in Black Star's hands was related to their ancestor.

...

The Arcane Church was also feeling frustrated.

After a series of negotiations, the Crimson Dynasty had already agreed to allow the Arcane Church ransom back one of their Beyond Grade A. After paying a huge price, the Arcane Church finally got back Dylan. They actually wanted Sagman, but the dynasty did not agree. The first one to be returned would be the weakest one for sure.

However, Dylan's Spacetime Amber seal was not released, and the dynasty wanted to get the Arcane Church to deal with it on their own. The main reason for doing so was so they could verify if the Spacetime Amber seal was truly as troublesome as Han Xiao made it out to be.

Naturally, the Crimson Dynasty still did not know that the Federation of Light had stolen the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter, and Urranrell wanted to use Dylan as an indicator to see whether the seal on the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was broken.

The dynasty made use of an excuse that Black Star was currently in seclusion and did not wish to be disturbed. Helpless, the Arcane Church could only get their own research personnel to attempt to break the seal.

The result was naturally the same as the Federation of Light, and they were unable to do a thing to the Spacetime Amber.

The Arcane Church was also extremely frustrated but also a little thankful.

They were frustrated that the dynasty had scammed them once more, and they would have to pay the price to invite the dynasty to unseal Dylan. However, they were thankful because the Federation of Light would probably be helpless toward the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter as well.

Although their own Universal Treasure had been stolen by the Federation of Light, the other party was only able to look at it through the seal but unable to use it.

If not for the grudge between them, the Arcane Church might have praised Black Star.

The Federation of Light and Arcane Church began paying close attention to the other party's research as a result. They wanted to see if the other party had any progress while also trying to spy on each other to 'copy the answer'.

With the Arcane Church taking a step back, the conflict between both parties was no longer as heated, and their soldiers were also recalled from the borders. The galactic organizations paying attention to this event heaved a sigh of relief.

The explored universe gradually calmed down.

The Federation of Light and Arcane Church temporarily took a step back, and the Super Star Cluster Civilizations that wanted to exploit the opportunity also became low profile. No one wanted to provoke the Crimson Dynasty at such a moment and wanted to wait until the storm passed.

...

The Black Star Army arrived at the Star System where the Gulal Civilization was located.

The outpost planet of the Pioneer Party was already within their sights, and the Black Star Army landed according to the instructions of the base. The warriors of the Black Star Army disembarked from the thousand-meter-long battleships and gathered at the port.

Apart from the army's warriors, there were a few million players participating in this mission. A War Employment Mission was a huge event, and it was much more interesting than exploring the Flickering World. Thus, most players accepted the mission and joined the civil war in this Star System Civilization with the identity of mercenaries.

Half a month ago, the Pioneer Party announced that they were working together with the Black Star Army, and news of the Black Star Army's interference stirred up a huge storm in the Gulal Civilization. The Ancient Emperor Party and Descendant Party were immediately thrown into internal chaos with a small portion of their upper echelons escaping or defecting to the Pioneer Party. The remaining members of the party decided to seize the initiative, and both parties joined hands to attack the Pioneer Party's territory.

There was no need for the three parties to make any preparations before the war as all three parties had always maintained war readiness. The three parties had split up the Gulal Civilization's land into three regions and lined up troops to guard their own territories. The commander only needed to give the order for war to begin.

Thus, the entrance of the Black Star Army also signaled the beginning of the war between the three parties.

The officers of the Pioneer Party first had a discussion with the commander of the Black Star Army's fleet, and the players were given a new list of missions to choose from.

The Pioneer Party provided a military star map with the nine Star Zones of the other two parties being marked out.

The majority of the Black Star Army manpower was sent back to the Flickering World, and the remaining manpower was left to guard their bases. Thus, not many mercenaries were sent to complete the mission, and they did not have an overwhelming advantage in strength. As such, it would be difficult to complete this mission in a short period. With their objectives of exterminating the enemy army and capturing the enemy's planets, the Black Star Army needed to push the battle line forward slowly to capture the enemy territories.

The colonial planets, resource rich planets, and military bases were the missions that the players could choose. As such, there were many opportunities for ground battles. This was a civil war after all, and they would not choose to bomb the enemy's planet to capture it. As such, the players were immediately put to good use. The greatest place to utilize a few million Grade B players was a ground battle!

After looking through the mission introduction, the players all grew excited. They had experienced many different events already and instantly knew that this mission would be the most exciting one. Fighting together with a battleship was extremely troublesome, and the players preferred fighting monsters on the ground instead. Furthermore, they were the main characters of this employment mission, and they only needed to enjoy the battle to their heart's content.

The size and levels of the enemy had been indicated, and the players could make their decision carefully. The levels of the enemies were also extremely clear. The enemy could be roughly broken down into a few different groups: cannon fodder soldiers, Grade C high grade monsters, Grade B elite monsters, Grade B mini-bosses, and a few Calamity Grade bosses that had their own names.

All the players were extremely satisfied with the mission. This was the main reason they joined the mission—to fight as they wished!

They finally did not have to just watch from the side!

Chapter 877: The Mysterious Individual Watching the Players

For one month later, the Pioneer Party defended against the attacks of the Ancient Emperor Party and Descendant Party while counterattacking with the Black Star Army. The three parties tried to break through the holes of the enemy's defenses, which resulted in a jagged territorial line on the star map.

At this moment, a colonial planet that was near the border of the Ancient Emperor Party was being invaded. The Pioneer Party and Black Star Army fleet were engaged in an intense battle with the defense fleet of the planet. At the same time, the cities on the planet were being attacked from the sky with their protective shields being bombarded and drop pods being launched at the holes created.

A hemispherical light screen covered the capital city of this colonial planet and endured the never-ending attacks from the sky. Multicolored explosions could be seen on the surface of the light screen, and the protective shield began to flicker unsteadily.

Upon considering the many reasons for a civil war, the local army closed off all the underground sanctuaries and prohibited their civilians from entering. The many inhabitants of the city could only tremble in their own homes, and the ground troops of the city gathered together and looked up at the sky.

Ka-cha!

The protective shield of the city finally could not endure the waves of attacks and began to crack before everyone's eyes.

The next moment, densely packed black dots could be seen appearing from the sky, descending from above like meteors.

The anti-air cannons of the city immediately opened fire toward the drop pods, and balls of explosions could be seen in the air.

A portion of the drop pods were destroyed in the sky, but many managed to land in the city.

The army of players emerged from the drop pods and sprang into action.

Every one of them had a detection device on them to scan and indicate all hostile targets who had a weapon. The descending army was already extremely used to such missions and began clearing up the enemies in the city.

Battles erupted in every corner of the city, and the players began exchanging fire with the ground troops. Although they had a disadvantage in terms of numbers, the players were almost all Grade B Supers, and a large majority of the enemies were ordinary soldiers.

Grade B Supers were mid-ranked combatants in the galaxy with all of them having the combat strength of an entire army. Destroying a building was a piece of cake, and the players were not ordinary Grade B Supers. They were not afraid of coming under fire and could fight without any worry.

The ground troops were extremely shocked to realize that these galactic mercenaries could charge forward while enduring heavy fire without any fear of death. They were able to easily cut through their formations and massacre their troops.

From the map, the black dots that represented the player army rapidly weaved through the city, and the red dots that represented the enemies disappeared quickly.

At the center of the city, the government building had already been attacked by seven parties of players.

In some room of the government building, an Ancient Emperor Party Grade B Super knelt on the ground with his eyes wide open in shock. The individual in front of him pulled out a blade from his throat, and blood splattered everywhere.

Life was drained from his body, and he collapsed into a pool of his own blood.

"This fellow's level is pretty high. I've only got thirty-seven percent of my health left." Frenzied Sword shook off the blood on his blade.

The silver black armor that he was wearing now was Mechanical Pugilist equipment with various hidden mechanical weapons hidden all around.

The entire room was littered with corpses, and the members of Rivervale and his teammates were beside him. They had just worked together to get rid of everyone in the room and were now repairing the durability of their equipment while searching for their spoils of war.

Outside the door, the sound of intense fire could be heard. This Grade B officer that they had killed seemed to be pretty important, and a large number of enemy troops were drawn to their location. Maple Moon was keeping guard outside the door, and she used her mechanic traps and electromagnetic artillery tower to return fire. The defenses of a Grade B Mechanic were not something that ordinary soldiers would be able to overcome. They were all suppressed in a corner of the corridor, and their few attempts to charge forward ended with a ground full of corpses.

Maple Moon usually enjoyed playing with Rivervale, and Frenzied Sword was also willing to bring along a reliable Mechanic. The two of them had a pretty good relationship.

When the Mechanics came into contact with compression technology in Version 3.0, they became the most popular choice to form a party with. Mechanics no longer had to slowly build their machines, and their preparation speed increased greatly. Regardless of whether it was to fight a dungeon or complete a mission, every party would generally have a Mechanic. Of course, every Mechanic had a different set of equipment and was able to deal with different circumstances.

Evil Sword injected himself with a serum to recover his health and casually said, "I wonder how many Grade B enemies there are in this city."

"We should have taken care of most of them." Frenzied Sword looked at the battle map. "The soldiers in the city have been mostly wiped out. Hao Tian and the others have already killed four Grade Bs downstairs."

"How lucky. We only managed to kill two along the way," Evil Sword said with envy.

Grade B Supers were elites that could provide them with plenty of experience. Furthermore, every Grade B elite had a name and would give them additional rewards for the mission. Apart from experience, they were able to collect an additional bounty from the Pioneer Party, and all the players were extremely passionate about killing Grade B enemies.

To a first-rate party, perhaps it would be impossible to solo a Grade B elite, but a party of five was able to easily win against an ordinary Grade B Super. Even if a mini-boss Grade B enemy was difficult to deal with, it was still within the capabilities of the players.

A Star System Civilization would only have ten or twenty Calamity Grade Supers, and they would only appear in key battles. Thus, the millions of Grade B players were basically invincible in the other colonial planets.

Not too long later, the army in this city was completely wiped out, and the players returned to the spaceship before being sent to a new battlefield.

...

"Another three colonial planets were taken down by the Black Star Army's immortals."

The upper echelons of the Ancient Emperor Party looked at the star map, and worry could be seen on their frail faces.

"The immortals of the Black Star Army are far too scary, and it is impossible to restrain them," one of the officers said. "Up until now, a total of twenty-one colonial planets have been seized by them."

If the enemy only had a fleet of battleships, they would not feel such a headache. The Ancient Emperor Party was completely helpless against the immortals.

The total number of immortals was probably more than all the Grade Bs in their civilization, and these immortals could not even be killed.

The upper echelons of the Ancient Emperor Party could only watch as the players capable of reviving captured their colonial planets one after another.

The immortals of the Black Star Army had always been famous in the Shattered Star Ring, and it was their chance to experience it personally this time. Everyone present could not help but feel despair.

Such an enemy was truly far too frightening. Anyone capable of having such a trump card would definitely have a place in the universe!

With the participation of the Black Star Army, the Ancient Emperor Party could no longer see much hope. It would be impossible for them to win if they continued fighting, and the Pioneer Party would probably emerge victorious in another year or so.

However, it was equally impossible for them to surrender. No one would be willing to give up a Star System Civilization. They had already held on for a year, and holding on further might give them a chance to turn the tables around. As they fought back, the upper echelons of the Ancient Emperor Party had been trying to find reinforcements and plan their retreat.

"That b*stard Ceselin actually defected to the Pioneer Party and even took all his subordinates away. I never imagined that he would be a traitor!" The Ancient Emperor Party leader gritted his teeth. "He must have done something to get the Black Star Army to help the Pioneer Party. If not, there isn't an explanation for their sudden intervention!"

Upon mentioning Ceselin, a look of hatred could be seen on everyone's face. If not for his betrayal, they would not have been reduced to such a pathetic state!

"This traitorous b*stard! We have never treated him badly before. We have given him both authority and wealth. Just what is he dissatisfied about, and what right does he have to betray us!"

The Ancient Emperor Party leader slammed the table and said with heartache, "He actually told me that our ideals were different. What a joke! Look at what he did. Just for his so-called ideals, he actually sacrificed so many of his fellow brothers. Does he really think that his actions are extremely noble‽ We have been ruling the civilization extremely well, and this civilization will lose their rightful rulers just because of him! Dammit!"

Upon hearing that, the upper echelons by the side listened with helpless expressions.

Others might have had the rights to say such words, but they knew that they did not. All of them were extremely clear about what their Ancient Emperor Party had done over the past few years.

The way they saw it, their leader must have been angered silly and was just venting his anger.

Right at this moment, the Ancient Emperor Party suddenly stopped cursing, and his entire body froze in place. He then suddenly regained his cool and stood up slowly, with his tone being completely transformed into a different persona.

"It seems like everyone is extremely frustrated. Maybe I can be of some help."

All the upper echelons were stunned for a moment, and they stood up abruptly.

Was their leader's mind being controlled‽

The leader of a Star System Civilization would usually be protected by a Calamity Grade spell and psychic energy. This was to prevent him from being controlled by another. At the very least, it would be impossible for a Calamity Grade Super to control the leader of a Star System Civilization without any traces in front of a crowd.

Just who did this?

Could it be a Beyond Grade A‽

"Who are you‽" a military officer said with caution and sent a message to get all the Calamity Grades to rush over.

"You don't need to worry. I did not come with ill intentions. I do not have any intention to tell you my identity," the Ancient Emperor Party leader said emotionlessly. "All of you only need to know that I will provide you with resources and manpower to fight the Black Star Army."

The upper echelons were still doubtful as they looked at each other. However, regardless of whether this was true or false, they decided to play along. At the same time, they were also worried that their comrades might have been controlled. After all, this mysterious individual indeed had the ability to do so.

"What do you want?"

"Don't worry. I do not want anything."

"Then, why are you helping us?"

"I am not bothered about your Gulal Civilization, but I am interested in the immortals of the Black Star Army. Furthermore, the longer all of you can survive, the more I can observe them," the 'Ancient Emperor Party leader' said. "My suggestion will only provide all of you with benefits. Do you accept?"

Everyone looked at each other before nodding hesitantly.

"Very good, I will get my people to contact all of you soon. Right, I can give you a suggestion. All of you can try employing the immortals of the Black Star Army."

Everyone was stunned.

"The Black Star Army is our enemy. You are asking us to seek aid from our enemies? Just what is the meaning of this?"

"Ordinary logic doesn't seem to be applicable to the immortals. How will you know without trying?" the 'Ancient Emperor Party leader' said with a teasing voice.

The Ancient Emperor Party leader then suddenly trembled, and his eyes fell into a daze. He then suddenly snapped out of his daze.

"Has the person controlling me left‽"

Everyone heaved a sigh of relief and immediately went forward to support their leader.

"Do you still remember what you said when you were controlled?"

"I remember everything. My body was controlled, but my senses were still present."

Right at this moment, the Calamity Grade Supers arrived, and after hearing what had happened, they began to check the leader's condition.

"How is it?" the Ancient Emperor Party leader asked.

"The enchantments used to guard your mind were destroyed in an instant. These enchantments are capable of defending against a Calamity Grade Psychic for ten minutes. The one who controlled you is definitely a Beyond Grade A."

The expression of the Ancient Emperor Party leader changed slightly. A Beyond Grade A had a huge significance to a Star System Civilization.

There were only five Beyond Grade As in the Shattered Star Ring, and only Psyker and Austin had the ability to infiltrate the mind.

Though, it might not be these two but a Beyond Grade A from another Star Field.

Thinking about the words of the mysterious individual, everyone could not help but have a strange look on their face.

To think that they would gain support through such a strange method. This was something that they had never imagined, but at least they now had some hope.

Although they did not know who the other party was, since he was also a Beyond Grade A, he should not be afraid of the Black Star Army.

"Right, he even asked us to seek aid from our enemy. Isn't this a joke‽ Does he think that the Black Star Army will turn around to help us?"

Everyone was the most puzzled by this suggestion. It was obviously a meaningless action, and they truly did not understand the point of doing so.

The Ancient Emperor Party leader nodded. "Since we do not have any way of retreating, why not we give it a try?"

Chapter 878: Suspicion

The governing planet of the Pioneer Party was located in Star Zone 3, and the upper echelons within the party were observing the situation of the battle.

In the conference room, the upper echelons of the party were gathered, and the atmosphere was completely different from the meeting in the Ancient Emperor Party. Everyone had a bright smile on their face, with the Pioneer Party's leader glowing with radiance.

Their army had the upper hand, and it was impossible for them not to be happy.

"The Ancient Emperor Party and Descendant Party are being forced back, and the citizens are also crying out for us to overthrow the rulers. The situation is to our advantage at the moment," the staff sergeant in charge of analyzing the battle situation said.

The Pioneer Party leader had a bright smile on his face but said, "We need to be even more careful during such a moment and prevent the enemy from fighting back in desperation."

Although the situation was looking good, he knew that it was impossible for the Ancient Emperor Party to surrender. The result of losing would be extermination.

Just as everyone was discovering the situation, the internal comms rang, and it was an emergency message from the intelligence personnel.

The appearance of the intelligence personnel appeared, and he had a strange look on his face.

"Your Excellency, the Ancient Emperor Party made an announcement."

"Send it over immediately." The Pioneer Party leader raised his brows.

Very quickly, the announcement of the Ancient Emperor Party appeared on the screen, and everyone present began reading it.

In this first half of the announcement, the Ancient Emperor Party claimed that they were the rightful rulers of the Gulal Civilization and criticized the Pioneer Party for using armed forces to seize authority. They then claimed that the Pioneer Party were traitors and called for the citizens to reject the Pioneer Party. They also began hiring help from the galaxy.

The details of the public announcement were extremely ordinary. They were trying to preserve their status as rightful rulers and suppress their opponents. They had made use of such a tactic for many years already, and the upper echelons of the Pioneer Party were extremely used to it. After they won, history would be written by them, and it would be useless to call them traitors now.

The way they saw it, it was completely useless for the Ancient Emperor Party to seek aid from the galaxy. This was only a civil war, which did not go against the Peace Treaty. With the Black Star Army on their side, no one in the Shattered Star Ring would go against the Black Star Army just for a Star System Civilization.

The mercenary groups that had some size would not help them, and the other civilizations would only watch by the side. Even the Bloodshed Land would not go against their titular ally for such a small matter. Thus, it was impossible for the Ancient Emperor Party to find any aid. This was the powerful effect of seeking aid from the Black Star Army. They were able to prevent the enemy from finding any support.

The Pioneer Party's leader then read until the end and was stunned.

"Wait a moment... the Ancient Emperor Party is trying to seek aid from the Black Star Army‽"

The Pioneer Party's leader rubbed his eyes and thought that he had misread something.

To think that the Ancient Emperor Party actually wanted to employ the Black Star Army and attempted to convince the Black Star Army to help them.

The upper echelons of the Pioneer Party all looked at each other with confused looks on their faces.

Just what was the meaning of seeking aid from their enemy‽

Even if the Black Star Army was external aid, they had already signed an employment contract. Why would they publicly break the contract? Would this not be destroying their own reputation? Furthermore, the Black Star Army was a Beyond Grade A organization, and since they had already decided to help the Pioneer Party, why would they suddenly go back on their word?

Even if you want to try and rope the Black Star Army over to your side, you should do it privately, right? With the current status of Black Star, would he openly go back on his word? Do you think he will go back on his word because of money? That's impossible!

But if the objective of this is to drive a wedge between us, isn't it far too coarse a method?

"It seems like the Ancient Emperor Party has truly gone crazy," the Pioneer Party leader said with his mouth cramping up. "This should be the funniest joke that I have ever heard."

"Hahaha..."

Everyone could not help but burst into laughter.

...

Not too long later, the announcement of the Ancient Emperor Party was spread all throughout the Gulal Civilization.

It was not just the Pioneer Party who were puzzled. Even the Descendant Party were completely bewildered.

Are my teammates fools‽

The members of the Ancient Emperor Party felt extremely embarrassed. They were currently fighting with the enemy, but their higher ups actually tried to seek help from the enemy. Just what was this stupidity?

There were many who interpreted this as the upper echelons being pessimistic about the outcome of the battle, and morale took a large hit.

On the Black Star Army's side, the members of the army could not help but laugh.

We are currently fighting a war. Can you please be more serious and not tease us like that?

Just when everyone was laughing at the actions of the Ancient Emperor Party, the players received a different message.

The plea of the Ancient Emperor Party had actually become a mission on their interface. A Grade S mission for them to help the Ancient Emperor Party.

All the players gasped in shock upon discovering that.

"So, it turns out that this is a faction series mission. It should be a Grade S mission that can be triggered regardless of which party we aid."

"However, the army has chosen to support the Pioneer Party, so we have no choice but to choose them as well."

"Hmm, if we support a faction up into power, we will be able to successfully change the entire fate of a civilization. I think we found a way to strike it rich."

"What if we persuade the NPCs to start another party and support the party. Would it be even more fun?"

This mission attracted the attention of many players, and they began to show off their creativity as they discussed the matter.

However, the influence of this new mission stopped there. Not a single player would choose to accept it.

The players were not fools, and accepting this mission would mean that they had to oppose the army. It would probably be no different from leaving the faction. They had fought in the army for three versions already and accumulated plenty of faction Contribution Points. Furthermore, the potential for growth in the Black Star Army was also extremely high. A mere Star System Civilization was not worth them betraying the faction.

Furthermore, the chances of the Ancient Emperor Party winning were far too low. Thus, it would be much better for them to keep to the Pioneer Party mission, especially since both were Grade S missions anyway.

After a month into the employment mission, the players had an understanding of the three parties. The Ancient Emperor Party was not anything good, and there was no meaning to help them.

With Summer Night Flower as an example, the number of players in the Shattered Star Ring willing to take risks had decreased. Thus, the players were only interested in the opportunity presented to them by the Ancient Emperor Party but uninterested in actually completing the mission.

...

In the Black Star Army headquarters, a large assembly line ran through Han Xiao's workshop without stopping to produce various types of mechanical soldiers and equipment. Bolts of Mechanical Force could be seen running through the assembly lines to increase the quality and efficiency of the production.

In another region, all the freshly manufactured mechanical soldiers and equipment were sent over with many mechanical arms modifying the equipment.

Han Xiao would naturally modify all his mechanical soldiers as much as possible, and all the modified equipment would have their grades increased. Even the cannon fodder mechanical soldiers had been raised to the orange grade.

At Han Xiao's level, an ordinary mechanical soldier was no more than cannon fodder, but these mechanical soldiers were all elite equipment that could not even be purchased with money.

Han Xiao stood in front of a machine and personally assembled a new mechanical host while humming a tune merrily.

The sound of metal ringing could be heard all around him, and Han Xiao had already gotten used to the environment in the workshop. Creating machines was a form of enjoyment to him. As his own strength increased, Great Mechanic Han also grew to enjoy the process of crafting new equipment.

Phillip's mini projection could be seen in front of Han Xiao, and he said to Han Xiao with a babyish voice, "Master, hum... I saw an interesting piece of news. Shall I read it out to you?"

"Alright." Han Xiao wasn't distracted and remained focused on hammering the alloy before him.

"It's news from the Gulal Civilization. The Ancient Emperor Party actually made a public announcement and hoped that we will go back on our word and help them instead. Master, hum... what do you think they are thinking about?"

"To think that they will make such an announcement. Do they think I am like EsGod, without any morals?" Han Xiao laughed.

"Eh‽" Phillip was stunned, and his eyes widened. "Isn't that the case‽"

"... You have also learned how to joke, huh?" Han Xiao immediately changed the topic and said, "Although it is difficult to understand why the Ancient Emperor Party would do so, I guess it is still understandable. If not for Ceselin, I would have never come into contact with the Pioneer Party. They... eh?"

Right at this moment, Han Xiao suddenly froze in place and thought about the Ancient Emperor Party missions. He then opened the forums to take a look.

The players were indeed discussing this matter on the forums, and many of the players took a screenshot of the Ancient Emperor Party Grade S mission. His guess was not wrong, and the Ancient Emperor Party's plea for help allowed the players to trigger a mission.

Han Xiao stroked his chin and fell into thought.

Although it only seemed like a desperate move by the Ancient Emperor Party, Han Xiao could not help but think that the matter was extremely odd.

"This is an illogical plea for aid. It feels as though..." Han Xiao's eyes narrowed. "This plea for help is targeted at the players."

It was not that he was being suspicious, but there were far too many coincidences. Although the actions of the Ancient Emperor Party seemed like a joke to everyone, it was not a joke to the players but a way for them to trigger a mission.

Was this by luck or an intentional action?

Han Xiao hesitated for a moment. He had too few clues and was not certain about his own guess. However, he would always plan for the worst-case scenario to be safe.

There was a reason for this. In his previous life, there was a similar phase. As the players began to grow and move around in the universe, many galactic organizations began to pay attention to the players and analyzed their characteristics, specialties, and habits.

Even during the current version, there were many organizations that paid close attention to the players.

He had operated in the Shattered Star Ring for many years, and no one would dare steal his trump card force with his status. However, the situation of the players in the other Star Fields was different, and it was not strange for the players to attract the attention of the organizations.

He was not the only one who wanted to recruit the players.

Han Xiao was not too worried about this. The players had already invested three versions of their time and effort into the army, and they would not be so easily stolen by another. Furthermore, ordinary NPCs would only treat the players as a special force. Other NPCs did not have an interface and would not be able to obtain a massive amount of experience from the players.

However, it would also be extremely frustrating if someone really wanted to steal his vegetables.

I originally planned to ignore the Gulal Civilization mission, but it seems like I must pay close attention to it now. Someone has set their eyes on the players of the army.

A cold glint flashed past Han Xiao's eyes.

...

A mysterious fleet then entered the border of the Gulal Civilization. This was the Ancient Emperor Party territory, and the Ancient Emperor Party fleet was already present.

In the main flagship, the Ancient Emperor Party leader looked at the star map and heaved a sigh of relief. "They're finally here."

That mysterious Beyond Grade A had promised to provide them with reinforcements, and this fleet was the first batch of reinforcements. The Ancient Emperor Party leader wanted to guess the identity of the Beyond Grade A through the fleet but could not help but be surprised upon seeing the insignia of the reinforcements.

This was a local armed organization in the Shattered Star Ring that was managed by four Calamity Grade Supers. One of them was even a Beyond Grade A seed. As a result, the fame and size of the organization was not too small, but many people believed that they did not have any backers.

However, it seemed like this low-profile organization actually had an unknown Beyond Grade A behind them.

Just who was this mysterious Beyond Grade A. Could it be that he had more than one organization under him in the Shattered Star Ring?

The Ancient Emperor Party leader suppressed the doubts in his heart and contacted the other party.

With the aid of this armed organization, their situation will be much better.

The flagships of both parties met each other, and the Ancient Emperor Party leader's projection met the four Calamity Grade leaders.

"I am the leader of the Gulal Civilization. I thank..."

"We will help you suppress the traitors. There isn't any need to thank us as we are only fulfilling our orders." That Beyond Grade A seed interrupted the words of the Ancient Emperor Party leader.

The Ancient Emperor Party leader thought for a while before probing, "I wonder, who is the one giving the orders?"

Right at this moment, a member by the side suddenly trembled, and he was possessed by the mysterious Beyond Grade A. "Don't try to find out who I am, otherwise our agreement will come to an end."

The Ancient Emperor Party leader was shocked and immediately nodded in agreement.

"We have followed your suggestion, but the Black Star Army has shown no reaction."

"Is that so?" The mysterious individual was not surprised. "Failure cannot be avoided, and the habits that I have grasped won't always work. That's why I need to observe and experiment more."

The mysterious individual fell into deep thought. "However, it seems like Black Star doesn't only have good luck but has also grasped some of their habits like me."

Chapter 879: End of the Penalty

With the Ancient Emperor Party receiving fresh reinforcements, the advancement of the Pioneer Party was restricted.

An armed organization being led by a Beyond Grade A seed entering the battle to help the Ancient Emperor Party? All the organizations watching the civil war were naturally shocked.

There were still those who dared fight the Black Star Army in the Shattered Star Ring? Although the Black Star Army was not the sole tyrant of the Shattered Star Ring, such an action still baffled many. After all, this was fighting the Black Star Army head on.

The Black Star Army had plenty of experts in its ranks. Where did the four Calamity Grade Supers get their courage to intervene in the Black Star Army's employment mission? Even if one of them was a Beyond Grade A seed, it still was not enough.

Han Xiao, who received news from Phillip, had his thoughts verified at that moment.

Furthermore, Han Xiao knew who the mastermind was upon seeing the armed organization.

"It turns out to be them..." Han Xiao came to a realization.

The Beyond Grade A seed of this organization was called Luthor, and he was a famous Super who was active in the Shattered Star Ring. In truth, Luthor was actually an elite member of a financial group that spanned across various Star Fields called [Limitless].

Peaceful times brought about plenty of business opportunities and many large financial groups. Limitless was a unique financial group because its leader was a Beyond Grade A Super.

Not every Beyond Grade A wanted to form an armed organization, and different Beyond Grade As had various interests and strengths. The Limitless leader was a Beyond Grade A who enjoyed making money by the name of Sorokin. He had a special position in the universe.

After Sorokin took over as leader of the financial group, he developed the Limitless Financial Group to its current scale.

This super financial group was an elite business organization that was involved in many sectors, including management, military, technological, trade, intelligence, service, and manufacturing. It had many different brands under its name, and its operations spanned across many different Star Fields. It was a conglomerate that was extremely famous and even had business dealings with the three Universal Civilizations.

The Limitless Financial Group belonged to the neutral faction and was already a listed company in the universe. Their assets were frightening, and their logo was a Mobius strip.

The armed branch of the Limitless Financial Group was not to be underestimated. With a frightening amount of wealth, the Limitless Financial Group developed many subsidiary organizations in the various Star Fields, which were akin to the military might of the financial group. Luthor's organization was such an existence.

Furthermore, Sorokin was not the only Beyond Grade A combatant in the Limitless Financial Group. Sorokin had roped in a few other Beyond Grade A allies through their stocks with a few Ancient Ones being included.

With money to open the path for them, the Limitless Financial Group's network was unfathomable.

In comparison, although the Black Star Army was also a Beyond Grade A organization, its history was far too short, and the scale was incomparable to the other party.

Luthor had only exposed his own identity in the later versions, and no one knew that Luthor belonged to the Limitless Financial Group at this moment. However, Han Xiao was different; he understood Luthor's background. As such, he immediately knew the mastermind interfering in the Gulal Civilization's affairs.

This was his unique advantage. Many 'secrets' were not secrets before his eyes.

The Limitless Financial Group seems to be extremely interested in the players, but this isn't too strange, Han Xiao thought to himself.

In his previous life, the Limitless Financial Group was a faction that players could join with their headquarters being in the Sea of Star Spirits. Many players in the Sea of Star Spirits joined the financial group during the middle phase of the game.

Even now, there was a large group of players in the Sea of Star Spirits being recruited by the Limitless Financial Group, and the Limitless Financial Group was pretty popular on the forums.

Han Xiao could guess the other party's intentions, and they probably wanted to spy on his vegetable garden.

Hmm, they should have noticed that the immortal troop is extremely similar to the players that they have recruited and sent someone to probe the players. Perhaps the Limitless Financial Group will discover some of the player's habits. For example, they only have to issue a request to the players, and even if it isn't logical, some of the players will still carry out the request. Thus, they got the Ancient Emperor Party to issue a plea for help toward the army to test the reaction of the players.

Han Xiao's guess was not too far from the truth.

If I'm remembering it right, the Limitless Financial Group was also very active in the Flickering World...

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The various Star Fields had their own organizations, and they would all enter the Flickering World in Version 4.0 to become competitors. The Limitless Financial Group was one such organization.

It seems like I cannot avoid coming into contact with them in the future.

Han Xiao pondered for a moment before calling for his Black Star Guards.

Very quickly, Hila brought the members of the Black Star Guards into the workshop.

"I have a mission for all of you."

With a wave of his hands, a holographic screen appeared with Luthor's information being displayed.

"This armed organization entered the Gulal Civilization civil war and provided reinforcements to the Ancient Emperor Party. I want all of you to reinforce the front lines and get rid of the four of them. Right, the one called Luthor is a Beyond Grade A seed. Hila and Hadavy, be careful."

"Alright." Hila nodded.

"I know Luthor." Hadavy crossed his arms. "I approached him for a spar a long time ago. He is an extremely powerful Pugilist. Strange, I remember him as someone who kept an extremely low profile. Why would he suddenly go against the army?"

"Who knows?"

Han Xiao was not prepared to tell anyone else that he was aware of the other party's background.

The Limitless Financial Group probably thought that they were still operating from the shadows, and Han Xiao planned to keep things as such.

"Alright then." Hadavy did not say anything else. Although he knew Luthor, he would not go easy on Luthor since he was going against the army.

The Black Star Guards then left the room. Han Xiao opened the doors to the secondary dimension and summoned his Apostle Weapons.

"Lord."

Psionic Prime knelt so that his head was at the same level as Han Xiao.

"Take a batch of mechanical soldiers to the Gulal Civilization," Han Xiao said. "If Hila and the others do not succeed, find a chance to get rid of Luthor's group of four. Phillip will send you information about the enemy."

He could not do anything to the Limitless Financial Group as both parties were not enemies. However, exterminating Luthor's group was not an issue since it was in line with the Black Star Army's stance. Since they had accepted an employment mission to go against the Black Star Army, the other party would definitely kill members of the army.

Since the Limitless Financial Group was eyeing on his immortal troop and wanted to probe them, Han Xiao would use this opportunity to pull out the claws sent by the Limitless Financial Group. He would still be able to warn the other party even if he pretended that he was not aware of their objective. This would prevent the Limitless Financial Group from becoming bolder and sending more people to probe him.

...

Boom!

A spaceship crashed onto the surface of an uninhabited planet, leaving a huge crater behind.

When the spaceship stopped rolling, Luthor crawled out from the wreckage.

Hila and the other Black Star Guards descended from the sky with light injuries.

Luthor's injuries were far more severe, and he held onto his bleeding chest. His beating heart could be seen through his ribs, and his wounds were slowly healing.

"Black Star truly thinks highly of me. He sent out his entire Black Star Guards. Cough cough, it will be an honor even if I end up dying today." Luthor's face was pale, but despair could not be seen on his face. Instead, he looked extremely carefree as though he had seen through life and death.

Both parties had met on the battlefield, and the Black Star Guards had already taken out his three comrades. He was the only one left, and his time had come.

Hadavy shook his head and said, "I don't understand why you had to accept the employment mission of the Ancient Emperor Party. If it was to earn money, why did you have to go against the Black Star Army? You killed the members of the army, and His Excellency Black Star was always going to send experts after you. You definitely knew this fact."

"I do not have a habit of giving explanations to others." Luthor took a deep breath and prepared to fight to the death.

Hadavy hesitated for a moment and tried to persuade him. "Surrender. His Excellency Black Star is very easy going and treasures talents. You are a Beyond Grade A seed, and His Excellency won't make things difficult for you if you are willing to join the army."

"Ha! I am not interested in that. Either kill me or be killed by me. I am not prepared for a third choice."

"Is there really such a need?" Hadavy frowned. "There isn't any hatred between us, and it wasn't easy for you to become a Beyond Grade A seed. Why do you have to rush to your death?"

Bang!

Luthor replied with a fist to Hadavy's face.

The many Black Star Guards took action together and filled the entire planet with craters.

Even if Luthor was a Beyond Grade A seed, he could not endure such a ferocious attack. His mind, which was riddled with holes by Hila's attack, finally collapsed, and his soulless body fell to the ground.

Luthor became nutrition for Hila's Esper Ability.

Hadavy let out a sigh by the side. It was a pity that such a good man had been killed just like that.

The Black Star Guards then cleaned up the battlefield before leaving the planet. Not too long after they left the planet, Psionic Prime appeared outside the atmosphere with his mechanical troops.

"The Black Star Guards have killed the target, so we don't need to take action."

Psionic Prime had been watching the battle from the side.

...

"Luthor is dead?"

In the conference room, the upper echelons of the Ancient Emperor Party were stunned.

Although they knew that the reinforcements would not be a match for the Black Star Army, Luthor was a Beyond Grade A seed. They had never imagined that he would be killed so easily.

At this moment, one member of the upper echelons trembled, and his body was possessed.

In truth, this mysterious individual was the leader of the Limitless Financial Group, Sorokin. Despite being extremely busy, he had the ability to do a hundred things at once.

"It seems like our cooperation has to come to an end," Sorokin said slowly.

The Ancient Emperor Party leader was shocked. "You..."

"The reaction of the Black Star Army is far more intense than I expected. My original plan was only to probe and observe them, but the loss is out of my expectations. If we continue to work together, the cost required will be too great; this investment isn't worth it," Sorokin said calmly.

A Beyond Grade A seed was extremely rare, and Luthor's death truly made Sorokin feel a sense of heartache.

Sorokin did not know that Black Star already knew his identity. According to his plans, the Black Star Army was always going to react in some way, but he had never expected Black Star to send out the entire Black Star Guards.

As such, Sorokin's plan had failed. Although he was powerful, he could not possibly find Black Star personally for such a small matter, and he was not willing to sacrifice even more subsidiary organizations for a small experiment. Han Xiao's reaction had forced him to give up on the thought of probing the immortal troops.

His plan to test the immortal troops could only be delayed.

However, he was not someone who liked suffering a loss. Even though Black Star was not aware that Luthor was his subordinate, he was not planning to let the matter rest so easily.

Of course, Sorokin would not take revenge with force. The Arcane Church had already tried to do so and suffered a huge loss. He did not think that he would be able to match the Arcane Church in terms of high-level combatants.

However, history had proven that Black Star was an ambitious character, and Sorokin believed that Black Star would eventually have to face his Limitless Financial Group. This day might not be too long later as he was currently attempting to gain entry to the Flickering World.

Without waiting for a reply, Sorokin left the body.

The Ancient Emperor Party leader's face turned ashen.

...

A few months went by in a flash, and Han Xiao remained in the headquarters the entire time while observing the changes in the Gulal Civilization.

After the death of Luthor, the Limitless Financial Group retreated without any signs of fighting back.

The Limitless Financial Group wanted to hide their identity so that they would not be spotted by him. The Limitless Financial Group was a business organization and not an armed organization after all. As long as Han Xiao could make the other party pay a sufficient price, the other party would definitely give up.

Without any future reinforcements, the Ancient Emperor Party was dragged back into hell, and the civil war was controlled by the Black Star Army again.

Upon seeing that the Limitless Financial Group had given up on their attempt to probe the players, Han Xiao also stopped paying attention to the battle. As the players grew stronger, it would be inevitable for others to set their eyes on them.

The experience provided by the players was something that he needed to grow quickly, and this was a non-negotiable for him. If he did not take a hard stance, the other party would climb over his head.

After dealing with this little problem, Han Xiao turned his attention to something more important.

After a few months of seclusion, the sixteen-month experience penalty had finally ended!

Chapter 880: Thanks, Arcane Church

Han Xiao made a trip to the combat practice room and shut the door.

Taking in a deep breath, Han Xiao opened the interface.

The '40% Experience Penalty' status only had a few minutes left, and Han Xiao could not help but become excited as he watched the timer go down.

It hasn't been easy. Sixteen months...

Sixteen months ago, he had finally stepped into the realm of a Beyond Grade A Super.

In just a year and a half, he had fought Psyker to protect the Evolution Cube before having a duel with Heber. Following which, he had headed to the Crimson Dynasty's mother planet, where he was provoked by the allies of the dynasty again. Along the way, he fought EsGod once and met with his biggest crisis not too long ago.

He had only been a Beyond Grade A for a year and a half but had met with plenty of dangers. Han Xiao could not help but feel a sense of lingering fear as he looked back.

Thankfully, my quick-witted brain and handsome appearance resolved these dangers. Han Xiao praised himself shamelessly.

Dangers also brought him opportunities, and his status had now been cemented in place. Furthermore, his experience penalty was over.

Everything was getting better!

Han Xiao rubbed his palms with a look of joy on his face.

"I am now at level 260. I increased my level hastily to deal with the Arcane Church, which resulted in me spending forty percent more experience. With the experience that I accumulated over this period..." Han Xiao looked at his stash of experience, and his eyes sparkled. "I should be able to reach level 280."

At his current level, the experience required for every level was a sky-high figure.

Without the experience penalty and ignoring all Class Advancement missions, the experience required for him to level up once should be enough for a player to go from level 1 to 160. Furthermore, the amount of experience that he needed would only increase as his level went up.

If he did not have the players to harvest experience and only relied on missions for experience, he would probably take donkey's years to reach level 280.

The only reason he was able to accumulate enough experience to reach level 280 was because of the Political Asset. The combined effects of the Political Assets was like a double experience card.

It was truly frightening!

After lamenting for a while, the experience penalty status reached the last second and disappeared from his interface.

"The side effect of the Evolution Cube is finally gone."

Han Xiao rubbed the muscles on his body and felt the activity within the cells of his body. The way this side effect showed itself was the slow adaptation to the evolution of his genes. The more powerful an individual, the more energy contained within their cells and the longer the process needed for the conversion. At this moment, the slight tinge of discomfort within his cells had finally disappeared, and their evolution was complete.

The effect of the Evolution Cube is truly amazing, Han Xiao thought to himself. He had been in a rush to use the Evolution Cube so that he could reach Beyond Grade A quickly. The side effects of using the Evolution Cube did not come at the right time. Han Xiao naturally did not plan to only use the Evolution Cube once but would choose a better time to make use of it next time. The best time for him to use the Evolution Cube would be after he spent all his accumulated experience during the version update period.

However, that was still a long way away.

Han Xiao focused on his attribute interface and began to level up.

[Lord Mechanic] leveled up to Lv.2.

+360 Energy, +5 STR, +5DEX, +12 END, +15 INT.

You have received 12 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

[Lord Mechanic] leveled up to Lv.20.

+360 Energy, +5 STR, +5DEX, +12 END, +15 INT.

You have received 12 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

A warm surge of energy flowed through his body, and his energy level was upgraded.

As his experience stash went down, his level shot up and stopped at level twenty.

Every twenty levels, there was a Promotion Mission, and a notification popped up on his interface.

You have reached Lv.280. You have triggered the Promotion Mission [A Legend Takes Flight].

[A Legend Takes Flight]: Obtain 1 Universe Grade Legendary Point. Only the strong will write his own legends.

The moment this Promotion Mission popped up, it was already in a 'completable' state.

Upon looking at the mission, Han Xiao was overjoyed.

The Universe Grade Legendary Point was the highest grade, and his actions needed to shake the entire universe. A player had to complete a mission of extremely high difficulty or do something extremely ridiculous to obtain the Legendary Point. This Promotion Mission was already at the level of the later versions during the World Tree Civilization arc.

Even with Han Xiao's current status, it was not easy for him to obtain a Universe Grade Legendary Point.

However, Han Xiao did have a Universe Grade Legendary Point right now: Enemy of the Arcane!

Han Xiao's mouth contorted. Was it truly a blessing in disguise?

After roaming through the universe for so many years, he only had a single Universe Grade Legendary Point. It could be seen just how rare it was.

He did not have any Mission Completion Cards on hand, and he originally thought that he would be stuck at the Lv.280 Promotion Mission. Who would have thought that he would be lucky this time?

Han Xiao then burst into laughter.

Hehe, I really need to thank the Arcane Church for giving me a Legendary Point.

Right, I also need to thank Feidin...

Upon thinking about Feidin, Han Xiao's hands grew a little itchy.

This was a surprise that dropped from the sky, and Han Xiao chose to complete the mission without hesitation.

You have completed the Mission Requirements.

Lv.280 Promotion Mission completed.

+55 END, 1 END = 410 Health = 420 Stamina

Your Energy Rank has exceeded 52,000 Ona.

You have received the talent [Strengthened Elemental Resistance]!

You have received the talent [Optimized Energy Usage]!

You have received the talent [High Grade Life Vitality]!

You have acquired the skill [Mighty Prestige]!

The effects of all your Virtual Technology skills have been increased by 40%.

Han Xiao's eyes glowed with a blue bolt of lightning, and he spat out a cloud of bluish gas.

Since there was no race evolution this time, there was not much pain throughout the whole process.

He looked down to see if there were any changes to his body. From the outside, there were not many changes. He had grown slightly taller, and his muscles looked more toned.

He then felt his head itch slightly and grabbed a bunch of hair off from his head while scratching it.

"I'm shedding hair‽"

Han Xiao was shocked and immediately summoned his mirror to take a look, but after getting a clear look, he heaved a sigh of relief.

His Promotion stimulated his metabolism and improved the cell structure of his entire body. As such, his original hair fell out, and new hair grew out. However, the hair that had dropped was still stuck in his head, which explained why he felt the itch.

"Thankfully, my thick black hair is still around."

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief. For a moment, he thought that he had walked the evil path of exchanging his hair for power. The balder he got, the more powerful he would become.

The upper limit of the Lord Mechanic class was level 40, and he would complete his Class Advancement when he reached level 200. The next race evolution was also at level 300, and level 280 was just an ordinary Promotion in the middle.

However, 52,000 Ona seemed to be a stable boundary. Not all Beyond Grade As were able to reach 52,000 Ona, and the few talents that he had obtained felt like the basic abilities of a new realm.

After learning [Endless Material Science] and [Virtual Creator], his Energy Rank rapidly approached 52,000 Ona, and he finally broke through the boundary after increasing his level.

Han Xiao then looked at his new abilities and verified his guess.

Although he did not experience a race evolution, every Promotion was also an increase to his realm. Going past 52,000 Ona meant entering a new realm, and every life form that reached this realm would receive the same talents.

[Strengthened Elemental Resistance] boosted his attributes like [Perfect Mechanical Sense], and its multiplier was 1.25.

[Optimized Energy Usage] reduced the energy and stamina consumption of all his skills to 27%.

[High Grade Life Vitality] increased the upper limit of his health and recovery rate. His health increased by 17%, and his recovery rate increased by 120%.

These three talents strengthened his basic ability to take damage, which was something that all classes required.

The only skill, [Mighty Prestige], was a halo type ability that could be turned on and off. A life form at a higher realm was capable of emanating pressure, and this had turned into a skill.

The suppression would cover a certain region, and the individuals within the region would be affected by it, inflicting a negative status to reduce their attributes. However, it was only useful to life forms with intelligence, and certain life forms that were immune to mental skills were immune toward it, such as Mechanical Lives. It was useless against individuals of the same level.

After thinking for a while, Han Xiao concluded that the skill was completely useless apart from bullying noobs. But if he wanted to bully noobs, a Mechanic like him would not need a halo like this. He could just have a team fight.

The three talents that he had obtained were still much better.

Although this was only an ordinary Promotion, the increase to his strength was still pretty good.

His base Endurance boost was one Endurance point to 410 Health. The increase from his other abilities included an additional 60 from [Advanced Strengthened Life], 140 from [Eternal Body], 50 from Grade S boost, 10% health from [Extraordinary Physique], 17% health from [High Grade Life Vitality], and 100 health from [Well Trained].

For his Mechanical Force, he also had various different talents and skills to convert Intelligence to Machinery Affinity.

He then threw all his Free Attribute Points into Intelligence and looked at his attributes with satisfaction.

Level: 280

Main Class: Mechanic

Race: Black Star Race

Attributes: 3,347 STR, 4,080 DEX, 6,129 END, 9,029 INT, 2,950 MYS, 1,163 CHA, 1 LUK

Free Attribute Points: 0

Potential Point: 21

Health: 5,137,427

Stamina: 4,417,950

Energy: 89,320 [Lv.17]

Lv.17 Energy bonus stats: +1,206 STR, +1,488 DEX, +1,890 END, +2,345 INT, +1,123 MYS, +311,520 Stamina Limit, +1,632% Machinery Affinity

Energy Rank: 53,750

Grade: S+ (Beyond A)

Grade S Bonuses: +50 END, +25 All Resistances. +25% Highest Attribute, +15% Other Attributes, +750 Free Attribute Points, +50 Potential Points

The future of a Beyond Grade A is like a cloud of mist. Everyone is searching for their path and will meet many bottlenecks during their evolution process. Congratulations for going past the first bottleneck.

The remark is so solemn this time.

Han Xiao rubbed his muscles and tried to get used to the changes.

Now that he was at Grade S+, he was still considered Beyond Grade A despite the growth in his strength. His strength did not achieve such a huge change like when he went from the Calamity Grade to Beyond Grade A. Because there was no clear distinction between the combat strength of the Beyond Grade As and the grades within the Beyond Grade A realm being slowly figured out, the realm was segmented into mini realms.

Just like how everyone thought that the Calamity Grade was the upper limit of strength during the early days of the exploration era, the people now felt that Beyond Grade A was the limit of an individual's strength. EsGod wanted to break through the current limits just like the Primordial Ones did and raise his strength to a whole new realm.

After his promotion, the amount of experience required to level up increased yet again. Han Xiao knew that it would be impossible for him to save up enough experience to reach level 300 quickly. After all, he used the faction store to earn the players' experience, and even if he could earn experience quickly, he needed the time to accumulate it. Currently, the players had already learned plenty of knowledge, and the experience that they provided had begun to stagnate.

Han Xiao was not prepared to continue waiting. He had already been in seclusion for a few months, and it was better for him to get rid of EsGod as quickly as possible.

He had crafted many pieces of equipment that were made specially to deal with EsGod, and as long as the dynasty was willing to help him, he would have some confidence to kill EsGod.

"I haven't contacted the dynasty at all during this period. I wonder how matters are still unsettled between them and the Arcane Church. If they have come to an agreement already, they should have the capacity to deal with EsGod."

Han Xiao then took out his communicator and was about to ask about the dynasty's situation.

Right at this moment, Phillip suddenly appeared.

"Master, hum... Someone sent me an encrypted message just now."

"Sending an encrypted message to me? Decrypt it and see who sent it."

"I can't decrypt it alone; that's why I came to you."

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed. Phillip was a capable assistant, and since Phillip was unable to decrypt the information, it meant that the other party was not a simple individual. They had to be at the Star Cluster level at the very least.

"What is said in the encrypted message?"

"They said that they are the descendants of Spacetime Freezer and want to talk to you face to face."

Han Xiao was stunned, and his expression changed slightly.

When he was searching for information regarding the Spacetime Amber, he remembered the current state of the Spacetime Freezer race.

So... the Federation of Light is looking for me?

Since they have chosen to send the Spacetime Freezer race over, are they trying to hint to me that they are aware of the Spacetime Amber's origins?

Han Xiao then pondered for a moment before instructing, "Reply to them. I agree to meet them."

Chapter 881: Whereabouts

Phillip sent out a message and received a reply a few seconds later.

"Master, hum... They would like to meet you privately. You can decide the time and place."

"If that's the case..." Han Xiao contemplated.

This matter was a little sensitive since the Federation of Light had come to find him. However, Beyond Grade A allies were not subordinates of a Universal Civilization, and he had a certain degree of freedom and rights. Even if the dynasty knew about the meeting between them, it was not a big deal.

Han Xiao thought for a few seconds before saying, "Tell them that I don't accept a private meeting. I temporarily do not wish to have a 'shared secret' with them. Invite them over to the Black Star Army as guests. They can come if they are willing, but there isn't a need to meet them if they aren't."

The other party was the one who took the initiative to find him, and he did not do anything wrong. It would not be good for him to behave sneakily. Thus, he might as well invite them over to his territory openly. If not, it would seem as though he was concocting some secret plan with the Federation of Light, which would attract more misunderstandings.

The second mission of the Spacetime Amber was for him to come into contact with the descendants of Spacetime Freezer. Because the Federation of Light was protecting that race, Han Xiao had not completed the mission yet. But since the other party was taking the initiative to request a meeting, Han Xiao treated it as a small surprise, and it would save him quite a bit of energy.

However, he could not seem too anxious. Since the other party had taken the initiative to meet him, the rules would be set by him.

After sending out an invitation, the Federation of Light did not give a reply as though they were considering it.

Han Xiao was not too anxious. He then took out his communicator and called Tarrokov.

Tarrokov appeared, and he said with a smile, "Black Star, you have the time to contact me already?"

"Haha, chief commander, how are things recently?"

"Sigh, it's still the same as always. We are still eating dirt in the Flickering World. When will you come back to continue your exploration?"

"In a while."

"Hurry up then. The first exploration phase will end in a few years, and we will enter the construction phase. We will only start off our second exploration after digesting the territories of the three Star Clusters."

Han Xiao then chatted casually with the other party for a while before saying with a serious expression, "I haven't contacted the outside world during this period, and the negotiations should have been going on for a few months already. Has the dynasty reached an agreement with the Arcane Church?"

"There shouldn't be any problem." Tarrokov nodded. "Although both parties look like they are in conflict on the surface, they have already come to an agreement in private. The only thing that is left are the details of the agreement. The Arcane Church paid a heavy price in order to ransom their experts, but the exact figure is confidential. I can only say that the other party made huge concessions in military, economic, and political affairs. They also released some of their technological skills. In any case, the dynasty promised the Arcane Church to release three Beyond Grade As—Dylan, Taylor, and Mercer. Only Sagman is still in our hands as a bargaining chip."

Han Xiao nodded.

The foundation of a civilization was their people, and the conflicts between the civilizations were usually because of status and resources. Compared to the long history of a civilization, every Beyond Grade A was no more than a shooting star in a part of their history. Returning three Beyond Grade A captives in exchange for resources was a trade that the dynasty was extremely willing to do. At the same time, it could be said that the three Universal Civilizations were on the same tide. Despite having their own conflicts, it was impossible for any party to wipe out the others. Apart from their conflicts, it was also important for them to suppress the civilizations beneath them and maintain order.

"Right, how did they deal with the Spacetime Amber?" Han Xiao asked.

As the Arcane Church researched the Spacetime Amber, the name of the Spacetime Amber had spread throughout the universe, and every large organization was now aware of it. The two Universal Treasures in Black Star's hands were the Evolution Cube and Spacetime Amber. As such, Black Star had a special status in the universe.

"The Arcane Church isn't able to break the seal and wants to invite the dynasty to help them. The dynasty dragged the matter on and didn't contact you, so you are still unaware about it."

"Does the dynasty plan to agree to it?"

"Hmm, the Arcane Church is willing to pay the price, and the dynasty is going to ask you to unseal one of the captives. They also want you to make a trip to the Central Galaxy."

"Alright." Han Xiao nodded. The players now had the Gulal Civilization and Flickering World, so they were having the time of their lives. He would not need to interfere with the players until the end of Version 3.0, so he would be free.

Furthermore, he was also prepared to head to the Central Galaxy and find some helpers to deal with EsGod.

"I would like to ask, has the dynasty found EsGod yet?"

"We have found some clues. Some eyewitnesses claim to have seen the Fallen Ark at the Primeval Star River. The wormhole cluster in the Shattered Star Ring should have sent them there."

"As long as their whereabouts are known," Han Xiao said. "The Arcane Church has already given in, and the dynasty can only channel some manpower to deal with the accomplice EsGod."

Tarrokov observed Han Xiao's appearance and said with a smile, "I feel as though you are extremely determined to kill EsGod."

"That's right. He had been eyeing up the Evolution Cube for such a long time and almost took my life. Can I not hate him?" Han Xiao shrugged.

"This isn't the same." Tarrokov shook his head but did not continue.

It was not only because of the Evolution Cube. He felt that Han Xiao's enmity toward EsGod had a sense of urgency within it, as though EsGod posed a huge threat to him.

"In any case, the upper echelons have already sent out their forces to attack the Fallen Ark. EsGod isn't in his main camp. The dynasty plans to send manpower to kill him, and you are also on the list. Even if you don't ask, the upper echelons will find you regarding this matter."

"Alright, I will be there. I can participate in this mission during my trip to the Central Galaxy."

Han Xiao then chatted casually for a while more before hanging up.

As the final boss of the evil faction, EsGod had been able to avoid death.

The three Universal Civilizations had tried to deal with him many times before but were unable to kill him. It might be possible that the dynasty only treated killing EsGod as putting up a show.

He was probably the only one who resolutely wanted to kill EsGod.

I hope that history doesn't repeat itself, Han Xiao thought to himself.

If he could wipe out EsGod this time, he would be able to resolve the threat of the World Tree entering early.

It was not that Han Xiao did not have any confidence in the three Universal Civilizations. In his previous life, the three Universal Civilizations won a pyrrhic victory, so they might not be able to emerge victorious at the moment.

A few ferocious characters from the later versions had not grown up fully yet.

Especially the players.

Ding!

Right at this moment, Phillip received the reply from the Federation of Light indicating that they would accept his invitation.

...

On the other side, in the Federation of Light's Shattered Star Ring stronghold, Mona placed down his communicator. He was the emissary in charge of contacting Han Xiao this time and also a descendant of Spacetime Freezer. His skin was light blue with diamond-like crystals growing on it.

"Black Star has agreed to meet us," Mona reported to the upper echelons.

"Alright, remember your mission. First, you must probe Black Star's attitude. Second, you need to investigate the origins of the Spacetime Amber. If the probing isn't ideal, do not mention the trade. Also, do not make any unnecessary moves."

Mona nodded solemnly.

The Federation of Light wanted the seal on the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter to be undone, but Black Star was an ally of the dynasty. Thus, it was unlikely for him to help them. Without sufficient benefits, Black Star would not risk offending the dynasty to help them undo the seal.

Black Star was able to get most resources from the dynasty, and there was no need to make a deal with them. Thus, the Federation of Light can only probe to see if Black Star had any special requirements.

Even if the hope was slim, the Federation of Light would have to give it a try. Bader truly could not bear to just stare at a useless Ten Thousand Deity Scepter.

Since they had already offended the Arcane Church, they could not walk out without any benefits.

"I will not make any rash moves, but His Excellency Manison..." Mona then turned to look at a mechanical host beside him.

This was Manison's Lord's Descent host that was not activated yet. Manison's consciousness had not descended on it, and it was being controlled by AI from afar.

Upon hearing those words, Manison appeared through a long-distance projection.

"You don't need to bother about me. I will be paying Black Star a visit in a personal capacity and not interfere with your affairs."

Mona could only nod as he heard that. At his level, he did not have the right to control Manison.

Manison shook his head with a strange look on his face.

In truth, Manison had been looking forward to meeting Han Xiao for a long time. He paid close attention to all the Beyond Grade A Mechanics.

Black Star's name had resounded throughout the Beyond Grade A ranks in the universe, and he had long wanted to test Black Star's strength.

Only then would he know the price he had to pay for the Spacetime Amber.

Chapter 882: Meeting, Second Chain Mission Completed

After straightening his clothes and arranging his hairstyle, Han Xiao pushed open the door of the training room and walked out.

Outside the door was a silvery white corridor, with built-in lamps along the ceiling lighting the place with a white light. The corridor was ring-shaped, and on both sides were training rooms, with numbers engraved on the doors in black lettering. The suspended virtual screen on the side showed the user who was inside. This was a dedicated training place for the officers.

The satellite base in the headquarters was humongous, and it was divided into multiple bases. Where Han Xiao was located was the core area.

Han Xiao touched his stomach. Because he had just advanced, he was still full of energy, but he felt that he had consumed a lot of energy mentally. After thinking about it, he decided to head to the dining area to get himself a good meal. He was afraid that if he stuck to just eating nutrition packs every day, his taste buds would rot away sooner or later.

The dining area was a basic need of life. Furthermore, due to the diverse tastes of the various races, there were also chefs of various races.

Because of the size of the base, various anti-gravity suspension vehicles were used as modes of transport. They were all products of the logistics department. Within his 'home', Han Xiao would naturally not be so idle and choose to walk over. Thus, he searched for one of the vehicles and set a course for the dining area.

From afar, one could see the sea of people within the dining area. As one got closer, the din grew ever louder. No matter what time it was, the human traffic in the dining area would always be the highest.

Landing on the docking platform, Han Xiao stepped off the suspension vehicle and walked in. The army members who were idly chatting at the door after having their fill noticed Han Xiao's figure, and those leaning on the wall immediately stood upright.

"Army Commander, good day!"

"Oh, good day. Have you all eaten already?" Han Xiao nodded and greeted back casually.

Whenever he met his subordinates at the headquarters, he would definitely reply. His airs were projected only for the outsiders, and he was more casual and friendly toward his people.

Upon entering the wide hall of the dining area, many pairs of eyes immediately glanced over. The atmosphere quietened for a moment, and many of them showed a face of emotion as they hurriedly got up and saluted. Some remained sitting as they ate, only raising their head to curiously size up Han Xiao.

Following the expansion of the Black Star Army, many of the new members had never even seen their leader once. Han Xiao also did not typically appear in public areas, choosing to stay within the core areas, thus his image in the members' minds grew more and more mysterious.

Furthermore, the event of Enemy of the Arcane had given an additional halo around Han Xiao, causing his reputation to constantly rise. His image only grew bigger in the eyes of his members.

Every large organization would have internal faction disagreements, and it was the same with the Black Star Army. With its current size, the factions had also become more obvious, where different races and tribes all formed their own small pockets. Only Han Xiao was able to completely suppress all of them. As long as he was present, the army was truly unified.

"Don't mind me, just continue eating." Han Xiao helplessly waved his hands. This was the reason why he did not like to show himself.

Every time he strolled around within the base, he would seem like an inspector going about his rounds. What a lonely life.

"Teacher, here, here!" This time, Han Xiao heard a familiar voice. Turning his head, he saw Sylvia waving toward him. She was having her meal with Aroshia.

Han Xiao walked to the seat facing hers and sat down. He then picked up a drumstick from his tray and took a bite. The meat was tender and juicy, full of substance and stimulating to his taste buds. After chewing a few times, an even stronger fragrance was emitted.

"The taste is pretty good. We should raise the salary of the chefs here." Han Xiao finished his drumstick in two or three bites. He licked the corners of his mouth, savoring the last bit of taste, and he started to pick at the other dishes. "Remember to grant funds to the canteen department as well to research a new flavor of the nutrition fluid."

"I get it. You really love the nutrition fluids." Sylvia grunted as she cut into her vegetables.

"Eating a meal requires ten minutes, but drinking a tube of nutrition fluid only needs three seconds. I like the more efficient method. Learn from me, sister," Han Xiao joked.

I'm the one in charge of miscellaneous tasks, and you have more time than me. What sort of time are you trying to save? Sylvia rolled her eyes, going back to her meal feeling depressed.

Han Xiao then turned toward Aroshia. "How have you been?"

"Ah owh..." Aroshia did not raise her head, fully focused on the mountain of food in front her. Her face was expressionless, her cheeks moving like a chipmunk as she quickly chewed. The amount of food in front of her was almost ten times Sylvia's.

She had known Sylvia for a long time, and their relationship was pretty good. However, because Aroshia's combat abilities could no longer match Han Xiao's tempo, she was unable to move out on operations together with him. However, she still had a special position within the army due to her experience and popularity due to her looks. She was the crush of countless army members and had even attracted a group of fans from the players.

Because of the [Reboot] mission, Han Xiao did not wish to come into contact with Aroshia and Risda too often. At this level, ruining any chance of a relationship with the Mechanic Empire over this small issue was not worthwhile. Risda had always been pestering him, but Han Xiao currently did not have any idea how to approach this issue. His current level did not allow him to have that sort of ability.

"That's right. Since you're already here, I don't need to send out the news." Han Xiao spoke to Sylvia. "In the next few days, someone from the Federation of Light will pay me a visit. Please arrange for it."

Sylvia was startled, raising her head. "Teacher, you're allied to the dynasty. Seeing someone from the Federation of Light isn't too good."

"They asked to meet me first. At least I have to listen to what they have to say."

As Han Xiao was explaining, he suddenly got interrupted by a voice behind him.

"Black Star, I... I have something for you!"

Han Xiao turned around, only to see a male player with his ID above his head standing behind him, holding something black in his hands.

Yet another guy who thinks giving gifts will brush up my favorability...

Because the players treated him as an NPC, they thought that their favorability with him would increase when he was given gifts. Han Xiao was resigned to this.

Every time he showed himself, someone would try this method. He had long gotten used to it.

After receiving the gift, it turned out to be a slightly rare mineral.

Honestly, Han Xiao did not understand why people would send him minerals. Did they think he could not afford it‽

Gazing at the face full of expectation, the corners of Han Xiao's mouth twitched, and he endured the impulse to lower that guy's favorability, merely forcing out a smile. "Thank you."

The player waited for a while but did not see any notification about an increase in favorability. He scratched his head, looking at the rare mineral in Han Xiao's hands, his expression regretful.

"Um, can I take back my gift?"

Han Xiao's expression turned black.

Brother, you're being too stingy.

"No."

"Sigh, I lost out." The player still did not give up, however. "Is there anything you would like me to do?"

No, scram!

Of course, this was only said within his heart. He would not be so rude to the players.

"... I currently have nothing for you to deal with. If you are free, how about you proceed to the Gulal Civilization and join the war there or help with the exploration in the Flickering World? There should be something for you to do."

Han Xiao smiled innocently but with the hidden meaning of asking the player to go f*ck himself.

"Alright then..." The player left with an expression of pity and regret.

To prevent himself from being mobbed by the players, he quickly finished his meal and left the dining area as though he was flying. He went to the logistics department next to check up on Nero's studies.

[Perfect Mechanical Sense] was a Molding Talent that he had desired for a long time, so he paid a lot of attention to Nero's progress.

Reaching the logistics department, Han Xiao walked into Reynold's office and saw Nero sprawled over a table full of books.

After drinking the dragonblood potion, not only did it energize the mind, it also rejuvenated the body. Thus, Nero's little face appeared healthy. However, his expression was bitter as though he had swallowed a pile of herbs. His face was so scrunched up that it looked as though it was about to be compressed into a single point, and he wrote as though he wished to pierce his entire pen into the textbook.

"Little Nero, your godfather is here to see you." Han Xiao smiled as he walked over.

Nero did not even look at Han Xiao. He turned his head, his expression one of grumpiness.

Han Xiao turned to Reynold. "How's his progress?"

"The dragonblood potion is very useful and has saved him the time needed to sleep. His progress is also extremely fast, and he will be able to start learning the introductory theory soon. I plan to add in some practical machinery classes in the next stage of his study plan." Reynold's tone was serious.

Hearing that, Nero's hand trembled, and the pen dropped onto the table with a 'clack' sound. His entire bearing appeared to have been frozen stiff.

Han Xiao smirked.

You're truly a devil...

This time, the door opened again, and Feidin, clad in loose blue robes, walked in. Seeing Han Xiao, he was surprised but revealed a warm smile. "Black Star, you're here as well."

"What are you here for?" Han Xiao's brows rose.

"I'm here to see Nero." Feidin laughed. "And to play some cards with him."

Nero immediately threw himself into Feidin's bosom, as though he had met his savior. He conveniently turned back and stuck his tongue out toward Han Xiao.

"Cough cough, Feidin comes to play cards with Nero every now and then. That's his free time," Reynold explained.

Han Xiao had an amazed expression on his face, as though asking, You actually will give him time to play?

"Er... once every half a month."

Oh, I was wrong.

Since it was rare to have any playtime, Nero excitedly took out the Wayne Cards and pulled on Feidin's sleeves to begin. Feidin smiled and took out his cards leisurely, beginning to battle with Nero.

Seeing this situation, Han Xiao's brows twitched. He felt that Feidin was very fond of Nero. Could it be that Feidin and Chen Xing were unable to produce children?

While Han Xiao did not enjoy playing cards, he knew the rules well. Standing by the side, he could not help but suck in a deep breath.

Was this the so-called battle between two lucky stars?

He seemed to see the Goddess of Fortune playing against herself, fighting on both sides!

Seeing Nero's practiced hand movements, Han Xiao felt a little heartache.

My little cub... in the end, you have still been infected by Hadavy and Herlous.

Seems like I need to correct this.

Han Xiao endured his laughter as he threw a [Luck Curse] toward Nero. He shook his head and stealthily left the scene.

Over the next few days, Han Xiao took the time to adapt to his newly increased strength and also cleared a few miscellaneous tasks, preparing for the meeting with the Federation of Light.

The spaceship landed at the headquarters of the Black Star Army, and Mona led a group of people off the spaceship. They were led to a reception room under the guidance of the reception robot.

Seated at the reception room, Han Xiao waited for a moment before the doors opened, and the emissary team from the Federation of Light appeared. They greeted each other before taking their seats.

"The Federation of Light's Advanced Combatant Team Sergeant, Mona." Mona gave a simple introduction.

Sensing that the other party was a Calamity Grade, Han Xiao opened the interface panel to take a look. Indeed, after being in contact with someone belonging to the tribe of Spacetime Freezer, the mission of the Spacetime Amber showed a change.

The Second Chain Mission of [The Primordial Ones' Inheritance - Spacetime Freezer] has been completed!

+1 Soul Connection with the Spacetime Amber.

Spacetime Amber: Current Soul Connection 2/5

The Spacetime Amber has gotten closer to you.

The buff 'Blessing of the Spacetime Amber' has been refreshed.

[Blessing of the Spacetime Amber (Lv.2)]: +15% Maximum Energy, +120 STR, +120 DEX, +120 END, +240 INT, +50 MYS, +50 CHA. In addition, +70% Basic Space Resistance, +30% Basic Psychological Resistance. The effect of all your spacetime related abilities are increased by 18% – 32%.

Buff Duration: Permanent

Han Xiao was overjoyed but did not show it on his face. With an increased connection to the Spacetime Amber, he had also developed a closer feeling to the amber, and from his senses, the Spacetime Amber seemed to have transformed into something that he had used for a long time.

This meant that his efficiency in creating the amber balls would also increase. However, he was now in a meeting with people and was unable to test it out.

Han Xiao glanced at the third series of the chain mission.

Third Chain Mission Requirements: Proceed to the ancestral land of the Spacetime Freezer, and take his body to visit his homeland.

Okay, so this is not a coincidence any longer... Han Xiao murmured to himself internally.

The ancestral land of the Spacetime Freezer was located within the territory of the Federation of Light. If he wished to complete the third mission, he had to personally make a visit. After all, it was impossible for the other party to bring the entire planet to him.

Closing his interface, Han Xiao cut to the chase. "The Federation of Light has few dealings with me. May I ask for your purpose in visiting me?"

"It's like this. The Federation of Light is curious about your Spacetime Amber," Mona said with a straight face. "After checking our records, we found out that the Spacetime Amber seems to have some relation with one of the Beyond Grade As in our history."

"Oh, there was such a thing?" Han Xiao feigned surprise, but he was actually shocked. To think that the Federation of Light even held secret records relating to the Spacetime Freezer and even made such an informed guess.

As for the Federation of Light expressing their interest in the Spacetime Amber, he did not find that surprising. Basically every single organization in Galaxy was curious about his two Universal Treasures and were probably researching them.

"Do you know about the Spacetime Freezer?" Mona asked.

Han Xiao had to put on a show, and thus, after a while, he nodded, his expression unchanging as he replied, "Let me check."

"Oh, now I know. What you mean is that the Spacetime Freezer and the Spacetime Amber are related, right?"

Mona had been observing Han Xiao's expression but could not deduce anything, so he could only continue the conversation.

"We cannot confirm this either, so it is only a hypothesis. I am one of the descendants related to the Spacetime Freezer, so I requested for the Federation of Light to help me get into contact with you to understand the origin of the Spacetime Amber."

"Why should I care about the history of the Spacetime Amber? How does that benefit me?"

Han Xiao raised his brows, but he was clear of the answer himself.

The reason the Federation of Light did this was because he could be considered to have picked up this Universal Treasure by luck and did not understand its history. Thus, the Federation of Light sent Mona as a descendant of the Spacetime Freezer to contact him and search for his ancestor's traces. However, the Federation of Light knew that Han Xiao would not buy this reason and thus only used it to get closer to him.

"Rest assured. Because this involves the ancestor of our entire race, the Federation of Light is only helping us to investigate it and add information of this new Universal Treasure into the public database. We have no other plans regarding your Spacetime Amber," Mona explained.

"I believe you." Han Xiao had on a straight expression. "Really."

Chapter 883: Breaking the Ice and Setting Conditions

Mona could hear Han Xiao's sarcasm in his tone, and his face turned red, but he persevered. "In short, we hope that you will allow us to investigate the Spacetime Amber. The Federation of Light will definitely give you satisfactory compensation."

"I refuse." Han Xiao waved his hand. "I'm not obliged to cooperate."

"Then... could you allow us to take a look at the Spacetime Amber? This is a personal request of mine."

"Nope."

The atmosphere grew a little stiff. However, Mona had expected it. Black Star would naturally not allow any outsiders to come into contact with his Universal Treasures.

He pretended to take a sip from his drink, glancing left and right, before suddenly lowering his voice and changing the topic.

"Your Excellency Black Star, I'm not sure... but what do you think of the Federation of Light?"

They are finally further probing my attitude... Han Xiao thought.

"My thoughts... I should be asking you this question instead. You helped the Arcane Church during the Battle of Planet Lighthouse, and then you turned around to aid the dynasty. I'm not sure whether I should consider you guys as enemies or friends. What do you think?"

Mona thought about it before solemnly replying, "While we belong to different factions, we are very willing to befriend you, Your Excellency Black Star."

Han Xiao raised his brows. "In that case, let me be more direct. We'll always be opponents from different factions, but we can be business partners. You won't object to that, right?"

"Of course." This was one of the conditions given by the upper echelons before he set off, so Mona did not hesitate.

The three Universal Civilizations had always warred against each other; however, they also traded with each other frequently, cooperating in many industries. In this interstellar era, so long as the civilizations did not tear off all pretenses and go to war with each other, their cooperative relationship would still be maintained. The three universal civilizations were already used to this method, and in fact, interstellar integration was one of the points that bound all galactic civilizations together as this magnified the cost of them being isolated.

Thus, in terms of business and trade, a Universal Civilization would not prohibit their Beyond Grade A allies from expanding their business to profit off other civilizations. However, if they were to use the name of commerce to sell secret information to other parties, then the universal civilization would hunt them down.

However, the Beyond Grade A allies in each civilization would not easily allow outsiders to obtain a share of their pie. If one wished to develop a business in other factions, they would be pressured by the organizations of that faction. Without an official relationship, it would be hard to conduct business.

"I'm sure that you're clear about our working style. Within the three Universal Civilizations, we are the most inclusive. We welcome financial groups and organizations from all over the universe to develop, and since the Shattered Star Ring is under the jurisdiction of the Federation of Light, you could say that we've always been working together," Mona said.

Han Xiao nodded. This part was true. The Crimson Dynasty was iron-blooded, while the Arcane Church leaned toward the spiritual side. The Federation of Light was undoubtedly the richest, with lots of territory and blooming with prosperity.

"Since you wish to be friends, then at least show some sincerity. Building a relationship requires funds." Han Xiao smiled.

"If you're willing, we can help the Black Star Army to develop their business in the Federation of Light at any time," Mona replied.

Han Xiao's eyes shifted quickly.

He roughly understood what the Federation of Light was trying to do. They first mentioned the Spacetime Amber before offering a trade cooperation. The situation was very clear. They wished to borrow the Spacetime Amber in the long run. After the previous incident, their relationship was strained, so one could imagine their success rate if they came knocking to request something.

Thus, the Federation of Light made a few proposals, of which one of them would be to use a business proposal to first break the ice, warming up their relationship before proposing a future follow-up relationship. In this way, they would not attempt to achieve their goals overnight but utilize a long-term relationship to obtain what they wanted.

As the requested party, Han Xiao had the advantage, and of course, he did not need to reply immediately.

"Ok, we'll talk about this again. I don't currently have that intention."

"Understood. If you still have any other requests, we'll do our best to consider it. No matter what, the Federation of Light looks forward to working with you."

Mona retained his sincere tone; the Federation of Light was not in a hurry to unseal the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. They could afford to wait.

"Other requests..." Han Xiao's eyes moved as he thought. He suddenly smiled. "I personally am not adverse to befriending the Federation of Light. It's just that because you helped the Arcane Church go against me last time, in addition to your sincerity, I feel you should display an apology."

He was referring to the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device. That time, the Federation of Light did not expect that they would need to request something from Black Star and could be said to have dug a hole for themselves. However, if they did not do so, then they probably would not have been able to obtain the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter. There were both advantages and disadvantages.

Mona's eyes lit up. He was not afraid of Han Xiao making a request but more afraid of him not having any.

"What are you thinking about?"

"It's like this. If you could do me a favor, I'll forgive you, and only through resolving this then can our relationship truly begin."

"What do you need?" Mona sat up straight.

"EsGod also took part in the battle of Planet Lighthouse, and the dynasty has been busy with capturing those from the Arcane Church. However, they have now turned their attention toward this accomplice. I have quite a huge grudge with EsGod, and if you could help the dynasty and I with encircling the EsGod and killing him, we can wipe off all other issues and start on a clean slate. What do you think?" Han Xiao's tone grew solemn.

Mona was a little surprised. He was expecting Han Xiao to raise up some benefits for himself, but to think that he actually invited them to hunt down EsGod. It seemed like their enmity was quite serious.

"In this regard, I have no way to make a decision. I will report this upward." Mona spoke truthfully. "But from my experience, there is a high chance that they will agree."

If it was something else, the Federation of Light would still hesitate, but dealing with the EsGod had always been one of the priorities and would also benefit them.

At this moment, one of the mechanical guards from behind stepped forward and took off its helmet. It revealed the head of a mechanical host, and an electronic voice sounded from its mouth.

"Regarding this matter, I can do it for you instead."

Hearing this, Han Xiao turned around. Seeing the material of the mechanical host, his eyes lit up. He could tell that the host had high technological content, seemingly a high levelled machine made by a Beyond Grade A, much like the mechanical host that he utilized for [Lord's Descent].

"You are..."

"'Mechanic Emperor' Manison, the Ancient One, Palpatine[1]."

Han Xiao's eyes changed, revealing a wary look.

Because the [Lord's Descent] was not yet used on the mechanical host, there were no fluctuations of a Beyond Grade A coming from it. Before Manison spoke, he had still thought it was just a normal mechanical soldier. In terms of stealth, Manison truly had the advantage.

The fact that Manison had chosen to approach him was out of Han Xiao's expectations.

A person's reputation was akin to the shadow a tree cast. The reputation of the Mechanic Empire in the universe was profound, almost universally regarded as the peak of mechanics. Furthermore, he had indirectly interacted with the other party before, so Han Xiao was vigilant of the name Mechanic Empire.

Mona coughed before explaining, "When His Excellency Manison heard that we were coming to pay you a visit, he requested to move together with us."

"Black Star, in actual fact, I've always been wanting to pay you a visit. This time was just a good opportunity." Noticing Han Xiao's furrowed brows, Manison spoke without any emotions. "What, am I not welcome?"

Han Xiao's thoughts revolved quickly, and he immediately smoothed his brows over, putting on another smile as he calmly replied.

"Of course not. I just felt it to be a coincidence. I also heard of your name a long time ago and have always wished to pay you a visit. It's just that I've never been able to find the chance to."

Mona stood up at this time. "This is my communicator number. Your Excellency Black Star, I'll report your intentions to the upper echelons, and you'll receive a reply soon. I won't disrupt your conversation any longer. Your Excellency Manison, we'll wait for you aboard the spaceship."

Manison's mechanical host nodded, and Mona left the room, following Phillip's directions back to the dock.

Only Manison and Han Xiao were left in the room.

"Hehe, Your Excellency Black Star, this should be our first time meeting." Manison sounded as though he was laughing, but the electronic voice did not display a single bit of emotion, making it a little frightening.

With the skills of the other party, it was possible for his host to completely mimic a person's emotions and tone, so this voice should be done on purpose.

"To be accurate, we're not considered 'meeting' yet. You've seen my face, but I still have not seen yours." Han Xiao raised a brow and spoke some mischievous words while he thought of Manison's intentions in coming here today.

It was normal for people of the same profession to converse, but he felt that Manison had a reason for visiting.

"There will definitely be a chance in the future." The mechanical host pointed toward its chest. "Do you mind if I send my consciousness over?"

Han Xiao shook his head to indicate his answer.

Boom!

The next instant, a surge of energy surged through the quantum infinite distance transmission channel, and the host's body jolted. Golden electricity spilled out from it, sizzling as Manison utilized [Lord's Descent].

The movements of the carrier instantly became a lot smoother. Manison twisted his neck, commenting, "That's much better."

Remote communication could be compared to doing a video chat. [Lord's Descent] was bringing one's consciousness into the scene, a lot more immersive.

Han Xiao smiled and did not speak, but he was full of awe in his heart.

When Manison's consciousness arrived, the mechanical force released by the host was so huge that it gave Han Xiao some pressure. To be able to allow another Beyond Grade A to feel pressure, the Mechanic Emperor was indeed unfathomable.

In all the Beyond Grade As he had seen, only EsGod's aura could be compared with Manison's... and this was only the host utilizing [Lord's Descent], not Manison's true body.

Just what level had this guy actually reached?

Thinking about it, Han Xiao tilted his mouth toward the door.

"Your Excellency Manison, how about we change locations?"

"Sure. Could you show me around your Black Star Army?" Manison nodded.

"Alright."

The two stood up and left the room while chatting.

They had only just met, so they did not talk about any sensitive topics but rather revolved around different topics such as about the headquarters, materials and technology used, and so on.

Han Xiao kept vision of the quantum network constantly active, letting Phillip maintain constant surveillance on the system.

While the possibility was low, it was better to guard against any secret Virtual Intrusion from Manison. After all, having Manison there was just like having the neighbor next door come to visit one's house. One could never know when one might be 'cucked', so it was better to deter than to resolve.

But Manison did not have such intentions. He was only focused on conversing about mechanical knowledge, as though they were really sharing technology between peers.

Just based on his technical exchanges, the Mechanic Emperor was indeed powerful. He had accumulated experience for many years and had collected all the mechanic profession knowledge. He was even at the forefront of technological innovation, having developed an unknown number of blueprints.

Just based on the main profession level, his was far off from Manison's. The other party had not lived so many years in vain.

Because this was the first time he was dealing with the Mechanic Emperor, Han Xiao constantly wore a smile on his face. However, he never lowered his guard. In addition to the preconceived notions, he also had to take into account the identity of the other party.

"Oh right, you mentioned just now that you would help me to deal with EsGod."

"EsGod is currently in the Primeval Star River. That is my base camp, and if the Federation of Light agrees to your request, it will be me who acts." Manison turned to look at Han Xiao. "Naturally, I also have my own reasons."

"What are they?" Han Xiao was curious.

"The first, I warned EsGod before that he was not allowed to wander into my territory. As for the second... hehe, I hope to obtain something from you." Manison did not bother hiding his intentions.

Obtain something from me? Han Xiao's eyes flashed. It would naturally not be his machinery, so it would most likely be the Universal Treasures. Was it the Evolution Cube or the Spacetime Amber?

However, Manison did not continue talking and only turned his head to another direction. At this moment, both of them had walked into a passageway, and surrounding them were combat training rooms.

"Since we're here, why not have a spar?" It was hard to tell what Manison was trying to do.

"Here?" Han Xiao shook his head. With our strength, we'll flip my headquarters upside down.

"Relax, I didn't bring any other mechanical units, only this host." Manison waved his hands. "You can control another host as well, and we'll stop when hit. This way, the movements are more controlled, and we will not harm our relations."

This method works... Han Xiao breathed in deeply and nodded. "... Alright then."

Since there was no need to fight with one's true body, it would be simple to repair the mechanical host afterward. It would also be safer this way. Han Xiao suspected that Manison wished to test out his combat strength based on his Mechanical Force.

Having broken through the 52,000 Energy limit, this level of Mechanical Force would not allow him to be easily abused by others. Han Xiao had the confidence to spar.

Moreover, [Lord's Descent] would also allow him to share the majority of his strength. He wished to also sneak a peek at Manison's attributes through the combat information.

[1] This used to be Papachi, but we're changing it to Palpatine from now on. Back

Chapter 884: Probing and Surprise

The two of them chose a combat training room at random. Swiping his identification, the doors automatically opened for them.

There were also differences in the configurations of the combat training rooms. Only the high-configuration combat training rooms would be able to handle a stronger aftermath.

The ordinary training rooms were free for most army members and players to utilize. They could withstand the impact of a Grade B Super at most. If one wished to use a higher configuration combat room, then they had to pay the rent. According to a member's status within the army, there would be different discounts attached, and the players would use the training room to brush up their skills and experience.

The core area was equipped with the highest-level training rooms, but even then, they could only withstand most Calamity Grade attacks, and a Beyond Grade A attack would be pushing it. However, if they only were using a single host for a spar, so long as they controlled the attack power, there should not be a problem.

This top training room had a lot of space, and the ground and walls were all pure white, displaying a grid-like appearance. The material was a synthetic form of a tough alloy with polymer and plastic nanomaterials, which had a self-repair function. With a virtual reality coating applied to it, it was able to simulate different environments.

At the same time, the walls and floor were movable to change the shape of the room to match the virtual environment. This could create a battlefield environment for further immersiveness, else it would be difficult to deceive one's senses.

Of course, the battlefield simulation was not child's play, and Han Xiao had specifically forbidden the players in the guidelines of usage for training rooms from occupying the training room to be spectators.

Han Xiao allowed Phillip to randomize the environment, and the appearance of the ground and walls rapidly changed, turning into a lush forest. In the distance was an endless forest and a mountain shrouded in mist. The training room even simulated the realism of a light breeze, with the coolness of early morning rain. One could even smell the fresh air and mud, as though they were truly present.

Surveying the scene, Manison murmured emotionally, "Being with machinery every day, all I see are dull colors. Sometimes, I forget what the great outdoors look like."

Han Xiao opened his secondary dimension and withdrew a mechanical host. The streamlined human body shape was painted with the three colors of silver, black, and yellow. This was a 'Mammoth' mechanical host, updated to the RX002 Generation. Compared to the RX001 Generation, the performance was slightly different.

The Mammoth RX001 Generation was designed as a standard model with comprehensive capabilities and balanced in every respect, while the RX002 focused on reducing the volume of the skeletal structure and nano tendons. It sacrificed a portion of strength in exchange for amplified flexibility and more mechanical weapons, making it more suitable to combat.

The effect of [Lord's Descent] would vary based on the basic configuration of the host. Different hosts thus possessed different abilities and attributes when using [Lord's Descent], so it was necessary to build various types of mechanical hosts.

Han Xiao activated [Lord's Descent], and blue-gold Mechanical Force shot out, colliding with the mechanical host, bursting into an eye piercing gleam!

Buzz!

His consciousness was divided into two. One stayed within the main body, whereas the other controlled the mechanical host.

Han Xiao's true body flew up high, not participating in this battle. He controlled the host to stand opposite Manison. While they were separated by a few hundred meters, this distance was as good as non-existent at their current level.

Han Xiao eyed the host's interface. Because of the First Gen Black Star Alloy, the host had several meat shield talents, coupled with high resistance. It possessed a power amplification of 64%, flexibility of 81%, and stamina amplification of 73%.

Han Xiao twisted his neck around within the Mammoth, adapting to it. Afterward, its back armor split open, releasing micro disks to form a suspended defense array. Various psionic cannon muzzles extended out from the shoulder, chest, and abdomen areas, and it lifted the left arm in a shield holding gesture as a psionic shield formed. A metal wrist-guard was fitted on the right forearm, and it held on to a mechanical blade wrapped with energy on the right hand.

Seeing this, Manison's host also entered battle mode. It turned on the floating array, activating the psionic shield, and took out a mechanical weapon that looked like a staff, shifting to a lowered position.

Utilizing [Lord's Descent] to spar was equivalent to remote controlled combat. Even if the hosts fought brutally, there would be no losses to their bodies.

Without further words, both sides exchanged glances for two seconds before their figures blurred and viciously slammed into each other!

Bang!

The huge impact created a shock wave, felling the trees around them under the effect of realistic destruction. Even Han Xiao, who was in the sky above, had his hair completely blown askew.

The next instant, both hosts turned into a single blurry image as they flashed through the woods. The mechanical blade and staff collided thousands of times in a short period, causing sparks, electricity arcs, and lights to flash.

Dang dang dang!

The sound of wind, rain, and metal striking all entered one's ear.

Mechanical Force collided with each other face to face, exploding into arcs in front of both hosts. Wherever it landed, grooves were created, holes were bored, and trees were set ablaze.

Both of them engaged in melee combat tacitly and controlled their strength, not utilizing their strongest weapons such as the long-range cannons, or else the training room would definitely be blasted to pieces.

They were only sparring, so they did not use their trump cards. There was no need to determine a winner because a mechanic's true prowess lay in their mechanical army.

Both of them only had intentions to probe the other, seeking to understand the other party through battle. Whoever obtained more intelligence about the other would be the one benefitting.

As they battled, Manison was sensing Han Xiao's Mechanical Force intensity.

At his level, as long as he opened his senses, he could roughly pinpoint Han Xiao's current standards. While the intensity could not compare to his, he still got a surprise when faced with Han Xiao's battle strength.

He had heard of how Han Xiao had captured Dylan, and based on his hypothesis, Black Star should be similar to him, possessing the top-level Mechanical talent.

However, in reality when they crossed arms, Manison discovered that Black Star's Mechanical Force was not as strong as expected, and he did not have the top-level abilities of a mechanic.

However, Han Xiao's life level was much higher than he expected. Manison naturally knew of the first limit one would face at the 52,000 Energy Rank. Just crossing this limit was nothing to him, but the problem was how long Black Star had been a Beyond Grade A.

Black Star had only reached the Beyond Grade A level a year and half ago. In just this short of a time, he had crossed the first limit.

The time taken for a Beyond Grade A to undergo a life level transformation was typically measured in decades!

Such unbelievable growth was a first for Manison, despite his age!

Such potential and talent...

Such an astounding growth rate made referencing Black Star's current combat prowess useless.

Since he knew that Black Star had already broken through the first limit, Manison felt that he had already achieved his objective. He thought that he had profited from this exchange, since Black Star would only know that he was strong but not to what extent.

Thinking about this, he clashed once more, taking advantage of the shockwave to pull apart. Manison then put his weapon away as he said, "Let's stop here, or else the room will be destroyed."

Han Xiao also stopped. Eyeing the various gorges and grooves within the training room, he too sheathed his weapon.

His true body descended and cancelled the [Lord's Descent]. After storing his mechanical host, he let out a smile.

"Indeed, Mechanic Emperor. You're really strong."

"I must say, your abilities exceeded my expectations." Manison nodded as well.

Han Xiao smiled but did not reply, instead changing the topic. "We've already toured the headquarters. Let's go to my office. We can continue talking about the problem of EsGod there."

"Okay."

The two of them left the training area, and on the way, Han Xiao snuck a peak at the interface whilst chatting.

Manison's level was displayed as ???, which meant that the disparity between them was not small. The majority of his attributes and skills were also displayed as ???, as there were many skills that he had not used during the spar.

A mechanic's skills were infamously numerous, with many of them overlapping with each other and could be ignored. As for those that Manison had displayed in the spar, Han Xiao noticed two Molding Talents.

The first was [Perfect Mechanical Sense], which was within Han Xiao's expectations. To be able to reach the peak of the mechanic profession, Manison had to have such a talent.

The second was [Virtual Technology Innovation—Manison]. His name at the back meant that this was a Molding Talent that he himself had developed. The effect was to strengthen his Virtual Technology with an enhancement coefficient of 1.75.

While it looked lackluster compared to the strengthening coefficient of 2.5 provided by [Virtual Lord], the meaning for both skills was completely different. As long as any mechanic learned the Ultimate Knowledge [Virtual Creator], they would gain this expertise, but [Virtual Technology Innovation—Manison] was an exclusive ability, which provided an extra bonus to him. This meant that Manison had a huge advantage in virtual technology, and it was thus classified as a Molding Talent.

Furthermore, the introduction of this talent said, "After utilizing Virtual Technology Innovation, there will be special effects." This was probably referring to the core specialty of Manison's strongest mechanic troops, the Indestructible Mechanic Empire.

Manison would naturally not only possess two Molding Talents, but only these two were displayed so far.

However, based on the combat information, as well as the performance of Manison in his previous life, Han Xiao had come out with a rough estimation of Manison's battle strength.

His main profession should out-level me by at least one stage, and he should have at least four Molding Talents. In addition, his Mechanical army should outnumber mine by several thousand times... How scary. I'd better not provoke him.

Overall, Han Xiao was quite satisfied with the spar. In the intelligence area, he had definitely benefited.

The combat information had displayed some of the abilities that Manison did not display, but Manison had no interface, so whatever ability he did not display, Manison would naturally be unaware. Displaying his life level was in fact a ploy of Han Xiao's to show off his potential so that Manison would not slight him.

Because of the presence of Character Summon Cards, there was misinformation on Han Xiao's combat strength. For example, he did not display [Perfect Mechanical Sense], which caused discrepancies to appear in Manison's intelligence gathering.

The Mechanic Emperor had chosen the wrong opponent to probe this time.

The corners of Han Xiao's mouth rose slightly.

...

Both parties had their own inner monologue as they returned to the office.

After sitting down, Manison began to talk about his purpose.

"My reason for meeting you this time is also to see if you're welcome to the idea of making a transaction."

"Please speak."

"I'm actually very interested in your Spacetime Amber. From what I know, this Universal Treasure can create copies of itself. I hope to buy a few pieces from you as research material."

Turns out, he wanted to buy the amber balls...

Han Xiao was silent as he thought for a while before shaking his head.

"Apologies, but I don't intend to sell them outside at all."

The Spacetime Amber was one of his trump cards, and the reason he had given Austin one was to repay his debt. He did not wish to use this to gain the support of others. This item was different from the Evolution Cube; he did not wish to allow the amber balls to circulate around the universe and be utilized by others.

He was not even willing to provide them to the Crimson Dynasty, let alone to the Mechanic Empire.

While Manison's status was otherworldly, giving him face was one thing, but in matters such as these, no matter how impressive he was, it meant nothing.

"A pity, but I can understand."

Manison shook his head. His host did not reveal any expression, nor could anyone discern his emotions from his voice.

"If you change your mind one day, you may look for me."

"Then about the problem with EsGod..." Han Xiao probed.

"Hehe, no need to worry, I'll listen to the Federation of Light on this."

Manison lightly went around this topic. However, he did not mind Han Xiao rejecting him, and he did not seem to have the intention of getting up yet.

His words suddenly took on a change.

"I have a subordinate in the Shattered Star Ring called Sardeem, and he once reported something interesting to me. He mentioned that you stole his Mechanical army and even captured him alive for a period of time."

"... There was indeed such a matter. At that time, the circumstances forced me to."

Warning bells rose once again in Han Xiao's mind.

"Relax, since you did not kill him, there are no problems. I just felt that we seem to be quite connected by fate, to think that we had been linked so early on..."

Manison did not seem interested in seeking recompense.

But this next sentence caused Han Xiao's scalp to tingle!

"But talking about this, we were linked even earlier on... This reminds me, hehe, could I trouble you to return those two lost sheep to me?"

Manison's synthesized electronic tone had no fluctuations. While he laughed, one could not tell that he had a jovial intention.

The Mechanic Emperor actually knows about Aroshia‽

Han Xiao immediately forced his expression to remain straight, suppressing the turmoil within his emotions, and deepened his tone.

"... What do you mean?"

"A long time ago, there were two lucky AI life forms that infiltrated my base. One of them made off with one of my spare spaceships, while the other utilized my equipment to transform herself into an indestructible Mechanical Life. They tried to set their comrades free, but they were spotted by the firewalls within my base and chased by my automaton troops. Luckily for them, they entered a wormhole and eventually found their way to your organization..."

At this point, Manison paused.

"Surely you don't think that the two AI lifeforms were able to make it into my base on their own, right?"

Chapter 885: Brewing Influence, Rising Waves

Han Xiao only narrowed his eyes, not speaking. In actual fact, he had also shared the same suspicions, but Risda had replied in the same manner each time he asked, making him unable to verify it.

Manison crossed his hands and calmly spoke.

"Just based on their ability, they would never be able to break through my firewall. Behind them was another Beyond Grade A Mechanic that was coveting my Indestructible Mechanic Empire and wished to wreck my trump card troops while I was not within my base. They secretly guided these two little guys that knew nothing and quietly opened the virtual data channels for them."

"A pity that his cheap trick was spotted by me, and his scheme thus failed. I actually knew that the little fellow who had turned itself into an indestructible mechanic soldier had always been residing in Floating Dragon Island. She borrowed my energy transmission channel and stole my recombination material, so I could naturally track her.

"But I didn't go and recollect it. That's mainly because I don't care about these two fellows who were wandering outside, but I also decided not to make contact with Ames due to my past relationship with Aesop. However, since I'm here today, it's just as well. You can hand both of them back over to me."

Han Xiao rubbed his temples, feeling a little helpless. Twenty years ago when he first recruited Aroshia, he had been but a Grade B Super. He was just a nobody in the universe, so naturally, Manison would not place him in his eyes.

When he discovered the origins of Aroshia later on, he had once worried about whether Manison would pursue them, but Aroshia had never met any danger, so he had thought that Manison did not know of Aroshia's position.

When he reached the Beyond Grade A level, his Virtual Technology knowledge grew deeper, and he also started to doubt the given description of their escape, but because of his preconceived notions and added to the fact that twenty years had gone by peacefully, he took it for granted.

To think that Manison had always known...

Han Xiao's brain quickly moved.

Obviously, with Manison's status, he did not care about Aroshia and Risda escaping. After all, he had an entire AI civilization as his army; just two escapees did not mean anything.

But the reason he had mentioned this was not to take Aroshia and Risda back but rather because Han Xiao had rejected his request to obtain the amber, so he decided to attack him!

This old thing... God only knows just how many cards he still has on hand.

Han Xiao frowned, pausing for a moment, before replying solemnly.

"Aroshia is a comrade of mine who has followed me for over twenty years. She has free will and is not a slave of mine. I can't just pass someone who is respected and was involved in the establishment of Black Star Army together with me. How would I answer to my officers in this manner?"

Manison wished to reclaim its escaped soldiers, but Han Xiao tweaked the situation, emphasizing Aroshia's position within the Black Star Army. Thus, he could firmly reject.

"Your Excellency Black Star, you're a really tough nut." Manison still remained calm, and he only sighed.

From the time they had met up till now, Han Xiao had always been courteous, but regarding any crucial issues, he had never given way and always had hidden needles to retaliate.

Want the amber? Not selling!

Want my people? Not giving!

Han Xiao was apprehensive of Manison's strength, but he was not afraid of the other party. It would have been one thing if he did not have any support, but the dynasty was backing the Black Star Army, while the Federation backed Manison. Both of them had prestigious backers, and there was no need to be afraid.

Since he was the one to obtain the Spacetime Amber, the dynasty did not force him to hand it over because as long as it was in his hands, it was equivalent to the dynasty's strength.

However, if he chose to deal with the Mechanic Empire, this would mean that the method of production of the Spacetime Amber would be passed onto the Federation of Light's hands. This would cross the bottom line of the dynasty, and he would suffer the consequences. Thus, not even a guarantee from Manison that he would only research it privately could persuade him.

The reason Han Xiao did not make the transaction was not just to maintain the deterrence of the Spacetime Amber but also because of the problem of their opposing factions. Even if he would end up offending the other, he could only reject. This even applied to the worst case where they turned hostile.

The atmosphere was a little heavy for a moment. Han Xiao only stared at Manison, not speaking, while Manison did the same, his mechanical host not showing any emotions.

After silence reigned for a period, Manison finally opened his mouth again. "Alright then, it seems that my request was a little overboard."

He did not insist on reclaiming the duo, maybe because he did not wish to turn hostile with Han Xiao over such a small matter. However, Han Xiao could not know if that was what he thought.

"Many thanks for understanding, Your Excellency Mechanic Emperor." Han Xiao's tone also softened. Since the other party had given him face, there was a need to respond appropriately.

"However..." Manison's words took a curve. "While I don't care if they have their own lives, there's something I need to remind you of."

"Please speak."

"Those two fellows have always wanted to free their clansmen. I hope you will not be fooled by them. The Beyond Grade A Mechanic who helped them the other time ended up as my trophy, and I don't wish to be enemies with you... or else the result won't be nice to see." Manison's tone remained calm.

Han Xiao's pupils needled. This was a pure warning!

At this moment, Manison stood up, and he expressed his intention to leave.

"No matter what, being able to come into contact with you, Your Excellency Black Star, has made this a worthwhile trip. It was pleasant getting to know you."

Han Xiao remained expressionless and stood up, shaking hands with the other.

After exchanging communicator numbers, they walked out of the room. Han Xiao personally escorted Manison back to the Federation of Light's spaceship.

Before the hatch closed, Manison turned back to look at Han Xiao.

"Since you are coming over to the Primeval Star River to deal with EsGod, if time permits, come over to my place for a visit."

"Sure, I'll try to do so." Han Xiao nodded.

Ka!

The hatch sealed itself, and the spaceship's thrusters ignited, taking off into the vast universe.

Sending them off with his eyes, Han Xiao secretly heaved a sigh of relief and murmured, "Old fox."

Dealing with Manison was really not a pleasant thing.

Han Xiao could not determine Manison's true thoughts. His attitude was also ambiguous, his every move seemingly carrying probing intentions.

This guy is not just a person who purely pursues benefits. His thinking was hard to predict, and even with Manison's deeds from his previous life as a gauge, Han Xiao still found it hard to figure out the character of this old fox.

When encircling EsGod, the battlefield will be in the Primeval Star River. There's a need to go to the territory of the Mechanic Empire to battle... From the current situation, since I rejected him, Manison will definitely be dissatisfied with me, but considering all factors, he probably won't make me an enemy for now.

Han Xiao shook his head.

Because of a conflict of interest, this meeting ended on a heavy note.

Beep beep!

This time, the communicator rang, and Mona passed on the news that the Federation of Light had approved Han Xiao's request to hunt down EsGod.

No matter what, at least I have more assurance in dealing with EsGod now.

Han Xiao regained his spirit. Regarding the Mechanic Empire, he could handle it at a later date. The pressing task at hand was to first get rid of EsGod.

He was only an ally and thus could not privately engage in a cooperation with the Federation of Light without the dynasty's knowledge, or it would be considered as overstepping his bounds. Thus, he had to inform the dynasty, which was also convenient to show the dynasty his firm killing intent toward EsGod.

Regardless of whether the dynasty was willing to cooperate, the Federation of Light would be dispatched, and the only difference would be whether they encircled EsGod together or separately.

...

At the same time, on the Federation of Light's spaceship, Mona approached Manison and respectfully said, "The upper echelons have accepted Black Star's request to encircle EsGod, and they hope that Your Excellency Mechanic Emperor will be able to help since the battlefield will be situated in the Primeval Star River."

"Got it."

Manison waved his hands before controlling his host to move toward the porthole, gazing at the shrinking Black Star Army headquarters in the distance.

"No wonder Sorokin suffered a loss here. This guy is one tough nut." Manison nodded.

He was one of the shareholders of the Limitless Financial Group, and he supplied the financial group with a large amount of mechanical materials yearly. Thus, he had known Sorokin for quite a long time.

The armed force that Sorokin was developing on the Shattered Star Ring was not a secret to Manison. His intelligence web was huge, to the point where even though the Calamity Grade partner of the Beyond Grade A seed Roseau seemed to be working for Sorokin on the surface, he was actually a spy loyal to Manison.

Thus, Manison was aware that Sorokin tried to probe the Black Star Army and ended up suffering in the Gulal Civilization.

Sorokin was interested in the undying troops of the Black Star Army, which were also of interest to Manison. From his point of view, Black Star's immortal troops were akin to his Indestructible Mechanic Empire, just that Manison's army was larger. Thus, he was not as eager as Sorokin was.

What he was most concerned about now was the Spacetime Amber.

As for the Evolution Cube, he was not too interested in it.

The theory behind the Evolution Cube was unknown, and it was impossible for the genetic optimization to be adjusted. He was different from EsGod in this regard; Manison did not like things that could not be controlled.

...

On the mother planet of the Crimson Dynasty, Urranrell put down the report in her hand. Facing the long distance projection of Tarrokov, she expressionlessly asked, "You're saying, Black Star took the initiative to contact you, saying that the Federation of Light had contacted him, wishing to reconcile with him, and he persuaded them to prepare to encircle EsGod together?"

"Yes." Tarrokov nodded.

Not too long ago, Han Xiao had contacted him once more and roughly summarized the events for him. After ending the call, he had immediately reported upward to Urranrell, conveying Han Xiao's intentions.

"Hmm..." Urranrell leaned back in her chair, her hand rapping on the table as she turned to look at her confidant, Clotti. "What do you think?"

"Black Star did not ask the dynasty in advance and privately found a collaborator without permission. He has crossed the line, forgetting his identity now that he has made some achievements." Clotti's tone was indifferent, and he did not like or dislike Han Xiao, merely speaking his mind.

"It's not that serious. In fact, it's a good thing. Plus, he reported it immediately. This minor issue is not worth pursuing." Urranrell waved her hands. "I know that he wishes to kill EsGod more than anyone else. He's probably worried that EsGod will still eye the Evolution Cube and will make a comeback."

She pondered for a while before making a decision.

"Since the Federation of Light wishes to participate, pull aboard the Arcane Church. Let's have a three-pronged operation."

Because EsGod had turned traitor, it resulted in huge losses for the Arcane Church. Thus, the Arcane Church would definitely remember this grudge. Furthermore, because they had worked together with EsGod during the battle of Planet Lighthouse, it had caused some negative public opinion within the interstellar society. There was an urgent need for them to express their position against EsGod.

In this regard, EsGod was just like a chamber pot. When there was a need, they would take it out to use, but once they had utilized it, they would find it smelly and kick it back into the corner once more.

Urranrell's idea was to drag the Arcane Church down as well, to relieve the pressure on the dynasty. If they were going to fight, all of them should do so. No one should sit by the side and watch.

Furthermore, eliminating the EsGod would also help to fulfil Black Star's wishes.

...

In a certain desolate universe belt of the Primeval Star River, EsGod's fleet was currently cruising along, moving toward the edge of the star field.

In the main hall of the spaceship, Fakisen came up to the throne of the EsGod, awakening the snoozing EsGod.

The dark mist swirled, forming ugly facial features. EsGod opened his eyes, gazing at his assistant before asking indifferently, "What's the matter?"

"There's a problem with our main camp. The troops we have in the Central Galaxy have been encircled by the Crimson Dynasty and the Arcane Church, and our losses are disastrous."

"Oh, is there anything else?" EsGod nodded as though he did not care.

Fakisen paused for a while before forcing a smile. "We've also angered the Arcane Church this time, and they may join hands with the dynasty to send Beyond Grade As after you. Are you not worried?"

"They're the ones that should be worried, not me." EsGod closed his eyes again, his tone akin to one dreaming. "I can also test out my strength after my evolution."

Seeing EsGod once again sink into slumber, Fakisen left the hall. As he closed the door, it covered the ferocious arc of his mouth.

Anger, glee, complacency, resignation... all sorts of complex feelings flashed across.

Chapter 886: Borrowing Strength

Two days later, Han Xiao called all his officers to his office and informed them that he was going to the Central Galaxy.

Sylvia nodded upon hearing that and asked, "How long will your trip be?"

"I have to see the dynasty's arrangement. We will only be able to take action after they gather enough manpower."

"Alright. The affairs of the army will be managed by me, so you don't have to worry," Sylvia said.

By the side, Hila said, "I have some things that I need to pack. When will we be leaving?"

Han Xiao shook his head.

"You don't need to go. I won't be bringing the Black Star Guards this time."

Hila froze in place and asked, "Why?"

"Because I will be fighting with EsGod, and you guys won't be of help. It would be better for all of you to remain in the Shattered Star Ring," Han Xiao said.

The members of the Black Star Guards were all Calamity Grade elites, and their main responsibility was to deal with the enemies that did not require him to make a personal appearance. There was no need to bring them along to deal with EsGod; they would only be a burden to him. Thus, Han Xiao decided to go alone this time.

"... Alright." Hila grunted with dissatisfaction and left the room.

She seemed to be agitated again.

Han Xiao laughed in his heart. This was a good thing. Hila was not the crazy individual that she was in her previous life, and it would be good to provide her with timely motivation.

"My sister will be going through a devilish training regime again." Aurora then looked at Han Xiao and said with worry, "Will there be any danger if you go alone?"

"I'm not taking the Black Star Guards, but I didn't say that I will be going alone."

As he said that, Han Xiao turned around to look at Reynold.

"Hmm? Me?" Reynold pointed to himself with a puzzled look on his face.

"That's right. It's you."

"But I still have to manage the logistics..." Reynold did not understand why Han Xiao wanted to bring him along.

"Won't you get bored if you spend all your time dealing with logistics? Follow me on a walk. Right, who is the vice director of the logistics department?"

"A Calamity Grade Mechanic that joined a few years ago. This is his resume." Sylvia immediately took out some information.

The army had developed rapidly over the past few years, and Han Xiao had plenty of experts under his charge. There were more and more Calamity Grades working for him, and the number of Calamity Grades he had was more than a Star System civilization. Apart from the Black Star Guards in the Shattered Star Ring, the other Calamity Grades were scattered in other departments and had a respected position.

There were more Calamity Grade Supers who came from the outside, such as Hadavy, Lagi, and so on. There were fewer Calamity Grade Supers that were trained by the army like Herlous, Sylvia, and Reynold.

Han Xiao then flipped through the records and asked, "Does he have any record of accepting bribes, reselling the army's blueprints, or corruption?"

"No. I would have reported it to you if he did so..." Sylvia burst out in cold sweat.

You are a Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanic and probably even know about the size of my undergarments. Is there anything in the base that is hidden from your eyes?

"Then the matters of the logistics department shall be handed over to him temporarily." Han Xiao then turned around and looked at Reynold. "Nero is still a child, and he will be traumatized if he spends every day studying. I plan to bring him along to tour Planet Crimson Ring. Of course, having a holiday is one thing, but his studies cannot stop."

Reynold then came to a realization. I see, His Excellency Black Star wants to bring Nero out on a holiday but doesn't want to let his godson relax completely. Thus, he is also bringing the teacher along.

Sylvia immediately felt her heart turn sour.

I am also His Excellency Black Star's student! Why is our teacher so biased toward Reynold? I can also be Nero's teacher!

I also want a holiday!

"Don't worry, all of you will stay on Planet Crimson Ring when I fight EsGod, and there's no need to follow me. There won't be any danger." Han Xiao then looked at Feidin. "Follow along as well. You can accompany Nero."

"Alright." Feidin smiled. "Nero should be very happy."

I don't know if he will be happy, but I definitely am...

Han Xiao chuckled to himself.

Han Xiao mainly brought Feidin and Nero along because he believed in luck. After all, it would be difficult for him to deal with EsGod, and bringing two high grade protagonist level characters with him along might increase his chances of success.

The boost from two Advanced Luck Glows was better than an unlucky him working alone.

Han Xiao then set the departure time to two hours later.

Everyone left the room, and Hadavy dragged the napping Lagi out of the room as though he was dragging a bag of rubbish.

After the end of the meeting, Reynold immediately returned to the Logistics Department to give out his instructions before returning to his office and opening a side door.

Nero was currently doing his homework in this side room.

After drinking the dragonblood potion, he did not feel like sleeping at all. Thus, he got into the same napping posture that he had in Planet Aquamarine to try and fall asleep.

After checking Nero's homework, a bright smile of satisfaction emerged on Reynold's face. At the very start, he had only taught Nero because it was Han Xiao's instruction, but throughout the teaching process, he had truly grown to like this student of his as he saw himself in Nero.

Although Nero did not like machines as crazily as him, he was also capable of enduring hardship. Nero had a strength in that he would never skive. Even if the amount of homework that he had drove him to despair, Nero would still complete it earnestly. Reynold truly liked such a student.

After all, the Mechanic Class was different from the other classes; knowledge was power. The better the foundation, the smoother his future would be. Thus, Reynold felt that Nero would definitely be able to go a long way.

Despite having such thoughts in his heart, Reynold naturally would not say that with his personality. He then coughed dryly and said, "Stop doing your work and pack up your things. The Army Commander wants to take you to the Central Galaxy."

Nero's eyes immediately sparkled with excitement.

"Godfather is going to bring me out to play! Hahaha... I finally don't have to do homework!"

Nero then threw his pen down and was agitated to the point he almost teared up.

Godfather still dotes on me!

The tiny bit of resentment in his heart disappeared, and he almost wanted to jump for joy to praise his godfather.

"Pack your things quickly. We will be setting off very soon."

Nero's actions froze in place, and he turned around slowly. "Wait... we?"

"The Army Commander wants me to follow along to guide your learning," Reynold said expressionlessly.

Nero's face froze in place.

...

Han Xiao and the others then gathered at his private dock. Feidin was the first to arrive, and they chatted for a while before Reynold and Nero arrived.

Nero carried a small bag with a dispirited look.

"Everyone's here. Let's set off."

Han Xiao led everyone onto the spaceship and got Phillip to activate the autopilot mode.

The spaceship then flew into space and entered hyperdrive.

He had gone to the Central Galaxy the previous year and was already familiar with the journey.

After flying for a period of time, they arrived at the army stargate and skipped past many Star Fields to arrive at the Crimson Ring Star System. Under the guidance of the army, they then weaved through the Psionic Seal Ring and arrived at Planet Crimson Ring.

"This is the capital of the Crimson Dynasty..." Reynold looked at the various mechanical structures around him and murmured in awe.

"How magnificent." Nero looked out of the window. This was far more spectacular than his home planet, Planet Aquamarine.

As their spaceship landed, there was already a dynasty's emissary waiting for them at the dock. Bowing to Han Xiao respectfully, the emissary led the group into Tarunamir Palace.

This was the legendary capital of a Universal Civilization. Nero was extremely curious about everything, and if not for his godfather, he would never have been able to visit this place in his lifetime.

The emissary then said with a smile, "Your Excellency Black Star, we will be in charge of all of your daily needs. Please find me if you need anything."

"Hmm, then why not take them to explore this place? The mother planet of the dynasty is very big, and you can show them all the fun places," Han Xiao said.

"Godfather, aren't you going to come along with us?"

"I still have something else to do and have to meet the Dynasty Ruler."

Han Xiao waved his hands and headed toward the core political building where Urranrell was. He had already reported his arrival, and Urranrell was waiting to see him.

Han Xiao arrived outside the office of the Ruler quickly.

The secretary knocked on the door, and Urranrell's voice could be heard from the inside.

"Please enter."

The door opened, and Han Xiao walked in.

This was the second time that he had seen the Ruler, and just like the first time, only the two of them were in the room.

"Black Star, you're here. Please take a seat," Urranrell said.

Han Xiao nodded, and just as he sat down, Urranrell continued speaking.

"You rendered huge merits during the battle at Planet Lighthouse. Good job."

Urranrell had only praised him through long-distance communication previously and would naturally have to give a personal praise to Han Xiao now that they had met each other.

"I only did something small," Han Xiao replied.

"You're too humble. The dynasty will always reward those with merit, and you should already know that we will increase our support to you in terms of resources and give you some benefits when assigning the territories for the Flickering World."

Urranrell then paused for a while before slowly saying, "I can give you a heads up. After the end of the first developmental phase, we will set up various basic facilities in the different Star Clusters and assign some territories to our allied organizations. You can give some suggestions on the topic of territory assignment, and we will consider your suggestions seriously."

Han Xiao raised his brows. This was akin to letting him pick the first territory. It probably was not only for his merits but also to rope him in.

The development of a new Star Field was a long-term plan, and the dynasty was not anxious. After the exploration would be development. They would have to first develop the various regions that they had explored before expanding out into the other Star Clusters. At that time, the various allies would surely receive more than one piece of territory.

This was good for Han Xiao. He would be able to gain a territory after the first phase was over and could officially develop his Mechanical Life civilization and shift the Black Spirit Race over.

He would have a lot more freedom in his own territory compared to in the Shattered Star Ring and would not have to share a region with the other Star System Civilizations.

"I'm looking forward to it." Han Xiao smiled.

"Hmm, let's talk about some proper matters. The dynasty has summoned you this time for two matters. First, the dynasty promised the Arcane Church to help them unseal one of the Beyond Grade As, and we need your help."

Han Xiao nodded to indicate his agreement.

"The second matter is to surround EsGod. It is also related to the first matter. The Arcane Church will only agree to join in the battle if you unseal one seal."

Han Xiao was slightly shocked upon hearing that.

The Arcane Church was also dragged into it?

He did not receive news of this beforehand and was a little surprised.

"Isn't it only the Federation of Light? The Arcane Church is..."

"This is my intention. Since you pulled the Federation of Light into this, I called the Arcane Church along, and they are willing to help us."

This was an unexpected surprise. With the Arcane Church joining, the three Universal Civilizations were working together, so they would have a greater chance of getting rid of EsGod!

Han Xiao pretended to ponder for a moment before saying with a smile, "We were the only ones involved originally, but with the three Universal Civilizations working together, we can save a lot of effort."

"This isn't the only reason. It is also because of you."

"Me?"

"Yes, the dynasty can feel your murderous intent toward EsGod, and we chose to do so to fulfill your wish."

Han Xiao was truly overwhelmed with grace.

This meant that his suggestion had influenced the decision of the dynasty!

"You are an important ally of the dynasty, and we will naturally respect your thoughts." Urranrell paused for a moment before continuing. "We shall end the conversation here today. I still have some things to take care of, and the Arcane Church fleet has not arrived yet. Remain on Planet Crimson Ring for a while, and we will inform you of the exact time of the operation."

"Okay."

Han Xiao could tell that the other party was inviting him to leave.

It seems like the Dynasty Ruler is truly busy.

Han Xiao then stood up and took his leave.

Hearing the door behind him close, Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief and was truly excited.

The Crimson Dynasty originally only planned to put up a show to deal with EsGod, but he caused the three Universal Civilizations to work together!

This situation was because of his suggestion, and the outcome was better than he had imagined!

His resolution to get rid of EsGod was recognized by the dynasty, and there was also the effect of the Political Asset.

The influence that he had accumulated over the years was finally effective!

"It's payback time." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, and a cold glint flashed in his eyes.

Chapter 887: Troops Established

Leaving the government building, Han Xiao's communicator rang. It was Milizaus who called him.

"Black Star, are you on Planet Crimson Ring already?" Milizaus chuckled.

"Yes, are you here too? I didn't see you around."

"I haven't arrived yet. We are having a long-distance gathering. Come online for a while."

"Alright." Han Xiao entered the quantum network and found an encrypted channel.

The next moment, his projection appeared in a huge room with a round table in front of him and plenty of seats around. His own projection was currently in one of the seats. Most of the seats were filled with only four empty ones at the moment.

Han Xiao then looked around and realized that everyone present was an ally of the dynasty. It was like a Beyond Grade A group chat for the Crimson Dynasty.

Without anybody organizing a meeting, the 'group chat' would usually be silent with no one online. Currently, most of the Beyond Grade As were online, and many familiar faces were present. That included 'Dragon King' Milizaus, 'Incineration' Beyoni, 'Warship Emperor' Maximiler, 'Fox Arts' Ravenlaude, 'Star Slasher' Viru, and Little Ty-Ty. 'Dark Lord' Clotti and another of the three pillars were not online.

"Haha, Black Star is here." Beyoni was the most welcoming, and he looked very happy.

Everyone then looked at Han Xiao and greeted him. The two who fought with him on Planet Lighthouse were the friendliest. Maximiler was also pretty friendly. Ravenlaude and Heber greeted him calmly, and the others had a trace of respect in their voices.

After the battle on Planet Lighthouse, Han Xiao had gained the battle record of capturing a Beyond Grade A alive, which cemented his status in the Beyond Grade A group.

Although Han Xiao had only entered the Beyond Grade A realm not too long ago, he had already gained the respect of his comrades and was officially accepted into the group. He was now at the middle rungs of the group and had an even greater status than some ordinary Beyond Grade As. At the very least, there would not be anyone who intentionally provoked him anymore.

Fists reigned supreme after all, and the Beyond Grade As only respected strength.

Facing the friendly looks on the faces of his comrades, Han Xiao replied to all of them warmly.

After which, the organizer of this meeting, Milizaus, started the meeting.

"The other four aren't coming, and there isn't a need to consider them. Let's begin our discussion. Everyone knows that the dynasty plans to send out at least three Beyond Grade As to kill EsGod and has prepared a name list. However, they would like to ask us if we are willing first. There isn't a need to talk about Black Star since he is resolute about killing EsGod. I also plan to help him. Is anyone else interested?"

A Universal Civilization could not easily order a Beyond Grade A around and would generally consider if the Beyond Grade A Super was willing to participate in the operation.

Everyone then fell into deep thought while glancing at Han Xiao once in a while.

Han Xiao looked around and felt Milizaus looking at him. He immediately understood Milizaus' intentions.

Milizaus had heard from the dynasty about Han Xiao's intention to kill EsGod and thus summoned most of the dynasty's Beyond Grade As. In fact, he was trying to find partners for Han Xiao and give Han Xiao a chance to choose his teammates.

Right at this moment, Beyoni shrugged his shoulders and said, "Black Star, you were around when we last fought EsGod. It isn't that I don't wish to help you, but I am also an Esper, and EsGod's ability is my nemesis. I shall not take up a slot in this battle."

Han Xiao nodded in agreement. Indeed, EsGod had the ability to silence Espers and was the nemesis of most Espers. Beyoni was not wrong to say that he would be useless if he went.

However, understanding was one thing, but he still had to show disdain.

Ah, little brother.

I only have a single word for you—noob!

Upon seeing the rest remain silent, Han Xiao said, "The Dynasty Ruler revealed some information to me just now. The dynasty isn't the only one taking action this time; the Federation of Light and Arcane Church will also be participating. With all three parties working together, they won't be putting up a show. There is a good chance to get rid of EsGod. I definitely won't let go of this opportunity, and I will definitely be thankful to anyone who is willing to help me."

Upon hearing that, the eyes of many lit up. This meant that they would be able to use the Evolution Cube if they helped Black Star get rid of EsGod.

"I will participate." Ravenlaude was the first to speak.

"Alright, who else?" Milizaus asked calmly.

As an Ancient One, both him and Ravenlaude were not easy to deal with. Although their relationship was not good, he also recognized Ravenlaude's strength. An ordinary Beyond Grade A was not capable of becoming an Ancient One. Milizaus would naturally be willing to select a few more powerful allies for Black Star.

There was no need to consider the other two pillars. Clotti would keep guard beside Urranrell, and the other one was guarding a Star Field.

Heber was also tempted but could not bring himself to offer help.

Some rejected and others were not too interested. Finally, more than half of the Beyond Grade As present decided to participate in the operation. Together with Han Xiao, there were seven individuals in total.

Milizaus, Maximiler, Ravenlaude, Viru, Kohler, and Lotus Swordsman—these six were his comrades participating in the operation to get rid of EsGod. Kohler was a Pugilist, and Lotus Swordsman was a female Psychic. There was not a single Esper among the group.

"Will seven of us be too many? Will the dynasty agree?" Ravenlaude asked.

"We can help him in our personal capacity if the dynasty doesn't agree. Can the dynasty object?" Lotus Swordsman said.

The Crimson Dynasty originally planned to send out three to five people, but because Han Xiao had promised to use the Evolution Cube as a reward, the troop had seven individuals, which was out of the dynasty's expectations.

However, the dynasty did not have any issue with it. After all, it would not be good for them to stop their allies from seeking help personally. Furthermore, it was not a bad thing either.

Han Xiao then sized up this female Psychic. She had long white hair and violet skin. Her appearance looked similar to that of a human, and she was considered beautiful by the standards of the galaxy. She gave out a dreamlike aura and had a unique sense of charisma.

Lotus Swordsman was her name, not a title. Swordsman was her surname, and Lotus was her forename.

She came from a special race called the Rainis Race. The members of this race did not have any gender before the age of fifteen, and their bodies would undergo a special transformation at the age of fifteen. They could become a female or male, and this ceremony would be called the 'Gender Determination Ceremony'. Once their gender was decided, they would not be able to change it in the future.

As such, the race put heavy emphasis on splitting up the workload evenly. However, because the Gender Determination Ceremony affected one's life, there were far too many people who chose to become males every year. Even if society increased the benefits and status of females, the birth rate was still falling.

As such, the Rainis Race had a quota of females to fulfill every year to ensure that their race could continue to reproduce. Lotus Swordsman was one of the unlucky candidates to be picked when she was young and forced to become a female.

Despite the Rainis Race producing a Beyond Grade A Super, they did not receive any protection. Lotus Swordsman had long announced that the Rainis Race had nothing to do with her and managed her own organization.

Their other comrade, Kohler, was a Beyond Grade A who had completely submitted to the dynasty. He did not have an organization, and although his strength could not be compared to Heber, he was still a Beyond Grade A.

"I will have to rely on all of you for help," Han Xiao said sincerely.

After chatting a while longer, Milizaus announced the end of the meeting and informed the dynasty of the outcome.

Han Xiao then left the quantum network and heaved a sigh of relief.

His teammates had already been set. With the dynasty sending out seven people, there would definitely be more than ten Beyond Grade As together with the other two parties. The scale of the battle might reach the same level as the battle on Planet Lighthouse.

But this time, all of them were going to deal with EsGod alone, and EsGod's situation was far worse than the dynasty's during the battle on Planet Lighthouse.

Han Xiao clenched his fists in excitement and prepared for battle!

Chapter 888: Future Dynasty Ruler

The dynasty's team had been decided. A group of seven Beyond Grade As was an extremely powerful force, and the number had exceeded Han Xiao and the dynasty's expectations. The dynasty agreed to the list of members of the team and gathered their fleet to prepare for the battle.

Before dealing with EsGod, they had to first complete the trade with the Arcane Church.

The Arcane Church escort fleet was still on the way, and Han Xiao was awaiting his orders on Planet Crimson Ring. He could take the time out to accompany Nero and the others to explore Planet Crimson Ring.

Planet Crimson Ring was extremely large with plenty of floating cities in the sky. There were many sights that were famous in the universe. Furthermore, Planet Crimson Ring was the origin of the Crimson Dynasty Civilization, and many historical locations from a long time ago were retained.

Under the lead of the tour guide, Han Xiao and the others spent this time exploring many different tourist locations.

Han Xiao belonged to the dynasty faction in his previous life and had naturally explored the mother planet of the dynasty before. Because he was familiar with the situation on the planet, he was not too curious and was mainly there to accompany Nero and the others.

Planet Crimson Ring had plenty of rich mission resources, but to the present Han Xiao, the value of these missions was not great. Furthermore, his current status was different, and his every action would be watched by others. As such, it was impossible for him to become an errand boy for someone else.

Most importantly, there were many familiar missions and characters that had not appeared at this time yet.

Today, their group arrived at the Saint Palace Museum of the dynasty.

This museum was the largest one in the Crimson Dynasty and had objects from every historical period during the development of the Crimson Dynasty.

The Saint Palace Museum was a large garden with dozens of different palaces. The palaces all had different styles to represent the different time period of the dynasty.

The advantage of having the dynasty's tour guide beside them was that they did not need to queue up or buy an entrance ticket. Han Xiao led Feidin, Reynold, and Reynold to skip the long queue and entered the museum through a special entrance.

Their special privilege drew the attention of those queuing up, and everyone began whispering to each other.

"That seems to be Black Star from the Shattered Star Ring. I saw him on the news before."

"To think that we'd be able to meet such a bigshot. How lucky."

"Quick, take a picture!"

These tourists were all extremely excited and took out their cameras to take pictures. A Beyond Grade A Super was an individual who truly held great authority and was completely different from these ordinary galactic residents. Now that they had met Han Xiao, it was like meeting a famous celebrity on the streets.

These tourists came from many different races and civilizations. The Psionic Seal Ring was there to protect the mother planet but not to seal off the mother planet. At the very least, they would not do so during this generation. It was just that every visitor had to go through stringent checks and could only spend a limited time on the planet.

Every year, Planet Crimson Ring would welcome a huge number of tourists to support the local tourist industry. The dynasty was not interested in that little bit of money but in increasing the influence of the dynasty's culture through tourism.

Han Xiao and the others walked into the museum and entered the main palace under the tour guide's lead.

Compared to the bustle on the outside, the palace was extremely silent and had a solemn atmosphere.

The main palace described the development direction of the Crimson Dynasty, and everyone listened to the explanation of the tour guide as they looked through the various objects being displayed.

Nero was filled with curiosity toward the dynasty's history and looked through the introduction of every item. Feidin followed behind Nero and was also pretty interested in the items being displayed. Reynold's attention was mainly focused on the various ancient machines being displayed. Although these machines were considered outdated compared to the current technology, Reynold was still more interested in these items than the others.

Han Xiao walked the fastest and arrived in front of ten gigantic black stone slabs. The height of the ten stone slabs almost reached the ceiling of the palace, and the history of the Crimson Dynasty was written down from the beginning to now. The development of the Crimson Dynasty had not always been smooth.

The Crimson Dynasty was also once weak and had been through many struggles such as civil war and revolutionary attempts.

The advancement of their genes brought about risk of mutation. The advancement of the machines and artificial intelligence risked the betrayal of the intelligent machines. The use of heavy machines brought about changes to the environment... As their technological skills advanced, the civilization also met many different forks in the road.

There were plenty of other dangers such as the various wormholes, pandemics, exploration wars, and so on. Through the many tribulations that the Crimson Dynasty had experienced, they finally developed their iron-blooded character.

They grew from a weak civilization into one of the rulers in the universe. They had been through plenty of tribulations throughout this period, and the ten stone slabs recorded the price that they had to pay to get there.

In front of the history of an entire civilization, everyone seemed extremely small.

Just when Han Xiao fell into a daze while looking at the stone slabs, an old voice sounded beside him.

"I'm always in awe whenever I see these stone slabs."

Han Xiao turned around and saw an old man wearing the uniform of the museum. He had a compassionate look in his eyes with his back straight as though he was a soldier.

"That's right. Every civilization capable of reaching the universe level deserves to be respected," Han Xiao replied.

The old man then nodded and turned around to look at Han Xiao. With a smile, he said, "Let me introduce myself. I am the vice manager of the Saint Palace museum, Karl Fleur Wishandi. Hello, Your Excellency Black Star."

"Hello." Han Xiao also nodded, but his heart began thumping.

Karl Fleur Wishandi? This name sounds so familiar...

Usually, the names that he found familiar would be the famous characters from his previous life. Han Xiao immediately began searching through his database while talking to the vice manager.

Karl was a healthy old man who did not seem too concerned about Han Xiao's status and talked to Han Xiao on equal grounds.

"I have always been interested in the history of the dynasty and have guarded the museum for many years. I enjoy protecting the items in this place." Karl stroked the stone slab in front of him and lamented.

Han Xiao glanced at the 'Do Not Touch' sign by the side and decided to ignore the vice manager breaking the rules.

"Vice Manager Karl, did you use to be a soldier?"

"That's right. I served in the Seventh Reconnaissance Corps of the dynasty when I was young and joined in twenty-three battles. I was then transferred to become a long-distance commander before landing an admin job. I served in the army for more than half my life and applied to retire. Then, I became the vice manager of the museum."

Rather than saying that he was explaining his origins to Han Xiao, it was more like he was talking to himself and reminiscing about the past.

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao's eyes lit up, and he finally remembered who the person beside him was!

More accurately, the retired soldier beside him was not a famous NPC, but his descendant was famous throughout the universe.

Karl's surname was 'Fleur Wishandi', and one of the future Rulers of the Crimson Dynasty had such a surname!

It was very likely that the future Ruler of the dynasty was the descendant of this old man before him!

It could be said that he had met a large fish this time!

Han Xiao then turned around to look at Nero and Feidin slowly.

They are truly terrifying...

Of course, according to the time, that Dynasty Ruler might not have been born yet. However, there was still value in befriending him, and it could be said that the value was even higher.

Han Xiao then said with a smile, "I joined the dynasty recently, and I am also very curious about the dynasty's history. I wonder if you will be interested in giving me an introduction?"

"It would be my honor to introduce the dynasty's history to a Beyond Grade A ally." Karl laughed heartily.

As a retired soldier of the older generation, he was very willing to narrate the dynasty's history to others.

For the entire day, Karl snatched the job of the tour guide and accompanied Han Xiao and the others to view the other palaces.

Since Han Xiao intended to befriend the other party, both of them chatted merrily for the entire day and agreed to continue the next day.

For the next two days, Han Xiao followed Karl to explore the Saint Palace Museum and finally finished viewing all the palaces at night.

Han Xiao then invited Karl to go out for a meal, but Karl did not accept the invitation. Instead, he invited Han Xiao to be a guest at his place and said that he would personally cook.

At the appointed date, Han Xiao and the others headed toward Karl's residence.

As a retired, high-ranking officer, Karl received special treatment from the government and had a small villa on the mother planet of the dynasty. It was not too far from Tarunamir Palace and was pretty convenient to reach.

Han Xiao and the others arrived in front of the villa, and Nero knocked on the door.

Everyone waited for a while, and a middle-aged man pushed open the door.

"Hello, Your Excellency Black Star, please come in," the middle-aged man said with a face of excitement and respect.

This middle-aged man was Karl's eldest son and was working for the Crimson Dynasty. With his father's connections, he had climbed to the middle rungs but was still nothing much before Han Xiao.

Knowing that his father had befriended a Beyond Grade A Super, he was extremely excited and made plenty of preparations for the gathering that night.

Walking into the hall, Karl's head appeared from the kitchen, and he said, "Your Excellency Black Star, please sit for a while. The dishes will be served in a while."

"Don't worry, take your time. We have plenty of time." Han Xiao waved his hands.

They then sat down on the couch in the living room. Karl had another two children, with the middle child being a daughter and the youngest child being a son. The former was an entrepreneur who managed a galactic travel agency, and the latter was a sculptor. Both of them were extremely respectful and looked extremely nervous.

Looking around at the decorations of the room, Han Xiao saw the picture of a lady being hung on the wall. She should be Karl's late wife.

Karl had three children, and Han Xiao did not know which branch the future Dynasty Ruler came from. It was not that he could not remember but that he did not study the matter in such great detail in his previous life. However, according to the occupations of the three children, it should probably be the descendant of the eldest son.

Karl's eldest son intended to befriend him with a fawning tone in his voice. As for Karl's other two children, they did not dare speak up much.

Han Xiao chatted casually with Karl's eldest son for a while before Karl walked out of the kitchen with the dishes and called for everyone to come and eat.

The dishes were all common household dishes from the Crimson Dynasty and were all very tasty. Nero ate to his heart's content, and Karl's eldest son snatched Feidin's job to help serve Nero food.

After the meal, Karl's daughter and youngest son took the initiative to clear up, and the others returned to the living room. It could be seen just how happy Karl was today, and he was truly full of smiles.

"Your Excellency Black Star still has the greatest face. These three little b*stards, always complaining that they are busy every day and do not have the time to meet me. But the moment you arrived, they all ran over obediently. Especially this little brat, he is even more passionate than this old man."

Karl chuckled.

"Cough cough." Karl's eldest son coughed awkwardly.

Han Xiao then chuckled and asked Karl's eldest son, "What is your position in the Crimson Dynasty?"

Karl's eldest son immediately lit up and described his post.

"Oh, it isn't too bad for you to be able to sit on such a post." Han Xiao stroked his chin and added, "You can always find me if you need any help in the future. Give me your number."

"That's great! Thank you, Your Excellency Black Star!" Karl's eldest son was overjoyed.

He was so passionate about hosting Han Xiao so that he could receive Black Star's protection. His political sense was not too poor, and Black Star's status was extremely high. Together with the fact that the Dynasty Ruler paid close attention to Black Star, Black Star's protection would result in a positive impact for his career.

Furthermore, with Black Star's age, he would be able to protect the Crimson Dynasty for a long time and would definitely have a higher status in the future.

Karl did not like his eldest son's style and felt as though his eldest son made his friendship with Black Star become complicated. However, he would not stop his eldest son's opportunity and could only pretend that he did not see anything.

"Right, I also brought a gift for you." Han Xiao smiled.

"Sigh, a gift isn't necessary." Karl waved his arms.

"How could that do? I can't possibly come empty handed."

Han Xiao then snapped his fingers, and ten compressed orbs landed on the table.

"I personally made these mechanical guards. They are equipped with a transmitter to send a signal to me. You can press this button when you meet danger, and I will know that you guys are in danger. I will then be able to send my Mechanical Force through the void dimension to activate these mechanical guards and protect all of you. The mechanical guards that are boosted by my Mechanical Force should be able to deal with Calamity Grade dangers."

"Wouldn't this be too precious?" Karl hesitated.

Han Xiao laughed upon hearing that and said, "Hahaha, I am a Mechanic."

"Alright then, I shall thank you for your gift." Karl then accepted the ten compressed orbs.

He was already old, and even if he did not care about his own safety, he had to consider his future generations.

The mechanical guards of a Beyond Grade A had enormous value. Black Star's life span was very long, and as long as Black Star remained alive, these ten compressed orbs would be like a family heirloom!

After giving out the gift, both parties were much closer than before. After chatting a while longer, Han Xiao took his leave.

Upon leaving Karl's villa, Han Xiao's mouth curled up slightly in a smile.

He had befriended the ancestors of a future Dynasty Ruler. If he really became the senior of a future Dynasty Ruler, things would be interesting.

This small investment had a chance of bringing him huge returns, and there was no reason for him not to make such an investment.

Thinking about it, Han Xiao stroked Nero's head.

Nero enjoyed the feeling of Han Xiao patting him on the head, and he looked at Han Xiao.

"You are really my little star of fortune." Han Xiao chuckled.

Nero blinked, and although he did not understand what Han Xiao meant, he could tell that Han Xiao was in a good mood. Thus, he made use of this opportunity to ask, "Then, can my homework be reduced?"

"Sure. In your dreams."

Nero then shook his head to shake Han Xiao's hand off and placed his bag above his head to prevent Han Xiao from patting him.

Han Xiao spent the following days casually in this manner, taking Nero and the others out to tourist hotspots while farming favorability with Karl's family. After some time, the dynasty finally sent him some news.

The Arcane Church's troops had arrived at the transaction location, and he could set off.

Han Xiao left Nero and the others on the dynasty's mother planet and followed the dynasty's fleet on his own.

Chapter 889: EsGod's Preparation

Region 1749-C was the border between the Constellation Corridor and Silver Arm, and the Crimson Dynasty and Arcane Church had a large number of troops stationed there.

It only took Han Xiao a few days to arrive at the borders with the various stargates of the dynasty. This was the transaction location for the dynasty and Arcane Church.

Their battleship stopped beside the outpost, and Han Xiao's spaceship received a message from the outpost commander.

"Your Excellency Black Star, the Arcane Church escort fleet has arrived. They are waiting to complete the transaction with us. The location of the transaction is on an uninhabited planet between the two borders. His Excellency Milizaus and the outpost fleet will escort you to the destination."

"Milizaus is also here?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

Just when he asked that question, the old dragon's voice sounded in the channel.

"I arrived a long time ago and have waited here for a long time already. The dynasty only wanted me to come as a precautionary measure. Although the odds of anything going wrong are slim, we cannot ignore the possibility that the other party may want to snatch the Spacetime Amber."

"Hmm, alright." Han Xiao nodded. "Commander, we can set off now."

A fleet of heavy-armored battleships flew out from the outpost, and Milizaus' gigantic body followed beside them.

The fleet did not enter hyperdrive but relied on their thrusters only. After flying for a short while, an uninhabited planet appeared in their sights.

The Arcane Church and the Crimson Dynasty's fleet had already arrived on the planet, and both parties were currently in a standoff outside the atmosphere. In the middle of the standoff was an Arcane Church escort fleet with the sealed Dylan being placed on the ground.

The dynasty had agreed to unseal Dylan. The weakest individual would usually receive special treatment from the enemy.

Han Xiao first scanned the situation on the planet and confirmed that there was no trap.

However, he had been caught off guard by the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device in the battle on Planet Lighthouse. Thus, he did not lower his guard.

"We have arrived. Your Excellency Black Star, let's go." In the bridge of the flagship, the dynasty emissary invited Han Xiao to set off with him.

Han Xiao nodded and left the spaceship.

The surface of the red planet got closer and closer to him.

Han Xiao landed on the ground and stepped on the sandy surface.

Walking in front of the Arcane Church squad, he looked at Dylan, who was trapped in the amber.

The dynasty emissary then talked to the Arcane Church emissary for a while before nodding to Han Xiao.

"Your Excellency Black Star, please release the seal."

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao stepped forward and stood in front of Dylan. He then turned around to look at the Arcane Church escort squad.

Great Mechanic Han then raised his brows and stomped on the ground lightly.

The next moment, the ground transformed into nano alloys, and a large metal wall was erected from the ground to ensure that no one would be able to see what was going on in the region.

Black Star obviously did not want to show others his method to unseal the seal. Everyone could only wait silently with disappointment.

After a full ten minutes, the alloy wall collapsed and returned to Han Xiao's palms. Dylan's seal had already disappeared, and he collapsed onto the ground with a look of fear in his eyes.

"Your Excellency Dylan, are you alright?" The Arcane Church escort squad immediately went to support him.

"I'm alright."

Dylan snapped back into his senses and stood up on his own while glaring at Han Xiao with enmity, anger, and fear.

"How have you been over the past few months?" Han Xiao squinted and chucked.

Dylan trembled and subconsciously took a step back.

His body had been sealed by the Spacetime Amber, but his thoughts had not been. He could clearly feel his body but was unable to control it. Such a feeling was unbearable as though he was possessed by a ghost. During the period when he was sealed, Dylan felt like every day was a year and had almost gone mad.

If not for the mental strength and will of a Beyond Grade A being extremely powerful, he felt that he might have truly been driven insane.

Although a few months of captivity was not enough to wipe out his consciousness, Dylan could feel his soul becoming weaker. If he continued to remain trapped, it was very likely that his soul would have been wiped out!

Such a possibility made Dylan tremble in fear.

It was not only capable of trapping his body but also capable of wiping out his consciousness. Even a Beyond Grade A was unable to resist it. The terrifying might of the Spacetime Amber truly made him tremble, and he never wanted to experience it again.

Han Xiao then looked around and suddenly said, "The seal has been undone. Where is your ambush? It's time for them to come out."

He had always felt that the Arcane Church would arrange for their troops in the nearby region, and these troops would appear right after the transaction was completed.

"We don't have an ambush," the Arcane Church emissary replied.

"Really? I thought that you guys would try and deal with me. This time, not only will you be able to snatch the Evolution Cube, you guys will also be able to get the Spacetime Amber. I never thought that there really wouldn't be an ambush around..." Han Xiao shook his head and chuckled. "It seems like you guys are really scared of me."

The face of the Arcane Church emissary turned frosty.

Black Star had already used his strength to prove himself. In consideration for the other allies that were still sealed, they did not intend to take any risks. Furthermore, they were located at the border between both the civilizations, and the dynasty still had their guard up. It would be impossible for them to prepare an ambush.

Of course, aside from all these excuses, the truth was that they were truly afraid.

It was because Han Xiao said the truth that his words stabbed right into their hearts.

The Arcane Church emissary gritted his teeth and replied, "Since our transaction is complete, we shall take our leave. I hope that we will be able to complete similar transactions in the future."

Han Xiao then stroked his chin and said, "Are you just going to leave like that, Dylan? Do you want to stay behind and catch up with me?"

The Arcane Church emissary immediately became wary and asked, "Your Excellency Black Star, what do you want to do?"

The transaction location was located at the border because both parties were wary of each other. The dynasty was afraid that the Arcane Church might launch another ambush, and the Arcane Church was afraid that the dynasty would go back on their word and capture Dylan again. With both parties wary of each other, it was extremely easy for the Arcane Church to misunderstand Han Xiao's words.

"Why are you so nervous? Are you afraid that I will snatch him back?" Han Xiao smirked.

The Arcane Church emissary remained silent and did not respond.

Dylan then gritted his teeth and replied, "I will pay a visit to the Black Star Army in the future if there is a chance!"

"Then I hope that you will come with good will." Han Xiao raised his brows. "If not, history will probably repeat itself."

Upon hearing that, Dylan shrunk back and did not say another word.

A few rays of light then landed on Dylan and the others, sucking them back into the battleship.

Han Xiao looked at Dylan ascending into the sky and the Arcane Church fleet leaving the planet.

"The transaction is complete. Let's return."

Han Xiao patted the emissary on the shoulders with a teasing look on his face.

The Arcane Church would definitely ask Dylan about how he felt when he was sealed. Dylan would cooperate, and the Arcane Church would know that the seal could cause the death of one's consciousness.

The Arcane Church originally was not clear that being sealed by the Spacetime Amber had a risk of death, and after receiving the report from Dylan, they would be anxious to release the seals on the others.

This way, they would be at a disadvantage in their negotiations with the dynasty. In order to save time, they would have to accept some more ridiculous terms from the dynasty.

Their outcome could only be described with a single word—pitiful.

"Heh, I extorted a great deal out of them again." Han Xiao chuckled.

The happiness of an individual was usually built upon the suffering of others.

The transaction went smoothly, and Han Xiao followed the fleet back to the border outpost. He then received news from the upper echelons that the Arcane Church would send their Beyond Grade A combatants to participate in the operation to kill EsGod.

The allies who agreed to participate in the operation were already headed to the gathering point before heading over to Primeval Star River together.

Milizaus then came over to Han Xiao. "Black Star, I am preparing to head over to the gathering point. Do you have anything else to do?"

"I also planned to go now."

"Alright, then let's go together. My injuries from the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter haven't healed yet. Do you still have that medicine?"

"Oh, I still have the medicine, but... you should understand the meaning of equal exchange, right?"

"Speak, how much dragon's blood do you want? Do you want mine?"

"Cough cough. Let's talk along the way." Han Xiao's mouth cramped up.

Indeed, as long as an individual broke their bottom line once, there would be a second time.

Milizaus originally refused to give Han Xiao his own blood, but after seeing Han Xiao gather quite a bit of his blood, he decided to just give up entirely. Since the other party already had his blood, a little more would not make a difference.

They did not remain at the border any longer and set off together.

The security in the dynasty was pretty good, and apart from Milizaus being a little anemic, they did not face any problems along the way. They were the first to reach the gathering point and waited for their allies to join them.

...

At the same time, in a desolate universe belt of the Primeval Star River, the Fallen Ark floated above a Fixed Star with its energy shield blocking out the powerful radiation.

In the command room of the flagship, Fakisen looked out of the window at a spot on the surface of the Fixed Star, which was where EsGod had landed. A whirlpool-like energy spiral could be seen with EsGod at the center.

The energy of a Fixed Star was far too blinding, and even with his Calamity Grade senses, he was unable to see EsGod's figure clearly. The large energy whirlpool disrupted all the radars on board the spaceship, and the target region was covered with EsGod's Esper Ability. No one was able to see what EsGod was doing on the Fixed Star.

"His Excellency EsGod has made us wait here for two days already. Just what is he doing?" a member of the spaceship asked impatiently.

"I don't know," Fakisen replied.

Two days ago, EsGod got them to await orders outside of this Fixed Star while he landed on the Fixed Star and absorbed energy like a bottomless pit.

At this moment, EsGod had his arms stretched out wide as he absorbed the endless energy of the Fixed Star.

He had an Esper Ability that could absorb the energy of the outside world called 'Black Hole'. He had once displayed this ability when fighting Han Xiao.

As the energy was absorbed into his body, a black fog-like figure separated from EsGod's body and transformed into a black crystal-like item that floated beside EsGod.

This black sphere was a doppelganger created by EsGod from absorbing the crazy amount of energy.

The more powerful an individual, the greater the effects of the Evolution Cube. EsGod's strength received a huge boost, but he could clearly feel that his own body had not been completely transformed. It was as though the evolution energy had sunk into his cells and was like a treasure being sealed in a box.

EsGod did not have an interface and did not know that this was the additional Race Evolution opportunity that he had obtained by using the Evolution Cube. He would only be able to trigger it with a Promotion.

But if he was able to complete this promotion, he would experience a qualitative transformation!

However, the Evolution Cube did not have the ability to increase an individual's level, and thus, EsGod did not receive this energy at the moment.

Although the evolution ability did not allow EsGod to promote, it released some of the restrictions on EsGod's body.

For example, gene load!

Because of the conflict between genes, EsGod's body was not able to contain too many different abilities at the same time. His doppelganger was able to make up for this shortcoming and store certain Esper Abilities, but his main body could not make use of these abilities.

However, there was an obvious disadvantage to this method. The doppelganger created by EsGod was not without any burdens because maintaining the doppelganger required the activation of an Esper Ability.

If EsGod was like a computer, every Esper Ability would be like a program. The upper limit of his main body would be like his RAM, and maintaining a doppelganger was like running a program in the background. It would constantly take up his RAM.

The more powerful his doppelganger and the more doppelgangers he had at the same time, the more RAM it would require.

He needed his RAM to have extra space for him to use other Esper Abilities.

Thus, EsGod would not use his doppelgangers during a head on battle mainly because of this reason. The presence of his doppelgangers would reduce the combat capabilities of his main body.

However, the Evolution Cube had changed this.

Simply put, it increased his RAM and simplified his programs.

The upper limit of his main body was increased, and the load of every Esper Ability was reduced. This meant that he would be able to use more Esper Abilities at the same time.

This strengthened EsGod's abilities to a large extent!

As such, EsGod was now capable of supporting more Beyond Grade A doppelgangers.

The change in quantity resulted in a change in quality!

It could be said that the improvement from the Evolution Cube changed EsGod's combat strategy!

EsGod was currently sucking up energy from the Fixed Star so that he could create a large number of doppelgangers and prepare for the enemy's revenge!

Since he had frustrated the Arcane Church and the Crimson Dynasty, it would only be a matter of time before both of them attempted to surround him. Since both parties seemed like they were about to take action, he naturally made his own preparations.

EsGod treasured his life a lot as he would only be able to fulfil his wishes if he remained alive. However, he was not afraid of danger either as he would only be able to become stronger by fighting.

The attack of a Universal Civilization would definitely be a good opportunity for him to test his strength. He would only be able to understand his own strength after fighting with other Beyond Grade As.

The attack this time was also an opportunity to him even though the meaning was slightly different.

This was his first battle after his evolution!

EsGod was truly excited in his heart.

He would only know just how strong he had become after testing his strength out.

Chapter 890: Mission Triggered

The gathering point for the dynasty's troops was in a military region. This was a key Inter-Star Field Stargate relay point, and the stargate being guarded by the military would lead them directly to the Primeval Star River.

The military stargates of the three Universal Civilizations led to many different regions. With the Central Galaxy as the middle, they had stargates that could reach all the various Star Fields. This was the foundation of protecting their status as the ruler of the universe.

After waiting for a few days, the other few dynasty allies participating in the mission also arrived. After the seven of them were gathered, they boarded the main flagship for their expedition.

In the command room, the seven of them gathered together and greeted each other.

Since they were going to work together, it was important for them to know each other.

During his first trip to the dynasty's mother planet, Kohler was also present, so they had met before. Lotus Swordsman was the only dynasty ally that he was meeting for the first time.

"Your Excellency Black Star," Lotus Swordsman said with a calm expression.

"Hello. This is the first time we are meeting, right?" Han Xiao replied politely and stretched out his hand.

Lotus Swordsman then looked at Han Xiao's palms and hesitated for a moment. She then shook her head and said, "I don't like others touching my body. I'm sorry."

"I understand." Han Xiao was not too bothered and retracted his arm. There were many Beyond Grade As with their own habits, and he would respect the other party.

Right at this moment, Milizaus' magical doppelganger walked over and patted Han Xiao on the shoulder. "Her Excellency Lotus will be our sharpest sword. Her Psychic abilities are very unique and have a strong penetrative ability."

"It isn't that exaggerated," Lotus Swordsman said. "EsGod also has abilities to protect his soul."

"Compared to his other abilities, his soul can be considered a weakness."

Han Xiao nodded upon hearing that. He had fought EsGod three times in total, and together with the information from his previous life, he had a pretty good understanding of EsGod's abilities.

EsGod's most frightening advantage was his ability to collect various Esper Abilities, which allowed him to have almost no weaknesses.

He had high mobility abilities such as 'Dimension Crack' and 'Instantaneous Movement'. He also had abilities like 'Strengthened Self Recovery' and 'Black Hole' to increase his safety. On top of that, he had various powerful attacks, control techniques, defense techniques, and mental attacks. Compared to his physical defense, EsGod's soul was not as powerful. As such, it would be the most effective to launch a soul attack.

Everyone chatted for a while, and the commander of the flagship walked in. He gave a military salute to the seven Beyond Grade As and said with a deep voice, "The fleet has completed its preparations, and we shall head to the Primeval Star River if there isn't a problem."

As one of the three pillars in the dynasty, Milizaus had the highest status in the team. He looked around, and upon seeing that no one had any objections, he nodded.

"Let's go."

"Okay."

The commander then walked forward to the control panel and gave a strict order. "The EsGod encirclement mission shall officially commence. All forces set off!"

The dynasty fleet began moving toward the stargate.

Right at this moment, Han Xiao's expression changed slightly.

The instant the commander announced the commencement of the mission, two notifications popped up on his interface!

The first mission that he triggered was [The Battle of the Empire: The Fallen Ark (Repeatable)]. This was a faction mission that Han Xiao had completed before.

The mission objectives required him to kill different numbers and types of Fallen Ark members with the highest reward being for him to deal with EsGod.

He would be able to obtain a certain amount of experience and Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points if he reduced EsGod's health by a certain amount. Furthermore, he would obtain an EsGod Character Summon Card if he was able to kill EsGod's doppelganger.

The second mission was called [Archenemy of the Three Universal Civilizations].

Archenemy of the Three Universal Civilizations

Mission Introduction: Chaos breeds order, and order gives rise to chaos. Chaos and order were extreme opposites while also different sides to the same coin. The three Universal Civilizations have explored the universe and are the manifestation of order. EsGod, on the other hand, is the representative of chaos and violence. In his unscrupulous pursuit for strength, he was bestowed with the titles 'Butcher of Life', 'Guide of the Crazy Believer', and so on. All the ferocious individuals in the universe have gathered under him, and he spreads fear everywhere. The three Universal Civilizations are extremely eager to get rid of this tumor and have chosen to work together to achieve this objective. You have been chosen to participate in this glorious mission.

Mission Requirements: Follow the three Universal Civilizations to deal with EsGod.

Reward: Rewards will be given according to the damage dealt to EsGod—both his main body and doppelgangers will be included—as a percentage. You will be entitled to a Random Reward if you reach 20%, [Character Summon Card: EsGod] if you reach 75%, and if your damage exceeds 100% of EsGod's health, it will be counted as 100%.

Additional Mission Requirements: Work together with the three Universal Civilizations and capture or kill EsGod.

Additional Reward: Randomly select three of EsGod's abilities. You will be able to select his skill or talent every time, and you can choose to split it into three draws or draw them in one go.

"The mission has been assigned." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Indeed, for a large event such as the three Universal Civilizations encircling EsGod, there would definitely be a mission.

He had already done the first mission before and did not pay much attention to it. The second mission was the main point, which seemed to have been triggered by the three Universal Civilizations working together.

It could be said that their cooperation was a result of his actions, and thus, he was the one who created this mission.

EsGod had a body full of treasures, and drawing his abilities would definitely give Han Xiao great rewards. Furthermore, the Random Reward this time was slightly different.

In the past, he would not be able to select the type of reward being drawn and would draw both skills and talents. This time, he was able to designate the type of ability being drawn, and the number of abilities had also increased. On top of that, he was also able to split it up into three different draws, which meant that he could increase the options from five to fifteen, thus increasing his possibilities.

However, the more plentiful the reward, the harder the mission.

EsGod's strength after evolution was still an unknown factor. Apart from being excited about the reward of the mission, Han Xiao also worried about the success rate of the mission.

Han Xiao then looked around, and the faces of the other allies were all calm. Although they knew that they were about to deal with EsGod, none of them seemed anxious. Only he knew the outcome of their actions.

This would determine the direction of the entire universe!

It also affected whether he would be able to develop safely in the future.

In order to get rid of the hidden danger of the World Tree Civilization, he had to get rid of EsGod even if there was no reward.

Thinking about this, Han Xiao calmed himself down.

The dynasty had already created an advantageous situation, so we will have to see the situation of the actual battle...

...

The Primeval Star River was a vast Star Field that was even larger than the Shattered Star Ring. It was split into thirty-one Star Clusters and controlled by four Super Star Cluster Civilizations. The level of prosperity in the region was comparable to the Sea of Star Spirits and belonged to the second rung in the universe. The first rung would naturally be the Central Galaxy.

Because the three Universal Civilizations controlled the Central Galaxy strictly, the second rung Star Fields such as the Primeval Star River had plenty of different civilizations and became extremely active. For example, the headquarters of the Ancient Ones were located in the Primeval Star River.

Historically, the Primeval Star River had once been glorious, and during the exploration era, the Primeval Star River was the main camp of a quasi-Universal Civilization. This civilization was a powerful competitor to the three Universal Civilizations of today but was not able to survive past the cruel exploration era.

Back then, many local Star Cluster and Star System Civilizations also perished in the war and left behind a large number of ruins. According to the number of ruins, the Primeval Star River was only second to the Ancient Star Desert. At the same time, the Primeval Star River had many desolate universe belts that were natural hiding spots.

Because they had a mission to complete, the dynasty fleet did not delay and headed straight to the gathering point.

A few days later, the Federation of Light and Arcane Church's fleets arrived and met up with the dynasty's fleet.

Han Xiao saw the manpower being sent by the other two parties.

The Arcane Church sent three.

The Federation of Light sent one.

Together with the dynasty, there were a total of eleven Beyond Grade As!

Even the scale of the battle on Planet Lighthouse was about the same.

Chapter 891: Plan and Meeting

In some locations of the Primeval Star River, the fleets of the Arcane Church, the Crimson Dynasty, and the Federation of Light gathered together with the eleven participating Beyond Grade As gathered together in the dynasty's conference room to discuss their strategy.

"According to our intelligence, EsGod is currently at this location."

A holographic projection displayed the star map of the Primeval Star River, and a red dot could be seen in a desolate universe belt. This red dot represented EsGod's location, and the commander of the dynasty fleet described the situation to everyone present solemnly.

The objective of the three fleets was to deal with EsGod's fleet, and the commander's mission was to work together with the Beyond Grade A allies.

"Hmm, that is an ancient battlefield with many planets destroyed in the exploration era. There's a large number of meteoroids in that region." Manison nodded in agreement. He was a local of the Primeval Star River and was familiar with the situation here.

The single Beyond Grade A that the Federation of Light had sent out was Manison, but he did not go personally. He only sent a mechanical host with three mechanical fortresses, which had a large number of mechanical soldiers stored within.

Although he was alone, the troops that he had brought with him made him no weaker than the other two factions present.

An Arcane Church Beyond Grade A then knocked on the table and said, "We only received a report on EsGod's troops. Where did this report come from? Is it reliable?"

"This is the intelligence provided by a Super Star Cluster Civilization in the Primeval Star River. They have a complete surveillance system in the Primeval Star River," the dynasty commander replied solemnly. "After receiving intelligence on EsGod's fleet, they began tracking his fleet. According to the coordinates that he provided, we made use of a long-distance tracking tool to verify it, and I guarantee the accuracy of the intelligence."

The four Super Star Cluster Civilizations controlled the entire Primeval Star River and had plenty of eyes everywhere. At the request of the dynasty, they provided information on EsGod's location and worked together. However, they were not aware that the three Universal Civilizations were going to work together.

With EsGod's location locked on to, they would rush over with the stargate network to ambush EsGod.

The three Arcane Church Beyond Grade As that the Arcane Church sent out had not participated in the battle on Planet Lighthouse. Their classes were Psychic, Mage, and Cannon Master. Thus, not a single one of the eleven Beyond Grade As present were Espers.

The individual worth paying attention to was the Cannon Master who had the nickname 'Sun Hunter'. He was a member of the Ancient Ones and also the strongest of the three sent by the Arcane Church. He was old friends with Manison, Milizaus, and Ravenlaude.

His body was lean, only the thickness of a palm. However, his body was extremely tall, and he was a universal species that was endangered. He had the characteristics of a bug and was currently clad in armor.

His body was skinny, but his weapons were tens of thousands of times larger than him.

Han Xiao remembered Aesop mentioning him before and said that there were a few Ancient Ones trying to find out information about him. Sun Hunter was one of them.

He originally thought that this Cannon Master wanted to get him to craft weapons, but after considering it for a while, Han Xiao eliminated such a possibility. An Ancient One did not need to invite a new Beyond Grade A Mechanic to help him craft weapons.

At the start of the meeting, Han Xiao had his attention on the teammates from the other two factions. There was no need to talk about Manison; his mechanical body was completely expressionless. On the side of the Arcane Church, they seemed to be unfriendly toward the dynasty's allies and Manison.

Han Xiao still did not know that the Ten Thousand Deity Scepter had been snatched by the Federation of Light, and the Arcane Church was currently the most infuriated at the Federation of Light for taking advantage of their situation and hitting them when they were down. The Beyond Grade A allies of the Arcane Church naturally would not be too friendly toward Manison.

If not for the fact that they had to deal with a common enemy, both parties would probably have ended up in a fight.

"Since we have already grasped EsGod's location, the initiative of the battle will be in our hands. We need a plan," Milizaus said.

"You're right," Sun Hunter replied. Although his body was small, his voice was not soft. "Although EsGod is a battle maniac who likes fighting, he isn't a rash individual. The moment he sees the eleven of us together, he will escape for sure. As long as he abandons his fleet and escapes, we won't be able to catch up. The outcome will then be the same as before."

"With so many Beyond Grade As working together, we definitely aren't putting up a show and plan to get rid of EsGod," Han Xiao said with a solemn expression. "If we want to succeed, there are two problems we need to take care of. First, we cannot let EsGod escape the moment he sees us. Second, we must restrict EsGod's mobility so that he cannot escape whenever he wishes."

Everyone else nodded.

Although the three Universal Civilizations had failed in all their attempts to kill EsGod, an operation of such a scale was extremely rare. A portion of the Beyond Grade A allies present there were only interested in the reward, not EsGod's life or death. However, with so many of them taking action against EsGod alone, it would be pretty embarrassing if they failed.

Thus, all of them present wanted to complete this mission and get rid of this true archenemy of the three Universal Civilizations.

The will of a Beyond Grade A was extremely firm, and they would not be affected by the many past failures in history.

"It is easy to solve the first problem," Manison said. "EsGod wouldn't foolishly clash head on with eleven Beyond Grade As. We just need to split up into two groups. The first group will fight him head on and try to hold him back while the other group lies in wait."

Han Xiao nodded to express his agreement.

EsGod was not a foolish individual and would not attempt to fight eleven Beyond Grade As. Thus, despite having many combatants on their side, they could not appear all at once. If they did, EsGod would run immediately upon seeing them.

"You are right. The first batch of combatants surrounding him must be a reasonable force for an encirclement mission but not be too large that it scares him away," Ravenlaude said. "I think that it would be safer to have four or five Beyond Grade As."

"Five would be the best. EsGod received a round of evolution, and his strength has grown. He will definitely want to test his strength, and five people should be within his expectations," Han Xiao said.

The encirclement missions only had three ordinary Beyond Grade As usually, and EsGod's original combat capability was sufficient for him to take on three ordinary Beyond Grade As without an issue. He would be able to escape even when facing four or five Beyond Grade As. Things would be slightly different if the Beyond Grade As were more powerful, but as long as he wanted to run, no one would be able to keep him behind.

If there were five of them, they would be able to give EsGod pressure and incite his desire to battle but not let EsGod feel that it was too risky and make him run away immediately.

"The first batch of combatants shall be set at five. Three from the dynasty and two from the church. Let's not let EsGod know that the Federation of Light is participating in this mission."

Everyone quickly agreed with that.

Right at this moment, Milizaus suddenly said, "But if we do not restrict EsGod's instantaneous movements, the ambush of the others will be meaningless. Even if we launch a surprise attack, EsGod will be able to escape any time. Thus, it is more important to restrict his mobility, or our operation will fail for sure."

Upon hearing that, the Arcane Church's mage said, "That's right. The five people fighting EsGod head on will be in charge of tying him down and restricting his mobility shall be the job of those ambushing him. This would require spacetime magic to be cast in the battlefield to separate the region from the multi-dimensions and secondary dimension channel. We still need to stabilize the spacetime to prevent him from using any instantaneous movement or hyperdrive. Transforming the battlefield to become a locked region will require a great deal of effort."

Everyone nodded in agreement. This was the best way to trap EsGod, and it was proven by history. However, it was getting more and more difficult to accomplish such a feat.

First, this required a lot of time, and the larger the battlefield, the greater the effort required. Even a Beyond Grade A Mage would not be able to complete it in time. Second, EsGod would keep his guard up and escape before the spacetime could be locked down.

Even if EsGod fell into such a trap, it would still be possible for him to escape. He could use ordinary methods to break through the battlefield or use his Esper Abilities to create a small crack in the spacetime and escape from the locked down region.

During this limited time, it would be impossible for them to defeat or capture EsGod. He was not a fragile target, and his powerful recovery and defenses would drag the battle on for a long time.

"I have the equipment to quickly stabilize space and can reduce EsGod's Dimension Crack and instantaneous movement abilities," Manison said slowly. "I should be able to lock EsGod down temporarily and engineer the chance for an ambush."

He would be able to defeat EsGod alone, but EsGod was far too crafty, and it was difficult for him to catch EsGod. His various space-locking machines required time to activate. By the time he set them up, EsGod would have escaped already.

Furthermore, Han Xiao had rejected his offer, so Manison was not willing to give it his all. The Federation of Light's request did not have too much of a binding power to him, and he only planned to work together with his teammates.

Describing it simply, Manison treated himself as a support and not the carry of the team.

"If we want to create a locked down region, the five people fighting at the start must pin EsGod down in a certain region and not allow him to do as he wishes," Milizaus said slowly. "We have three Mages on our side and can all remain in hiding. Two of us can use our spacetime magic to modify the battlefield while the last can hide the flow of magic and reduce the chances of EsGod discovering us. The ones fighting EsGod head on will also have to work together to distract EsGod. We also need a Psychic to attack his mind to dull his senses."

"We have sufficient manpower, and this isn't difficult to accomplish. However, it won't be enough to succeed..." Ravenlaude hesitated for a moment before speaking the truth. "If EsGod falls into the trap, we will have to get rid of him using the shortest amount of time. If not, all our efforts will go to waste. However, it is extremely difficult to do so with EsGod's abilities."

The entire room then fell silent.

Everyone began to frown.

Although they had plenty of manpower this time, history would only repeat itself if they were not able to take care of this problem.

They all felt a huge headache just by discussing their strategy.

It was extremely difficult to deal with EsGod, and everyone knew that they needed some changes.

Just when everyone was thinking about how they should solve this problem, Han Xiao took a deep breath.

He had two changes in his hands.

The Spacetime Amber and Esper Silence!

These two abilities were definitely enough to turn the situation around and would also make this battle different from before.

Han Xiao then stood up, and everyone looked at him.

Looking at the others, he said slowly, "I have a plan..."

Over ten days later, in a certain desolate universe belt, EsGod's fleet continued to travel according to their designated route after spending a few days by a Fixed Star.

After travelling peacefully for a few days, the fleet's radar detected something.

A dynasty fleet had appeared right in front of them, and both parties were already extremely near each other by the time Fallen Ark detected the other party. The dynasty fleet had made use of their stealth mode to approach the enemy before revealing themselves.

The Fallen Ark fleet did not escape immediately. Instead, both parties stopped at the same time and entered a standoff.

Woo!

The alarms rang inside the Fallen Ark battleship.

In the main hall of the flagship, EsGod opened his eyes.

An expectant look could be seen on his face as he got up from his throne slowly.

"They're finally here. I hope that they can let me fight to my heart's content."

Chapter 892: Upgraded EsGod

Both fleets faced each other in a standoff in the dark universe.

EsGod's figure then disappeared from his throne and appeared beside Fakisen in the control room.

"The other party is the dynasty's armed fleet with almost five million battleships. The strength of their battleships is superior to our fleet. Since they appeared suddenly before us, it means that they can accurately grasp our coordinates. My suggestion is not to fight them but retreat immediately..." Fakisen began analyzing the situation upon seeing EsGod.

However, EsGod ignored him completely and expanded his senses. He could clearly feel three sun-like energy sources from within the dynasty's fleet.

Counting the number of opponents, EsGod revealed a look of disappointment.

"Only three of them?"

Right at this moment, the radar rang out again and an Arcane Church fleet appeared behind them.

After feeling the two Beyond Grade As in the Arcane Church fleet, EsGod's brows began to relax.

"Five people... only then will there be a meaning to fight."

"The Crimson Dynasty has indeed chosen to work together with the Arcane Church. It seems like they have already laid an ambush here and plan to wipe us out with a fleet three times our size. I recommend that we break through their encirclement and retreat immediately," Fakisen said.

EsGod did not even bother looking at him and calmly said, "Inform the fleet to prepare for battle. Hold them back, and don't let the enemy battleships disrupt my battle."

"I understand," Fakisen said with a disappointed tone as if he expected that. He knew that EsGod did not care about their lives and only treated them as tools.

Fakisen then issued an order in front of EsGod and formed a defensive formation.

EsGod nodded, and the next moment, his body appeared outside the battleship.

Following which, a wave of spiritual energy exploded with EsGod as the center. The dynasty and church's fleets had the equipment to block out a certain degree of spiritual energy, but the five Beyond Grade As received EsGod's spiritual fluctuations at the same time to build a communication channel.

Han Xiao was also part of the group, and he heard EsGod's calm voice.

"I have been waiting for a long time."

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao looked at his teammates, and they nodded to each other.

If EsGod decided to run away from the very start, it would be impossible for them to block him. Since EsGod said those words, it meant that he was prepared to stay behind and fight them. If that was the case, the first step of their plan was successful.

Looking at each other, Han Xiao's group of three left the dynasty battleship and entered the universe. The two from the church also flew out of their battleship and surrounded EsGod.

Milizaus and the other two mages hid in the darkness and began locking down the spacetime of the region. Manison also hid the fact that the Federation of Light had participated in this ambush and hid himself. He only passed his spacetime stabilizer to someone else. After some discussion, the five who were assigned to face EsGod head on were Han Xiao, Viru, Lotus Swordsman, Sun Hunter, and another Psychic from the Arcane Church.

The job of the two Psychics was to use their mental attacks. Viru served as the tank, and Sun Hunter was the main damage dealer. As for Han Xiao, his main body was present this time, and he was in charge of control, main tank, physical damage, and many other positions.

EsGod's gaze swept over everybody before landing on Han Xiao. "Black Star, it's you again."

"Since you ambushed me, this day had to come. You knew that, right?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Sigh, destiny is truly strange. I didn't plan on dealing with you, but you still want to pester me. You are truly taking the initiative to seek death... or perhaps it can be said that all of you are seeking death."

EsGod shook his head.

Upon hearing that, Sun Hunter could help but interrupt coldly. "I wonder if that brain of yours still remembers how many times you have been forced back by three Beyond Grade As. When facing the five of us, do you think you will still be able to emerge victorious?"

"Ah, that was the past me. In fact, I still have to thank Black Star for the Evolution Cube. The dynasty and church will regret sending all of you to deal with me."

Even before EsGod could finish what he had to say, Sun Hunter took the initiative to launch an attack, and a modified psionic Particle Cannon appeared beside him. A brilliant bolt of Mechanical Force shot out from his body and filled up the Particle Cannon, with a brilliant beam being shot out from the cannon the very next moment.

EsGod dodged the attack with his instantaneous movement, and a Fallen Ark battleship that was behind him was easily torn apart. The high-density alloy was ripped apart like a piece of paper, and the entire battleship was swallowed by the light and reduced to dust as though it had melted into nothingness.

With the first attack being launched, the dynasty and church fleet opened fire and the Fallen Ark fleet fought back. Both parties exchanged fire, and the dark universe was lit up by the exploding cannons.

The battle had erupted!

Han Xiao's group of five had also launched their attacks.

The Apostle Weapons under the lead of Psionic Prime began to encircle EsGod, Viru charged toward EsGod with his weapon, Lotus Swordsman and the other Psychic began launching their Psychic attacks, and Sun Hunter rapidly opened fire like an artillery tower.

The battlefield instantly became chaotic.

EsGod's combat method was to use various different abilities depending on the surroundings. He would not fight five Beyond Grade As head on. With his instantaneous movement ability, the encirclement of the five did not put that much pressure on him. At the same time, he was able to easily weave through the mechanical army and approach his enemies.

His powerful mobility meant that he had the initiative of the battle in his hands. At the same time, it also guaranteed him his safety as he could just leave whenever he wanted.

As such, EsGod did not intend to leave at the moment but treated the five as useful opponents to test his strength.

However, it was impossible to win against five Beyond Grade As single-handedly. This was a feat that no individual in the universe was capable of accomplishing. It was not just a simple comparison of battle prowess. The dense attacks of five Beyond Grade As would result in an individual being only capable of defending but not attacking. At this moment, EsGod had the initiative and could appear and disappear like a ghost. However, Han Xiao's group of five could support each other, and he was not able to defeat each of them individually.

The battle immediately fell into a stalemate.

Han Xiao had his guard up against EsGod, afraid that EsGod's strength might have improved greatly. But after exchanging a few blows with EsGod, Han Xiao was no longer that worried.

During the battle on Planet Lighthouse, Han Xiao had fought EsGod before and was familiar with EsGod's strength. Although EsGod did have some improvement in strength, it had not reached a qualitative change.

It seems like the Evolution Cube was not sufficient to cause an earth-shattering change in him, and he still belongs to the Beyond Grade A rank.

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief.

If EsGod really broke through the Beyond Grade A rank and entered the so called 'new realm', his combat capability would definitely soar greatly, and there would be a huge gulf between them.

Thankfully, although the Evolution Cube was powerful, it was not sufficient to allow an individual to break through into the next realm.

As he planned for this operation, he had tried his best to overestimate EsGod's strength, but the current strength that EsGod displayed did not reach his expectations. This way, Han Xiao had greater confidence in succeeding.

The other four also had similar thoughts. If EsGod's strength did not exceed their expectations, they would not have too much trouble holding him back.

However, an abrupt change happened!

EsGod used his instantaneous movement to avoid a wave of fire and suddenly sent out a message to Han Xiao and the others.

"Warm up is over."

The moment he said those words, he shot out black spheres from his body. These black spheres were the doppelgangers that he had prepared, and they all transformed into fog-like bodies emanating with energy.

Every doppelganger had a different Esper Ability that EsGod obtained and had a quasi Beyond Grade A strength. Furthermore, there were dozens of these doppelgangers around!

"Why does he have so many doppelgangers‽" Sun Hunter cried out with shock.

Information about EsGod was no secret. Everyone knew that his doppelganger ability had an obvious upper limit, and he was not capable of creating too many doppelgangers. This was already in their records!

Upon witnessing such a scene, Han Xiao's heart shuddered, and he immediately understood what was going on.

The Evolution Cube did not allow EsGod to break through into the next level but expanded his strength at the same realm. It did not increase his 'depth' but increased his 'breadth'. Compared to the other classes, a Mechanic understood just how frightening numbers were. A Mechanic relied on a large mechanical army to increase their strength and achieve a qualitative change.

The upgraded EsGod was also similar in this regard.

EsGod's main body did not achieve a breakthrough in strength, but his ability to produce doppelgangers was improved. There were tens of Beyond Grade A doppelgangers present, and every doppelganger was like half a Beyond Grade A. Even if his doppelgangers were fragile, they had many different Esper Abilities and were still a powerful army.

This meant that the number of Beyond Grade As that Han Xiao's group had to face had increased by dozens of times!

The threat that they faced had also increased greatly!

The three Universal Civilizations had tried to surround EsGod many times before. It was not that they had not sent out more than five Beyond Grade As before, but even if EsGod could not win, he could still retreat.

This time, EsGod already had the strength to deal with five or more Beyond Grade As head on, and he was not satisfied with escaping. If he could fight back or even kill the five Beyond Grade As that the Universal Civilizations sent, his own record would be broken, and he would be able to shock the entire universe.

However, EsGod did not know that he did not only have five opponents but another six hiding in the dark, waiting to ambush him.

The majority of the doppelgangers began to split up and surround Han Xiao's group of five. Instead of the five surrounding EsGod, it was now EsGod surrounding the five.

The remaining doppelgangers entered the battlefield of the battleships and used their Beyond Grade A strength to rapidly wipe out the dynasty and church's fleets. The Fallen Ark fleet that was originally at a disadvantage was gradually regaining ground.

Han Xiao and the other four felt a huge increase in pressure. It was akin to fighting tens of Beyond Grade As with different Esper Abilities at the same time. If not for the aid of the mechanical army, it would have been impossible for the other four to hang in there.

Through his doppelgangers, EsGod could unleash all his Esper Abilities without any restraint. His main body reserved the use of 'Strengthened Self Recovery' and 'Black Hole', and his other doppelgangers had many different Esper Abilities.

In the chaotic battle, Han Xiao looked at EsGod's main body, which did not participate in the encirclement, with a grave look.

EsGod's current appearance truly lived up to his nickname.

The god of all Espers!

Of the five of them, Han Xiao was still alright as he was sufficiently tanky. However, his mechanical army was rapidly being wiped out under the attacks of the many Beyond Grade As, and even his Apostle Weapons were trapped in a bitter battle.

Han Xiao originally wanted to save his 'Perfect Mechanical Sense' Character Summon Card, but he knew that it was impossible for him to do so right now. He immediately activated the Perfect Mechanical Sense Character Summon Card, and his Mechanical Force became thicker.

Han Xiao then endured the crazed attacks of EsGod's doppelgangers and got his mechanical army to open fire at EsGod's doppelgangers.

Every Esper Ability could only be used by a single doppelganger, and most of his doppelgangers did not have tanky abilities and were all very fragile. As such, the rapid attacks of the mechanical army were effective.

Rays of blue light struck the black fog like figures, and a quarter of EsGod's doppelgangers were wiped out.

However, the next scene immediately caused all of them to become nervous again.

EsGod then made use of his Black Hole ability and sucked in all the attacks to create more doppelgangers and replenish the fallen troops.

Everyone's heart sank as they witnessed this scene.

"We're in trouble now..."

"They're in trouble..."

On the other side, the six Beyond Grade As waiting in ambush had also formed a mental network through the Psychic. Their hearts all sank upon finding out about the ability that EsGod had displayed.

"EsGod's doppelganger ability has been strengthened, and even if we are able to successfully lock down spacetime, he would be able to make use of his doppelgangers to drag for time. This plan will not work," Ravenlaude said with a grave tone.

Their plan was to lock down spacetime to trap EsGod and control him according to Han Xiao's plan before he could escape.

However, the strength that EsGod had displayed was out of their expectations. Even if they were able to temporarily trap him, they could not control him before he escaped.

"We still have to give it a try. Don't stop." Milizaus was not confident but could only continue according to plan. They did not have any other choice.

"I wonder how much longer they will be able to hang in there," Manison said calmly.

They could not enter the battle before the trap was complete, and holding EsGod back could only be left to the group of five.

The six of them in ambush were not sure if they could hold on until the trap was completed.

Chapter 893: Appearance

Sharp pugilist flames cleaved EsGod's doppelgangers one after another and reduced them into black mist.

Viru's body was ignited with flames, and he weaved through the battlefield like a meteor. He accurately killed plenty of EsGod's doppelgangers under the cover of the mechanical army and was currently riddled with injuries.

"This fellow has too many doppelgangers, and it is impossible for us to kill them all. Furthermore, he is even able to make new doppelgangers. It will be pointless regardless of how many doppelgangers we kill. At the same time, we will be severely wounded if we are careless, and we are currently too passive," Viru said with a deep voice as he raised up his blade to block an attack from one of EsGod's doppelgangers.

On the other side, Sun Hunter was controlling his fortress-like artillery equipment to rain down fire on EsGod's doppelgangers. His face was extremely ugly, and he replied, "I am exhausting energy too rapidly in such an intense battle. I am not like Black Star and don't have the ability to recover energy so quickly."

The combat capability of EsGod's doppelgangers was not that powerful and was largely decided by the Esper Ability of each doppelganger. EsGod's doppelgangers definitely were not an opponent for a Beyond Grade A, and Psyker had once killed two of EsGod's doppelgangers single-handedly.

However, the situation was now different. The dozens of EsGod doppelgangers brought about immense pressure, and it was akin to facing dozens of Beyond Grade As at the same time. Furthermore, it was impossible to completely wipe out the enemy. It was truly troublesome.

Facing the encirclement of the doppelgangers, everyone was riddled with injuries, and apart from Han Xiao, the other four had limited recovery ability. Furthermore, such an intense battle also drained them of their attention and energy greatly. Apart from Han Xiao, the other four were gradually slipping up.

Han Xiao's brows were locked tightly as he controlled the mechanical army to block EsGod's doppelgangers. His mechanical army had been reduced to scrap many times over, and he used [Waste Modification] to send them back into the battle over and over again.

Mechanical soldiers were not afraid of death, and with their dense psionic cannon attacks, the mechanical soldiers killed far more doppelgangers than the others.

Thankfully, his mechanical army, which had been strengthened many times, had powerful attributes, which reduced the loss of the army. With the aid of his four teammates, they were still barely able to achieve a stalemate.

However, the upgraded EsGod was far more frightening in terms of sustained combat. As long as he was given enough time, the entire mechanical army would definitely be wiped out. Han Xiao had no choice but to admit that it would be extremely difficult for him to win against EsGod if he fought EsGod alone.

However, this was not a one-on-one battle, and he did not need to defeat EsGod alone. His current mission was to hold EsGod back and restrict him to this battlefield. They only needed to hold on until their teammates were done setting up the trap.

Han Xiao was extremely clear that if the five of them could not hold EsGod back, forcing the six in ambush to come out and save them, it was very likely that EsGod would escape immediately. The trap was not set at the moment, and if they could not hold EsGod back, the operation would fail for sure.

Han Xiao then turned around to look at EsGod's main body, which was seated crossed legged in space. New doppelgangers were formed every second.

After using his doppelganger technique, EsGod's main body retreated to the side and did not participate in the battle personally. As his doppelgangers engaged in a bitter battle with the enemy, he watched with interest.

He did not need to take action personally; just his doppelgangers were enough to reduce the five Beyond Grade As to such a pathetic state. EsGod enjoyed such a feeling of strength.

Sun Hunter and Viru had tried to break out of the encirclement and approach EsGod, but EsGod's instantaneous movement made it impossible for them to approach him. Even Han Xiao could not attack EsGod's main body, so he had plenty of abilities that could not be used.

He could only wait for EsGod's instantaneous movement to be restricted before he had the chance to make use of his trump cards.

With his current strength, even if he did not use any Character Summon Cards, Han Xiao's personal strength was sufficient to last a long time. His new talents brought his health up to about 5,000,000 HP, so he was extremely tanky.

Only Lotus Swordsman and the other Psychic could restrict EsGod slightly. They continuously unleashed their mental attacks on EsGod with their attacks being like swords stabbing at EsGod's mental defenses.

Regardless of how many doppelgangers EsGod had, he only had a single soul, and the two's Psychic attacks were effective against his main body.

However, EsGod also had Esper Abilities to guard his mind and repair any soul damage. Although he would suffer from mental damage, he would not be so easily restricted by the two.

Because the two Psychics possessed a certain degree of threat toward him, EsGod's main target was not Han Xiao, Sun Hunter, or Viru. Instead, it was the two Psychics. Thus, Han Xiao got his Apostle Weapons to lead a special team of mechanical soldiers to guard the two.

Psionic Prime's spear stabbed the core of EsGod's doppelganger, Mad Sky Hunter chewed on the head of a doppelganger, Silver Flash opened fire at a doppelganger, and Giant King Kong used his Divine Giant Armor and large body to protect the two Psychics and other Apostle Weapons.

The Apostle Weapons also had quasi Beyond Grade A battle strength, and they engaged EsGod's doppelgangers in a bitter battle.

...

A portion of EsGod's doppelgangers entered the dynasty and church's fleets to destroy their battleships.

One EsGod doppelganger shot through the shield of the battleship and pierced through the battleship.

Right at this moment, countless dark energy cannons shot over from all directions and reduced this EsGod doppelganger to dust.

In the flagship, the dynasty commander said with a solemn expression, "The damage of the fleet is increasing, and we aren't able to destroy the Fallen Ark fleet with these doppelgangers distracting us. Things will be bad if they continue to drag on."

Since the five Beyond Grade As could not hold EsGod back, the fleet would suffer from the attacks of the Beyond Grade A doppelgangers. The EsGod doppelgangers then weaved around the fleet and caused a great deal of chaos while disrupting the battleships in battle. As such, the fleet led by Fakisen was barely able to hold on and not get wiped out.

The Fallen Ark fleet formed a defensive formation in the center and endured the attacks which came from all directions. Fakisen directed the fleet while paying attention to EsGod's battle.

"His Excellency EsGod's strength is becoming more and more frightening," Fakisen said with hesitation.

"That's right. He is able to deal with five Beyond Grade As so easily. He is EsGod indeed," a vice commander said with reverence in his eyes.

Fakisen then said with a strange tone, "Even five Beyond Grade As aren't able to win against EsGod, and this isn't even His Excellency EsGod's limit. The three large civilizations sent too few people and have truly underestimated him. Tsk tsk."

Fakisen then summoned an officer.

"You shall take command of the fleet now."

"What do you want to do?"

"Ah ah, I still have something else to do. This is a secret mission that His Excellency EsGod handed over to me."

Fakisen then turned around, left the command room, and headed to a spaceship hangar.

He knew that EsGod was already beginning to become suspicious of him. After EsGod took care of the present danger, he would probably be next. EsGod would never need evidence when getting rid of his subordinates.

Besides, regardless of whether EsGod was able to survive this encirclement, Fakisen was not planning on remaining by EsGod's side.

...

The intense battle lasted a long time, and apart from Han Xiao, the other four were riddled with injuries. The mechanical army had also suffered great losses and was gradually becoming weaker.

EsGod looked at the few who were extremely pathetic and sent out a mental message with satisfaction.

"Black Star, do you see this? This is the strength that you have given me. What do you think about it?"

Han Xiao then used the amber ball formation to block an incoming attack and snorted in response. "It isn't much."

EsGod was not bothered by the reply and continued, "Ah, although I haven't broken through the Beyond Grade A limits, my strength should already be the peak of the entire explored universe. The five of you do not even have any chance of fighting back before me."

As Sun Hunter heard that, he immediately aimed his cannon at EsGod and fired.

This time, EsGod did not avoid the attack but used his body to receive the attack. He then activated his Black Hole ability and absorbed the attack to create a few more doppelgangers.

The remaining force from the attack charred his skin and disfigured him completely.

But the next moment, his injuries recovered rapidly, and his appearance went back to normal. His recovery speed was no slower than Han Xiao.

"A useless attack." EsGod glanced at Sun Hunter before looking at Han Xiao. "Black Star, you are not the only one with an indestructible body."

Han Xiao replied with an expressionless face, "Every time you repair your body, your cell's activeness will be exhausted. When your cells reach their upper limit, your life span will also come to an end. This is the disadvantage of a self-healing ability."

"That's right. I am already old. Every time I fight, my lifespan would be burnt up," EsGod said calmly. "However, your Evolution Cube increased my life span by a great deal, and it is enough for me to use. At the very least, you won't have a chance in this battle."

EsGod's current strength came from the evolution energy, and thus, he treated Han Xiao differently.

"Do you really think that you have won?" Sun Hunter interrupted coldly.

"Oh? Please give me a good surprise if you guys still have any unused trump cards. In a while, you guys won't even have the strength to escape," EsGod said with confidence in his voice. "After getting rid of the few of you here, the Arcane Church and the Crimson Dynasty will definitely be infuriated. I also do not have any interest in facing the next wave of enemies, so letting all of you go will be the best option. However, if all of you do not wish to escape, I don't mind killing you."

Through this battle, EsGod had already tested his own combat strength, and defeating this wave of enemies was sufficient to prove his strength. As long as he did not kill them, the three great civilizations would not bother him for a period of time. He wanted to remain low profile for some time to familiarize himself with his strength after the evolution. Thus, he truly did not wish to kill Han Xiao's group.

If not, a Universal Civilization would not let the matter rest after suffering such a huge loss, and that did not suit his current objectives. Thus, he hoped that Han Xiao's group would willingly retreat.

Han Xiao then looked around at his comrades. They had injuries all over their bodies and were not in good states.

Just as EsGod had said, it was impossible for the five of them to do anything against EsGod. If the battle continued, their lives would possibly be in danger.

Right at this moment, Han Xiao suddenly laughed and said, "EsGod, do you know that I am extremely clear about the threat you pose?"

"My threat?" EsGod raised his brows. "My deeds are spread all across the universe. Is there a need for you to emphasize on them?"

"No, I am not talking about that." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

"I don't get what you are talking about," EsGod said.

Han Xiao chuckled and was not planning to explain himself.

EsGod purposely revealed information about the wormhole because he wanted the other organizations to investigate the matter together with him. However, he hid information about the World Tree Civilization, and EsGod thought that he was the only one who knew the existence of the World Tree Civilization.

In truth, EsGod was not wrong in thinking so. No one else apart from Han Xiao knew about this secret and would fall for EsGod's trap to help EsGod research this wormhole. EsGod's wish was to open this channel and fish for benefits from the side.

However, EsGod could not have known that Han Xiao also knew about the existence of the World Tree Civilization. He was the second person in the explored universe to know about this, and EsGod was still in the dark regarding this.

It was because of the lack of information that EsGod was not clear about how resolute Han Xiao was about killing him. According to his past experience, there should be four to six Beyond Grade As coming to encircle him, so five was within his expectations.

As such, he never imagined that there would be far more than five Beyond Grade As coming to encircle him!

Right when Han Xiao finished what he had to say, an abrupt change happened.

EsGod's expression changed greatly as he could clearly feel a spacetime magic spreading out to cover the entire region. The secondary dimension was cut off, and spacetime was locked down. The space in this region became extremely sturdy without any cracks.

At the same time, Han Xiao also activated the space stabilizing equipment that Manison had given him and covered EsGod within it to prevent EsGod from escaping before the trap was formed.

Losing the ability of instantaneous movement, EsGod no longer had the initiative. EsGod then detected another six energy sources appearing from afar, rapidly approaching him.

Milizaus' group of six appeared on the battlefield and surrounded him.

Upon seeing that, EsGod's expression darkened, and a look of shock could be seen in his eyes.

"Why are there another six more‽"

Chapter 894: Key Variable in the Operation

Everyone was treated equally under the spacetime lock. Mechanics were unable to open their secondary dimension channel, and the Dimension Crack and teleportation of EsGod also lost its effect.

With the universe continuously being explored, the three Universal Civilizations had recorded all sorts of Esper Abilities and had developed counters or restraints toward most of them. Except for some Super High Risk Esper Abilities, there was no unsolvable ability.

"Turns out, this was a trap. You guys are really willing to pay."

EsGod was surprised but quickly regained his calm.

This was also not the first time he faced such danger, so he did not panic. While the number of the enemies was more than what he expected, with not only the Crimson Dynasty and the Arcane Church, even the Federation of Light was also involved.

There were eleven Beyond Grade As surrounding him, which outstripped his expectations.

If it were not for the fact that the Universal Civilizations had sent out enough manpower this time, it would have been difficult to make him fall into the trap. Just to fight him head on and not make him think it was a trap would already require at least four to five people, and there was still a need to ensure three mages could set up the spacetime lock secretly. That meant at least seven to eight Beyond Grade As were needed to complete the entire ambush. This was a completely different concept from having seven to eight ordinary people.

Upon realizing that he had fallen for the trap, EsGod did not talk further and immediately reacted.

He would not sit there and await death. While his teleportation was blocked in this area, he could still fly. As long as he flew in the opposite direction of Han Xiao and the others, the moment he escaped the range of the spacetime lock, he would be able to teleport again.

He was not an iron-headed person. When facing eleven other Beyond Grade As, he had no plans to fight them head on.

The six people involved in directly fighting him at the start were still chasing him, and they had yet to completely surround him. Because of the spacetime lock, they were unable to activate the hyperdrive to arrive immediately, so there were only five people who were able to suppress EsGod at the moment.

Han Xiao did not speak further, ditching Sun Hunter and the others, and pouring all of his energy into the mechanical suit propulsion module.

A blue flame burst out from the thrusters from his back, elbows, and feet, and his entire figure shot forward in pursuit of EsGod, leaving a dark blue arc in the universe like a comet.

The spacetime lock did not differentiate between allies or enemies, so his hyperdrive and Void abilities could not be used.

Many of EsGod's doppelgangers turned to hold Han Xiao back, stopping him from pursuing the true body.

While he had fallen into the trap, EsGod did not mind it too much.

He might have been in danger before his evolution, but things were different now. A large number of his doppelgangers were enough to contain his pursuers and give him enough time to escape the spacetime lock.

"Don't let him get away!" Sun Hunter shook a doppelganger off before unfolding a gigantic sniper rifle. He aimed it toward EsGod and fired.

A golden energy beam blasted out, with a tracking function toward EsGod. The speed of the beam was obviously faster than his flight speed, and the distance was quickly shortened.

EsGod frowned, only having the time to deploy a shield before the beam hit.

He originally wished to utilize the repulsion force to retreat even further, but the firearm used by Sun Hunter was not offensive in nature. The moment the beam hit EsGod, it swelled violently, turning into a ball of energy with a powerful suction force, dragging EsGod toward it. EsGod's speed dropped sharply, and the latter had no choice but to continue struggling to get out of the gravitational range.

Ranged attacks were the strength of a Cannon Master, and among the team, Sun Hunter's skills had the best effect against restraining escaping enemies. Furthermore, a Cannon Master did not only have one weapon. They were good at using a variety of firearms, not only offensive ones but also crowd control ones, such as the beam used against EsGod previously.

EsGod could not teleport, so his evasiveness was lowered. Being harassed by Sun Hunter, and with Han Xiao's mechanical suit speed originally being quicker than EsGod, their distance gradually closed.

Luckily, Milizaus and the mages did not underestimate EsGod, and thus, they purposely enlarged the area of spacetime lock, ensuring that there was enough leeway to chase him down.

As EsGod's back slowly grew bigger in his field of vision, Han Xiao estimated the distance before taking out a compressed orb with a flip of his palm. It transformed into a hexagonal alloy board, tens of meters in length with a slight curve to it. It was powered by a core of sub-psionic energy.

This was a Unidirectional Adsorption Gravity Device that Han Xiao had spent a few months creating. It could adjust the direction and strength of gravity, and it was mainly used for attraction.

Based on his tests, at full power, the gravitational force generated could reach the level of a planet's gravity. This gravity was enough to peel off the crust from a planet and achieve the power to tear apart the surface of a planet.

Even for a Beyond Grade A, this was an extremely strong means of crowd control, many levels higher than the spaceship traction beam.

Han Xiao activated the equipment, and a strong attraction force covered the entire area in front of him. EsGod only felt a huge pulling force acting on him, as though an entire star wished to devour him.

EsGod frowned, and with a thought, he split out another new doppelganger, which threw itself toward the attracting force, rushing up to Han Xiao to obstruct him.

This doppelganger only had the goal of destroying the gravitational attraction equipment, so it flew along with the attraction, its flight speed not affected.

Han Xiao activated his psionic shield, blocking the advance of the doppelganger. However, the doppelganger also possessed a battle strength at Beyond Grade A, so it was not so easy to deal with. Han Xiao's speed also took a hit. EsGod shot out a timely black and red energy beam to hit Han Xiao, conveniently using the repulsion to move further away.

"EsGod can continuously produce doppelgangers. The moment I come too close, I'll be obstructed by the doppelgangers. If I cannot hold him, I can only watch as he escapes," Han Xiao murmured, and having made his choice, the Mechanical Force around his body immediately flickered and condensed into a large arc of electricity that bound up EsGod's doppelganger.

The next moment, Han Xiao's consciousness stretched into the quantum network.

Soul attacks, I can do that too!

_____________________

You have utilized Virtual Soul against EsGod!

Attribute Judgment in progress...

Character level judgment failure, -30% success rate.

LUK Attribute judgment failure, -20% success rate.

MYS Attribute judgment failure, -30% success rate.

INT Attribute judgement Success, +40% success rate.

One of the above four judgments is effective. Skill is successfully launched!

Based on your Virtual Technology level, the basic success rate is 424%. After taking into account various judgements, final theoretical success rate: 384%

Calculation of the opponent's abnormal status resistance in progress... Calculations complete, final success rate: 76%

Final Judgment in progress... Judgement successful

Skill (Virtual Soul) is effective.

_____________________

In front, EsGod's body suddenly lurched to a stop. His soul was virtualized by Han Xiao, thrown into the quantum network and hence lost control of his body. The attracting force pulled him backward once again.

EsGod's weakness lay in his spiritual level. Because his doppelgangers and true body all shared the same soul, the [Virtual Soul] skill that Han Xiao utilized on the doppelganger could also be effective on his true body.

Because of the large difference in attributes, the duration of [Virtual Soul] was only for a short while and even had a cooldown of fifteen minutes. But this was enough for Han Xiao to close the remaining distance.

The quantum network was Han Xiao's home field, and his consciousness transformed into a luminous giant that covered the sky and the sun. He grabbed onto EsGod and pummeled him, all attacks converting into spiritual damage to EsGod.

The duration of [Virtual Soul] ended quickly, and clarity shone again in EsGod's eyes, but the soul damage he received made him look weary.

Upon surveying his surroundings, EsGod discovered that his true body was now in front of Han Xiao. Without any additional words, Han Xiao pounced on him.

Seeing this, EsGod knew that he could not escape anymore. The reason he escaped was not because he could not fight them off but because remaining within the trap would leave him the passive one.

As they fought, EsGod continuously released doppelgangers to strengthen his damage output. However, Han Xiao was akin to a sticky plaster. His HP and resistance was too high in addition to having the amber ball as a shield. EsGod got more frustrated the more they battled, as he was fully held back by Han Xiao.

"You irritating fool!" EsGod thundered.

"Thank you for the praise." Han Xiao smiled, his hands suddenly jetting out a Psionic Impact, directly shattering a doppelganger.

At the same time, the six involved in the ambush had started to surround them, and Sun Hunter's side had also eliminated several doppelgangers.

Because all the new doppelgangers created by EsGod were trapped by Han Xiao, there were no new reinforcements on that side, so they could catch up with EsGod after being relieved of the pressure.

Before long, all the Beyond Grade As arrived, each one taking a position and surrounding EsGod. Han Xiao's mechanical army and Manison's Mechanic Empire stood at each path of escape.

Seeing this, Han Xiao also stopped attacking for the time being, retreating into his mechanical army formation.

EsGod was completely surrounded, and from his position, he could only see densely packed mechanical soldiers. The energy signatures of the eleven Beyond Grade As burned his olfactory sense organs. His doppelgangers were recalled back, stationed around him for protection.

In the distance, the fleet of the Federation of Light also appeared. Without EsGod's help, the Fallen Ark fleet was quickly eliminated by the Universal Civilizations. The battleships burst into flames one after another, the light from the explosions illuminating the faces of everyone present.

Glancing at his destroyed fleet, EsGod turned toward Manison, speaking through the spiritual network. "Manison, I didn't expect you to also have come to deal with me."

Among the eleven, EsGod only respected four of them—Manison, Milizaus, Sun Hunter, and Han Xiao. All of them had fought with him at some point, with Manison being the person he most respected.

"It was a transaction. Besides, I've warned you before about not stepping into the Primeval Star River." Manison's tone was calm.

EsGod nodded before surveying the rest.

While he was surrounded, he did not display any panic, instead calmly saying, "Even if you have the numbers, it won't be so easy to defeat me."

He had two escape plans. One was to escape from the area that was locked by spacetime. Since that had already failed, he had to choose the second method, which was to use his own spatial Esper ability to penetrate the spacetime lock, drilling a gap to teleport away.

For this plan to work, he needed to stall them for long enough.

The assurance of EsGod in surviving mainly lay in his doppelgangers. Even if he was surrounded, he could still use them to fight against everyone. Coupled with his own regeneration and energy absorption abilities, he could survive for quite a period of time, so he was not worried.

Everyone present however knew this and knew that every second was precious. Thus, they exchanged a glance and nodded.

"Begin the operation."

"We're relying on you, Black Star."

The next instant, everyone attacked at the same time!

Faced with ten other Beyond Grade As, the doppelgangers died extremely quickly, but EsGod continued to produce more doppelgangers using his energy absorption, succeeding in holding off all the Beyond Grade As! While it was taxing on him, this was already shocking enough.

Even the Beyond Grade As encircling him could not help but sigh at his battle strength.

The evolved form of EsGod was really a freak!

If it was not for Black Star's suggestion for them to join hands and deal with him, who would still threaten this fellow in the future?

Han Xiao weaved through the battlefield, shuttling through the heavy blockade of the doppelgangers to get closer to EsGod.

Because EsGod had already fought with Han Xiao before, it did not suspect him and immediately rushed forward to challenge him.

However, when the two of them made contact, EsGod felt a strange power surge out from Han Xiao's body and into his own.

The next instant, it was as though a tranquilizer had been injected into EsGod, and his abilities all went silent.

"This is... Esper Silence‽"

EsGod's expression changed, and it finally turned into suspicion. He did not understand why Han Xiao had his ability.

"It's effective!" Seeing the notification on the interface, Han Xiao breathed a sigh of relief.

During the pre-war conference, Han Xiao had discussed this strategy with the rest, and the moment they surrounded him would be the time he unleashed the Esper Silence Character Summon Card.

Han Xiao had always hidden this move, just waiting for the opportunity.

The moment Esper Silence came into effect, all the doppelgangers froze, and without the ability to maintain it, the doppelgangers exploded and dissipated into black mist.

Because of their disparity, the duration of Esper Silence was at the lowest, but this instant was enough to disintegrate his doppelgangers!

Everyone was long prepared and took the advantage when EsGod lost his abilities. The three mages threw the restraint magic they had prepared, the psychics interfered with his mental state, the pugilists used force to suppress him, and Han Xiao also gave EsGod an injection, implanting him with nano-level cytostatic fluid to reduce his vitality.

This single instant was enough for EsGod to fall under heavy restrictions. With so many Beyond Grade As acting in concert, there was no way he could struggle free in a short while.

When his strength recovered, he tried to free himself, but the control skills were like shackles, binding each of its limbs and nailing him in place.

Under so many effects, the energy within his body stagnated, and he was unable to utilize it to activate his abilities any longer.

EsGod stared at Han Xiao, his eyes displaying puzzlement.

"How are you able to use my ability?"

"You'll have a lot of time to slowly think about that in the future." Han Xiao did not hesitate, immediately taking out the Spacetime Amber and pointing it toward EsGod. After entering its second layer of Soul Connection, the production of amber balls had sped up.

The Spacetime Amber was the key to this plan!

The people present might have been able to restrict EsGod, but they could not keep gathering forever. EsGod had too many Esper abilities, and there was no guarantee that he could not run after being locked up.

The only guaranteed way was the Spacetime Amber, which could restrict EsGod.

They had already decided that Han Xiao would be the core behind the operation this time, and everyone's responsibility was simply restricting EsGod.

Without Esper Silence and the Spacetime Amber, EsGod would likely manage to escape. They were the key variables in this operation.

EsGod was sensitive toward space and felt the space around him start to warp. A look of astonishment was seen in his eyes.

"So, this is the effect of the Spacetime Amber from the legends. What a miraculous Universal Treasure." EsGod paused for a while, reluctantly twisting his facial muscles. "I never thought that I would end up in your hands."

Han Xiao was deeply aware of the possibility of receiving a counterattack if one talked too much and did not answer, focused on creating the Spacetime Amber.

Seeing that the situation was hopeless, EsGod stopped struggling, staring indifferently at Han Xiao.

"Black Star, we will meet again."

"That will be left to when the three Universal Civilizations see fit to ask me to release you."

Han Xiao's eyes flashed, and he suddenly cut the energy supply.

EsGod's entire body was sealed within the Spacetime Amber!

Chapter 895: Success, Return

The moment the Spacetime Amber was formed, all energy was isolated, and everyone let go, surrounding it and gazing at EsGod, who was trapped within the amber curiously.

"Is it done?" Sun Hunter tapped the casing of the amber ball, gazing at the motionless EsGod. His eyes carried some surprise.

Before the operation, they had estimated that the success rate would not be low, but now that it had been completed, the Beyond Grade As found it unbelievable.

EsGod was famed in the universe and had escaped the grasp of the three Universal Civilizations time and again. Now, it had truly been caught!

Furthermore, the operation had gone quite smoothly.

"Once trapped within the Spacetime Amber, time and space will be frozen. EsGod still retains his consciousness but can no longer move his body. We've succeeded," Han Xiao summarized.

"Humph, to think this day would come." Milizaus shook his head.

"With eleven of us, it would be an embarrassment if we failed." Manison's expression was calm, but he felt emotional at the loss of someone he knew.

But just as this feeling surfaced, it was immediately suppressed down when his gaze shifted to the Spacetime Amber that Han Xiao was holding. Everyone also looked at the Universal Treasure.

The capture of EsGod filled everyone with surprise, but this did not last long as they were all Beyond Grade As. What they were more interested in was the Spacetime Amber.

Due to the rumors of the battle of Planet Lighthouse, the Spacetime Amber had entered the sights of the various Beyond Grade As, and they were interested in something that could easily imprison another Universal Treasure. Now that they saw it in person, feeling envious was only natural.

Black Star had the means to restrict a Beyond Grade A's abilities, which posed a threat to most of them present. Everyone had to reconsider their evaluation of Black Star's strength. His position was unique.

Sensing their gazes, Han Xiao's brows furrowed, and he put the Spacetime Amber away once again with a flip of his hand.

"What a good thing." Sun Hunter sighed. "Black Star, your luck is good to actually possess two Universal Treasures."

Han Xiao raised his brows in response. He was the happiest whenever someone praised his luck.

After all, something intangible had to be emphasized by others, just like how ordinary people liked to be called 'handsome' or 'beautiful'...

After pausing for a moment, he did not respond but rather changed topics. "Now that EsGod has been caught, the operation is complete. I'll take EsGod back to the dynasty. Any objections?"

Manison shook his head. He was interested in EsGod's body, but it was a pity that he could not open the Spacetime Amber.

The trio from the Arcane Church, including Sun Hunter, thought about it before finally agreeing to Han Xiao's request as well. The Arcane Church wished to take EsGod captive, but the situation always trumped one's desires. With seven Beyond Grade As from the dynasty present, there was no guarantee they could snatch it, and there was also no need to.

"Since everyone is agreeable, then leave it to us." Milizaus nodded. "Black Star, your contribution was the biggest in the operation this time. The dynasty will cooperate and announce your deeds."

"Alright." Han Xiao smiled.

EsGod and the Fallen Ark fleet were quite well known in the universe as notorious villains, frightening countless interstellar citizens. Now that this guy had been caught by the dynasty, it would definitely be big news. The dynasty would not let go of this opportunity to announce in public their 'contribution to maintain peace in the universe' by eliminating a scourge that threatened the citizens' safety.

As the promoter and biggest contributor to the operation, Han Xiao would naturally be the key figure of this propaganda. When the news was spread, his reputation would also rise, and it would most likely become one of his defining battle records. The influence of this event would not necessarily be lower than the battle of Planet Lighthouse.

For someone such as EsGod, he might not be able to obtain any political assets, but he should definitely get Legendary Points.

Of course, when compared with the hidden dangers of the World Tree Civilization, these were trivial things. It was more important to eliminate the hidden dangers. At least the citizens would not receive a sudden alert that a World Tree was invading when they were on the toilet one day. That would probably scare the sh*t out of them.

Without the threat of EsGod, the spatial research of the three civilizations would also be lowered somewhat, and the Fallen Ark would also not continue launching attacks without a leader. Thus, the time when the World Tree Civilization would be linked with them would be delayed.

Since he had captured EsGod at this stage, the storyline of EsGod would disappear, but compared to the disaster brought about by the early invasion of the World Tree, this consequence was worth it, and it would win him more time for a stable development.

In the future, the three Universal Civilizations and the World Tree Civilization would definitely notice each other, and there would be a cosmic disaster. Han Xiao was accumulating strength for this, so to him, the later it happened, the better.

That's right, EsGod said that he would meet me again.

Han Xiao's eyes flashed. Just now, he was busy trying to seal EsGod and did not pay attention to his words. Now that he had relaxed, all sorts of hypotheses began to float up.

EsGod also knew of the existence of the World Tree Civilization and was definitely certain that there would be a war between the two. His meaning was—would they let him out when they realized that they would require his strength?

Han Xiao shook his head. It was unknown when that would happen, and by then, it was hard to say that EsGod's consciousness would still be sane after the long period of captivity.

This time, the Lotus Swordsman opened her mouth, coldly remarking, "There's something I must remind you of. When I was interfering with EsGod's soul, at that instant when he was sealed, I felt an extremely strong mental fluctuation.

Han Xiao's expression stiffened. "What sort of fluctuation?"

"The mental state of EsGod exploded out at that time, and his resistance increased manifolds, as though he wished to use his mental energy to incite his body and remove his restrictions. However, he did not succeed, and the Spacetime Amber enveloped him shortly after, bouncing my psychic powers out."

"Ok, I got it." Han Xiao was silent for a while before he nodded.

It sounded like EsGod's last gamble, but he had seemingly failed. It should be very normal.

No one argued over the rights to hold EsGod, and they quickly reached a consensus.

Everyone then turned back to look at the battlefield. The three Universal Civilization's fleets were still clearing up the remnants of Fallen Ark, but no one intended to help.

They only had EsGod in their eyes. Now that the main evil had been cleared, these small fries were not worth moving.

Han Xiao remembered that the Contribution Points awarded by [Dynasty Battle Operation: Fallen Ark (Repeatable)] and thus split apart some of his mechanical army to hunt down the fleet.

The moment EsGod was caught, the rest of the Fallen Ark members also gave up resisting. No one surrendered since they were wanted criminals but fled in all directions. There was almost no one left on scene.

While waiting for the battle to end, Han Xiao opened the interface and viewed the large number of prompts that had popped up just now.

[Dynasty Battle Operation: Fallen Ark (Repeatable)] would soon end, and the few missions regarding facing EsGod directly had been completed. Just the reward for the experience measured up to thirty billion and was enough to level up a few times even at his level of 280. Of course, the premise was destroying his doppelgangers. Be it in the early or late versions, the number of players who could achieve that were few, but to him, it was not much effort.

The Contribution Points of the dynasty also surged up, crossing the ten thousand mark, almost nearing the amount where he could purchase two Ultimate Knowledges.

Very rewarding!

At the same time, a brand new [Character Summon Card—EsGod] also fell into Han Xiao's hands.

However, EsGod had too many abilities, and the chances of drawing Esper Silence were low. This time, his draw was ordinary, and he only got teleportation. He could use it about ten times, and its effect was pretty good, but it was chicken feed for him, given that he already had Void Hyperdrive.

However, Void Hyperdrive was a little less flashy, and having more methods would also be good.

This time, Han Xiao had spent a lot to deal with EsGod. He had completely used up his Esper Silence skill, so this sure-kill ability against Espers was gone. Furthermore, the number of [Perfect Mechanical Sense] uses had dropped by one.

He still had one final blank Character Summon Card, which he could use to produce another [Perfect Mechanical Sense], but he did not plan to do so currently.

The battle at Planet Lighthouse and with EsGod was enough to give him a strong reputation, and it was estimated that no one would come and provoke him for a period of time. There was no need to think about using the blank Character Summon Card.

The other mission, [Archenemy of the Three Universal Civilizations], also showed a 'completed' status.

By capturing EsGod alive, he had fulfilled the additional requirements of the mission, and thus, he could draw three abilities from EsGod, which was much better compared to the Character Summon Card.

His Molding Talents were all practically drawn in this manner.

Han Xiao did not accept the reward immediately. Such precious reward, if he did not go back and touch Feidin and his godson first, would he not waste his chances‽

Just based on his own face, he would probably draw something nasty out!

Other than the reward, Han Xiao also obtained a great amount of experience in killing enemies. Killing a doppelganger would net him a lot of experience, and since the doppelgangers came unceasingly, it allowed him to obtain a ton of experience.

While gazing at his interface, the battle finally ended.

Han Xiao looked toward the other two universal civilizations.

"Our cooperation ends here. I thank you all for your help."

"There's no need to be polite. If there's time, you can come over to my territory for a visit." Manison sent another invitation to Han Xiao.

"Not today. I still have to escort EsGod back," Han Xiao said. "Let's do it another time."

"Next time then."

Manison shook his head regretfully before turning to leave.

Sun Hunter exchanged communicator numbers with Han Xiao before leading the rest of the Arcane Church members back to the main flagship. Han Xiao took the captured EsGod and followed Milizaus and the rest back to the dynasty's flagship.

The eleven of them returned to their respective factions, and the three civilizations left.

At the same time, the operation's report was also sent to the upper echelons of the three Universally Civilizations.

Chapter 897: The Fall of EsGod Event

After the three rewards had been drawn, miniscule Mechanical Force arcs swam on the surface of his body, and he felt numb. The cells started to subtly change, and from Han Xiao's senses, he could feel that they had become even easier to control.

Because there was a base version, the upgrades to the talents were not uncomfortable and were actually quite pleasant.

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief, clenching his fists and feeling the endless strength surging in his body, as well as the vibrant vitality.

Following the evolution of the talents, Han Xiao's self-healing abilities had also risen to a new level. For the current him, having such strong vitality was not disadvantageous since he was holding onto two coveted Universal Treasures, or else he might end up being captured like EsGod one day.

"With my current self-healing level, so long as I'm not like EsGod being beaten up by so many Beyond Grade As, there should not be any problems."

Now that his HP and energy conversion rates were high, Han Xiao had plans for his subsequent advancements. Since the upper limit of his HP would increase with every level up, there was no need to pay attention to it. What he needed was to continue improving the energy attribute, as this affected his total energy as well as the speed of conversion.

In terms of his Mechanic class, he had to acquire advanced mechanic-related talents, learn more Ultimate Knowledges, research more blueprints, improve his machinery, expand the size of his mechanical army, and nurture a mechanical civilization... While he was resistant to attacks, this only ensured his tankiness. The main method of combat still had to rely on his Pay-to-Win... cough cough... his mechanical army.

The siege this time was considerably less risky than the battle at Planet Lighthouse. At Planet Lighthouse, they were the passive party under attack and were outnumbered. But this time, they were on the active side and outnumbered the enemy. His situation was not so dangerous because even if the operation failed, it would not have been life threatening. Thus, the pressure was lower.

As the interface for ability extraction disappeared, Han Xiao glanced and noticed another reward notification for this mission.

[Dungeon Copy: Fall of EsGod]

Han Xiao's eyelids jumped.

"D*mn, the difficulty of this dungeon will be through the roof!"

EsGod was considered one of the end game bosses of the evil faction, but receiving the dungeon copy was something Han Xiao expected. However, those players who dared enter such a dungeon would be masochists.

Ignoring the players, even if it was Han Xiao himself, if he attempted to solo this, he would end up being pummeled by EsGod. Luckily, he only distributed the dungeon crystals and did not use them himself.

"Oh, this copy can actually be used to display my heroism..." Han Xiao could not help but think about the professional boot-licker Bun-Hit-Dog.

Putting his thoughts away, Han Xiao then glanced at his notifications to make sure he had not missed any rewards.

"Such a notorious guy like EsGod should give me some Legendary Points. I believe when the three Universal Civilizations announce this, the points will be delivered."

There were two ways to obtain Legendary Points. One was the reward upon completing a mission, while the other was not part of the reward but more of the news being circulated around the universe, which would still award them with Legendary Points. Since Han Xiao had obtained Legendary Points in both ways before, he was not surprised.

Han Xiao could not help but think about the future developments, sighing internally.

"Now that EsGod is trapped, the unstable variable that is the World Tree Civilization has been resolved. Even if the Crimson Dynasty manages to crack the wormhole coordinates, as long as I'm operating, the Crimson Dynasty will then pay attention to hiding itself and will not lead them here. Rather, they will explore the World Tree Civilization in advance and obtain the initiative.'

Because of the coordinates from the wormhole, the storyline of the World Tree Civilization would inevitably change. The timeline being brought forward was a definite, but in his previous life, the World Tree Civilization had first discovered the three Universal Civilizations and seized the initiative. This time, however, Han Xiao estimated that it would be the three Universal Civilizations that would first discover the World Tree Civilization.

In this manner, the situation would change. The three Universal Civilizations had progressed all the way from the dark ages and definitely understood the importance of concealment. They would make a plan first before taking action. Han Xiao himself was also clear of the style of the World Tree Civilization, and there was no way both sides could co-exist. War was inevitable.

But who the invading party would be this time was difficult to say.

Han Xiao remembered that there was still another set of the wormhole data in the hands of the Tyla Civilization, and this would require the Crimson Dynasty to recollect it themselves. This was not a huge problem. With the ability of a Universal Civilization, it was likely that they would crack it before the Tyla Civilization, and then, the dynasty would take the initiative.

Furthermore, EsGod was now out of the picture, so it was likely that this set of data would hold less of an attraction toward the researchers since there were so many other research topics to work on. They would not spend so many resources on an unknown wormhole. Therefore, based on Han Xiao's expectations, even if the storyline of the World Tree Civilization was brought forward, it would not be so soon.

"Without their leader, the Fallen Ark should disband quickly, no longer being a paradise for thugs. Those players who like to pillage and kill will also have one fewer place to go," Han Xiao mused.

The storyline of EsGod could be said to have been completely subverted, and the destinies of many people would be rewritten. Most of them would lead better lives. With fewer planets being destroyed, they also would not meet with grisly ends due to EsGod. The number of lives saved would probably number in the billions.

This could be considered as doing a good deed, saving a wave of characters. Han Xiao stroked his chin, and the corners of his mouth curled up.

"After getting rid of EsGod, I can now lie low. There's nothing much for me to do. I can safely tide through Version 3.0."

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief. Thinking back, ever since Version 3.0 started, he had always been into dire straits and had faced many big issues. It seemed like he would finally welcome a long period of stability, where he could relax and slowly develop.

Just as Han Xiao was preparing his blueprint for the Black Star Army, Reynold took Nero to another machinery modification room.

Reynold came to a modification table, and his fingers marked several golden operation marks on the panel. The table was switched to a manual assembly mode, and on the clear surface of the table, several gaps appeared in which metal plates opened into arms for support.

"Since this vacation is over, I hope you can return to your studying mode as soon as possible. Theoretical knowledge is only the basis of a mechanic. The mechanics who are unable to turn this knowledge into actual manufacturing capabilities are considered failures. You have learned enough theory, and thus, starting today, you'll need to add the operation training of primary machinery into your curriculum."

Nero's spirit was refreshed. Studying theoretical knowledge was dry and boring, and having actual practical lessons would at least be more interesting. He had been interested in building machinery from the start, which was why he had chosen to become a mechanic.

Pressing a few buttons of the modification station, a virtual screen popped up, in which there were many low-level machinery assembly methods recorded.

This machinery modification table belonged to Reynold, and within it were a lot of low-level blueprints.

"Let's start from the simpler ones," Reynold said. "Okay, take this. The classic exoskeleton mechanical suit, with a technical difficulty of D1, at the weak planetary level. This is the technology of Planet Aquamarine, and the parts have already been produced. You just need to assemble them."

Nero settled down, recalling theoretical knowledge that he learned and applying it. He would watch the operation video whenever he was confused.

"Right now, we're training you on your familiarity with assembly. This is the basis of a mechanic, and even His Excellency Black Star started off the same way." Reynold stood by the side to provide guidance. "Don't just simply follow the steps to assemble. Use all your sensory organs to detect the machinery's structure. Use your mechanical force to penetrate it, touch it, and perceive it."

"Understood."

Nero focused, and the clearer a picture he got of the machinery, under the effect of the Advanced Luck Glow, his Middle Grade Mechanical Sense was slowly moving toward the advanced level.

...

In a certain restricted area of Constellation Corridor, a dynasty battleship landed on a huge mechanical space fortress. This fortress was in the shape of a cube, with a structured layer and covered with heavy armor. A large number of defensive weapons were arranged on the outside, arming it to the teeth.

This sort of armed space fortress was specially designed by the dynasty to hold prisoners who were powerful supers. It possessed powerful defense capabilities, enough to blow up an entire fleet, and a huge prison space. Only one Beyond Grade A was detained there, and all those facilities inside were to prevent the person from escaping.

"Please confirm the code and key of the imprisonment project... Procedure complete."

"The prison is being activated. The core is currently being opened, and smart docking is underway."

"Docking complete. The imprisoned cabin is ready to launch. Counting down... three, two, one, launch."

From within the dynasty battleship shot out a small egg-shaped cabin. Its body was silver and black. It was ten meters long, and EsGod, wrapped in amber, was locked inside.

This egg-shaped cabin possessed independent power propulsion, jetting out flames as it smoothly flew into the gap exposed by the prison fortress. The body fit perfectly, and the mechanical structures on both sides locked to complete the fitting.

The prison then closed and folded upon itself, turning back into its original cuboid shape.

This was where EsGod would be locked for the next five hundred years.

...

Some days later, a piece of news shook the entire Galaxy.

The three Universal Civilizations jointly released a news report that the criminal EsGod had been captured!

They had hunted EsGod multiple times, all of which had ended in failure, and the infamy of EsGod had long pierced deep into the citizens' hearts. For them to have suddenly captured EsGod shocked all the citizens.

Countless galactic residents thought that EsGod would remain unpunished, and many conspiracy theorists even believed that the three civilizations were secretly backing EsGod, but they were all equally shocked by this news.

After the initial shock came the cheers.

EsGod had been captured; everyone cheered!

After years of poisoning the universe, EsGod had caused a lot of tragedies. He had always remained the most dangerous criminal in the eyes of the galactic residents, and now the three Universal Civilizations had fought against this terrorism and captured the criminal.

The three civilizations' joint operation, in the eyes of many people, sent a signal to the outside world that the conflicts arising from the Battle of Planet Lighthouse had been resolved, and they were trying to promote their relationship now. The interstellar environment had returned to stability.

As for the joint operation, the three civilizations also announced the details. The eleven Beyond Grade As involved were introduced, and they emphasized on Han Xiao's merits, even calling him the core of the operation as well as its initiator. This further highlighted his contributions.

With the number of people being aware of EsGod, it was equivalent to Han Xiao stepping on the infamy of EsGod to boost his own renown.

Even before the topic of the 'Enemy of the Arcane' had disappeared, another matter that represented Han Xiao had appeared.

The universe termed this as the 'Fall of EsGod', and as the leader of the event, Han Xiao left an even deeper impression in the hearts of the galactic residents.

Various star fields and countless victims who bore hatred toward EsGod gave rise to emotions of gratitude toward Han Xiao.

...

The Shazik Planetary Transit station was a neutral planet that offered various services, located in the dangerous Central Galaxy desolate universe belt. It was a rare occurrence, and it provided people with venues for smuggling, repairs, and entertainment. The target of their service was the wanted criminals, including Fallen Ark.

Only people who were not afraid of death would establish a planetary transit station in this area. Those with no backer would be long looted by the mobs, so Shazik had linked up with the Fallen Ark, providing them with a large amount of protection fees in order to prevent being plundered.

The owner of this planetary station was also called Shazik. He was a Calamity Grade Super and had established cooperative relationships with a number of armed forces, including Fallen Ark. He was considered a middle level character in the desolate universe belt.

As for his origins, they were a secret, and the criminals there did not and would not care.

However, Shazik was no criminal but rather had his hometown ravaged by EsGod. He had developed a strong hatred, and thus, he had chosen to become an avenger, building a transit station there to look for opportunities to deal with Fallen Ark.

Upon receiving the news of EsGod being captured, he immediately called for a secret meeting.

"The moment EsGod falls, there will be no one keeping the insane Fallen Ark members together. They're sure to disband. We'll also be embroiled since our backer has fallen. There are too many fellows that want to plunder us," one of his close aides said.

"That's right. We cannot stay here any longer. We need to leave."

"Boss, what are you going to do?"

Shattered Star Ring solemnly said, "Bring all of our things. We'll go to Shattered Star Ring and look for the Black Star Army."

"Why him?"

"I made a promise to the gods before. Whoever could get rid of EsGod, I would serve under him." Shazik's expression was set.

Ever since his hometown was annihilated, he had only had revenge left in his life. However, EsGod was too strong, and revenge was out of the question. Now that Black Star had finished his life's work, even if it was not for revenge, Shazik also felt gratitude toward him and decided to use his strength as a form of repayment.

"With someone at Black Star's level, will he even want us?"

"That's why we have to bring a gift." Shazik lowered his voice. "Over the years, we've bribed several of the Fallen Ark members and have also sent in a lot of undercover spies. Now is the best chance. When the Fallen Ark is in chaos, they'll steal a portion of the riches, and this will be our basis to enter the Black Star Army."

Everyone's eyes lit up. They had spent so many years here and also gotten to know the Fallen Ark well. While they were a chaotic and loose organization, they also had a lot of valuable items, such as the trophies EsGod had stored over the years—secret intelligence reports, failed experiments, and even special prisoners that were locked up.

Now that EsGod was gone, they were definitely not the only ones looking to plunder the Fallen Ark. This was the best time to fish in muddied waters!

Chapter 898: Impact

The members of Fallen Ark were originally criminals that came from different star fields. Some of them were the crazed worshippers of EsGod, while others did it to obtain the protection of EsGod.

Now that EsGod was gone, without their strong leader, no one had the qualifications to step up, so the lawless criminals also lost their reason for banding together.

The criminals knew that without their leader, the next move of the three Universal Civilizations would be to bring the knife to them, completely cleansing the desolate universe belt.

After EsGod fell, the powerful Fallen Ark also began to split apart into countless smaller groups, and one by one, they started to raid all the Fallen Ark's treasuries.

The desolate universe belt in the Central Galaxy was actually the territory of the Fallen Ark and had maintained a very thin line of balance between all the forces, but now, it had become even more chaotic and dangerous, with the criminals killing and plundering each other.

At this moment, there were more than a thousand battleships surrounding a desolate planet and undergoing a battle.

This planet was one of the secret research facilities established by EsGod, and it stored various valuable materials, technology, and special products. The thousands of battleships belonged to the divided criminal groups, and their purpose was to snatch the results of this R&D base. One of the teams belonged to Shazik.

The surface of the planet had turned into an intense battlefield. Most of the battlefields were not equipped with annihilation weapons but rather only used their battleship cannons to attack. The plasma beams interlaced with each other, coloring the dark universe with bright stripes, as though paint on a canvas. Hulls melted wherever it passed, turning into red hot slag that became obstacles in the battlefield.

The battle continued for a period of time, and finally, the victors were decided. Shazik's team was one of them, and they raided this facility before leaving in satisfaction.

...

The inky black blade sliced across the throat, and fresh red blood seeped out, splattering on the bloodied cabin wall.

Plop!

A gray-skinned creature with dense compound eyes fell over, clutching his bloodied neck, revealing the killer behind.

It was a humanoid creature with a long blade wearing a hood and a black mechanical mask that only revealed a pair of scarlet eyes.

This was a tattered ship cabin, the walls of which were covered with slash marks and electrical arcs. Lying on the ground were hundreds of dead bodies of different species, and the ground was solidified with colorful blood scabs. Only the killer was left standing.

"Number 11,570..."

His voice was hoarse, sounding like a pair of worn bellows. With a flick of his wrist, the blood on the blade disappeared, and he sheathed the blade before pressing on his mechanical mask, sending a message to a number labelled 'employer'.

"Objective complete."

Very quickly, the employer replied, their tone filled with gratitude.

"Thank you very much, Mister Lothaire. Thank you for taking revenge for us. Without you, we would forever be..."

"This is a transaction. Remember to pay up."

Lothaire indifferently cut the other party off.

He was a lone bounty hunter, but his hunting targets were limited to members of the Fallen Ark.

Lothaire was born in one of the colonial planets of an advanced civilization and had grown up in a peaceful environment. However, the Fallen Ark fleet descended upon them one day, bringing death and destruction.

He had thought that he would die, but somehow, a hidden Esper Ability within his body burst out at the juncture of life and death, allowing him to escape from his fate... but resistance was futile, as they captured him and offered him to EsGod.

Thus, Lothaire met EsGod and had his newly awakened Esper Ability torn away from him, becoming a dying person, his life force flickering like a candle in the wind.

Normally, those whom EsGod had stolen abilities from would either be made into food or thrown out into the universe. Maybe Lady Luck was smiling at him, but Lothaire was thrown out into the universe. While ordinary people could not survive in the universe, he found out that the Esper Ability had changed his body structure, allowing him to survive even in the vacuum of the universe.

After the Fallen Ark fleet had left, the civilization's rescue force managed to arrive before Lothaire died, making him the only survivor. He held an extreme hatred toward EsGod and Fallen Ark, and under this drive, Lothaire, who had lost his Esper ability, experienced mortal hardships, embarking on the path of a pugilist and becoming a Super.

After his training was completed, he became a bounty hunter.

The members of the Fallen Ark were all criminals, and they fled under EsGod's umbrella to avoid being hunted by various civilizations. Lothaire was specialized in hunting down such criminals, and he made these self-confident fugitives pay their blood debt. Thus, his employers were usually victims of Fallen Ark.

As of today, the number of Fallen Ark members who had fallen under Lothaire's blade was in six digits, but Lothaire was still unsatisfied. He was just like an ascetic monk that continued to grind his strength in order to complete his hidden goal—assassinating EsGod!

His experience of meeting EsGod had always been his nightmare, bringing him endless fear and causing him to wake up from his sleep. But even though he knew it was impossible, he refused to give up on his ultimate goal.

Without caring about the ground strewn with corpses, Lothaire walked toward the control room of the spaceship. Suddenly, his communicator notified him of a news flash, which was the joint report by the three civilizations.

"EsGod has been captured?"

Lothaire's expression changed, and he stopped walking, concentrating on the news report.

After a while, he let out a long, relieved sigh. Suddenly, he felt a bit lost, as the goal in his heart had suddenly disappeared.

But very quickly, Lothaire regained the light in his eyes and muttered to himself, "The guy who caught EsGod is called Black Star..."

...

On one planet where the people were living like nomads, less than a tenth of the population remained after being attacked by EsGod.

When news of EsGod's capture reached this tribe, the people shed tears of joy.

"EsGod has been captured!"

"Wu wu wu... we've waited so long for this day!"

"All praise Black Star!"

"Long live Black Star!"

The same scene was being repeated on many different planets.

...

The news of EsGod's arrest incited joy but also alarmed a few secret organizations.

"EsGod was too violent in his bearings. I knew this day would come for him."

"Now that EsGod is gone, the Fallen Ark also won't exist. There's no one else to take away the attention of the three civilizations. This is disadvantageous to us."

"Continue maintaining a low profile and accumulate strength. We're not as unbridled as EsGod, so it's hard for them to focus on us."

"This is also a chance. We can accept those under EsGod as well as his inheritance and use it to bolster our forces."

"Yes, send someone to the Central Galaxy. There will be a lot of people who think the same way, so don't fall behind."

...

In the orbit of Planet Aquamarine, the Floating Dragon Island drifted.

Ames stood at the edge of Floating Dragon Island, overlooking the panoramic view of Planet Aquamarine.

Footsteps sounded behind her, and Ames turned to see Aesop walking to her.

"There's big news." Aesop shook his head. "EsGod has been captured by the three Universal Civilizations."

"What happened?" Ames' brows raised up.

"See for yourself."

Aesop put the communicator on her hand.

After glancing through, Ames returned the communicator, a smile on her face.

"He really can't sit still."

"Black Star went and did something big again. He's becoming stronger and stronger." Aesop felt a little emotional.

Throughout his long life, he had experienced the age where EsGod was the craziest. He feared EsGod somewhat, but to think that this fellow actually was captured by a newbie Beyond Grade A.

Although this was a siege, he also saw the extent of Han Xiao's current connections and influence from the lineup of the three civilizations in this operation. Even when he was part of the Ancient Ones, he probably did not have a reputation like Han Xiao's.

"Yes, he is becoming stronger."

Ames smiled but went a little silent. She still remembered the time she fought EsGod together with Han Xiao. At that time, his strength left her with a deep impression, but now EsGod had actually fallen to Han Xiao. This meant that Han Xiao's overall strength should have surpassed hers.

While she had always been pursuing strength, watching her subordinate catch up to her left her with complicated feelings.

She was originally high up above, but later on, Black Star reached Beyond Grade A and sat on the same level as her. However, whether it was in position, strength, or influence, Black Star had completely surpassed her, completing a counterattack under her watch.

While she was also improving, the majority of it was because of the evolution that Black Star had given her.

Their roles had swapped.

Ames stretched before lightly blowing out.

"It seems that I've been too lazy these years and not exercising properly. I should look for a time to have a good fight with Black Star."

...

Following the news, Han Xiao who was on the journey back also received a long-awaited notification.

You have received 1 Legendary Point.

Universe Legendary Point: The Fall of EsGod—The notorious leader of the Fallen Ark, the 'Butcherer of Life' EsGod, has finally been captured by the three Universal Civilizations. As one of the participants, and even the leader, countless races are grateful for your contribution and will remember your name.

Universe Legendary Point? Han Xiao whistled. The infamy of EsGod was really carved into everyone's heart.

As one of the end bosses of the evil faction, EsGod had quite the reputation. The sensation caused by capturing him was no less than the Battle of Planet Lighthouse. Since EsGod's influence covered the entire universe, he was given the highest legendary point rating.

Closing his notification, Han Xiao opened the forums. Everyone was discussing the fall of EsGod.

He had obtained reputation from this event, and this also seemed to have affected the players' gaming experience.

Chapter 899: Popularity and Recognition

The social media transmission within the galaxy was quick, and this explosive news quickly went around to various star fields. As for the players who also carried a communicator, they naturally did not miss out on such news.

Within the forums for the Shattered Star Ring, there were many players fervently discussing this incident.

After going through three versions, the players were already familiar with the erratic whereabouts of NPCs. Except for functional NPCs such as merchants, most of the characters would not stay within the same place all the time. A player could talk to a character and come back later to see that they had left for another place.

While this was a little inconvenient, the majority preferred such a characteristic, as it gave off a high sense of realism.

Following the expansion of the Black Star Army, the contact that Han Xiao had with the players had also begun to decrease. Ever since Version 2.0, he had adopted an image of a faction commander, and thus, the players were now used to not seeing a trace of their army commander and suddenly finding out news about him.

Discussing the deeds of the army commander became one of the pastimes for the players.

Many players were creating posts to discuss the fall of EsGod. At this stage, their level was too far from EsGod's; he was a character toward the mid-late versions. As such, there was little interaction between the character and the player. The players only knew that he had a badass introduction, and he was from the evil faction, nothing else.

Only the players from the three star fields in the Central Galaxy knew more, especially those chaotic players who had taken part in looting and pillaging without taking up any storyline missions. They had gone to the desolate universe belt to join the Fallen Ark, but they did not have the qualification to see EsGod, only seeing the tip of the iceberg.

Because they were limited in their understanding of EsGod, the impact of EsGod falling was not as great, and its significance could not be compared to the battle at Planet Lighthouse. After all, Planet Lighthouse involved two Universal Civilizations, and to the players, that was end game content.

As for the fall of EsGod, the majority of players did not experience it and did not know the significance of this matter. They just thought that a big shot character had been caught.

The reply that Han Xiao saw was thus a routine spit on their army commander.

"The Army Commander ran off to do something again. He seems very free."

"Sigh, I also want to go to the Central Galaxy to take a look. This abominable contractor, throwing us at the Shattered Star Ring to slave away while he goes to explore places leisurely."

"Will this lead to a new storyline?"

"I doubt it. I think this was supplementary to the battle of Planet Lighthouse. EsGod took part and thus got caught. Since there's nothing that us players can do, it's most likely a backstory."

"What a trash game. It's all just CG."

"Ah, there are no cutscenes to see. I'm going to die."

"I'm EsGod. I got captured yesterday by the three Universal Civilizations and require 5,000 Enas to bail me. Someone, please bail me. When I'm out, I'll bring you to explore the world. My account number is 480xxxxxx..."

"D*mmit, I'm part of the Fallen Ark faction. You guys captured my leader. All you Black Star Army dogs, eat sh*t!"

"Central Galaxy dog, scram!"

"The Constellation Corridor is shivering."

Seeing all sort of cr*p on the forums, Han Xiao's mouth curved into a smile.

Just as he was scrolling through all the posts of these moronic players, he discovered that one of them was actually pushed to the top, with the topic of 'The meaning behind the Fall of EsGod'. The post's popularity was flying up quickly.

As he clicked on the post, he saw the player's ID, 'Army Commander's JJ' [1. For those of you who need a reminder, JJ basically means the third leg.].

"... Crazy!"

Han Xiao's face began contorting.

Being perverts was certainly a strong point of the players. He was ashamed that he could not be like them.

Taking a deep breath to calm down, Han Xiao began to read the content.

"Brothers in the army, it seems as though many of you do not view the fall of EsGod with importance. I started off like this, but today, I met with a miraculous incident that changed my mind.

"It goes like this. I actually accepted a small employment mission some time ago and acted as a temporary escort for a long-distance travel spaceship, responsible for escorting them through the Giberian Star System. You guys know, all the Galactic Travelling Agencies now like to employ us Black Star Army people. As long as we are onboard, the pirates will not attack.

"Anyway, there was nothing to say about the journey. It was relaxing. But after we disembarked, a few of the other visitors from another star field stopped me, giving me some stuff and asking me to pass them to our Army Commander.

"[Picture Attached]

"[Picture Attached]

"As you can see from the pictures, they weren't anything valuable, just some handmade stuff, and the flavor text read 'This is a gift that is full of gratitude'. It triggered a corresponding mission.

"[Picture Attached]

"I had never interacted with them before, but they took the initiative to find me. These passengers said that their civilization had once been attacked by EsGod, and many people died. They were extremely grateful to Black Star for eradicating him, so they made the gifts to express their gratitude. They saw me as a member of the Black Star Army and wanted to ask me to deliver them to the commander.

"This is the rough idea. During the conversation, this group was enthusiastic, holding my hands as they laughed and cried, continuously murmuring thanks toward the Black Star Army. I've recorded the video here, and the emotions are very contagious...

"[Video]

"While this is just a small task, I feel that the meaning hidden within is not simple.

"Within the entire universe, how many people would have been harmed by EsGod, and how many wish to thank our commander! This number must be frightening! From this, you can tell that the true meaning behind the Fall of EsGod is not just a simple backstory but rather the dawn of justice shining upon many destroyed races and families!

"The Army Commander did a great noble deed, and honestly, seeing the gratitude on the NPC's faces gave me a feeling of satisfaction.

"Brothers, I've said too much. Let me be the first to conclude: the Army Commander is awesome!

"PS: To reflect my admiration to the commander, I've decided to go to the cash shop to buy a 'Name Change Card'. I'm going to add an additional 'Big' word to my name!"

Han Xiao scrolled down. This post had attracted a lot of players, and there were a lot of replies to it.

"It's ok to add a 'big' word. But it seems that the OP[1] is a troll."

"I suspect that you are guiding us somewhere, but I have no proof."

"I just saw the video. It's full of emotions. I give 100 points."

Some players ridiculed the poster, and some agreed with him.

"This made me remember the Mutation Disaster. In order to save his mother planet, the Army Commander actively went into the galaxy to gather reinforcements. He has always had a sense of responsibility."

"That's right. While Army Commander is a profiteer, he can still be relied on. I remember his speech. My goodness, so inspiring!"

When players chose a camp, other than just benefits, they also paid attention to the values it displayed. The players would often seek psychological satisfaction.

Han Xiao had always given the players a good impression, so many of them stayed in the Black Star Army not just because of the high welfare but also because they recognized Han Xiao as a leader.

Now that Black Star had received the gratitude of countless races, the players also felt honored being related to him. Many of them had a sense of honor and achievement.

After reading this point, Han Xiao scratched his head, and he found out that even he himself had underestimated the influence of this incident.

Just as the post had said, there were countless races that EsGod had trampled on, and now they saw him as their savior.

This popularity was different from the normal reputation. The ones before stopped at the level of acknowledging his strength and status, but everyone only knew him as a powerful person, having high influence. What the EsGod incident gave him were the hearts of the commoners and the recognition of the galactic residents.

One of these functions would attract more talents to take the initiative to join his faction. After all, some people would never be persuaded by benefits, and they were likely often talents.

A Universe Legendary Point was indeed not simple, and this EsGod could be said to be a treasure to Han Xiao. He was now in a good mood.

"EsGod has made countless enemies, and there are so many that want revenge on him. I wonder if those NPCs that would have attacked EsGod in the future versions will lean toward my faction."

Han Xiao stroked his chin.

...

After travelling for a few days, the spaceship finally returned to the headquarters of the Black Star Army, entering through the dedicated personal dock.

The moment Han Xiao exited, he saw Hila waiting for him.

"Hey, you personally waited for me?" Han Xiao smiled as he waved.

"Humph." Hila did not deny it, brushing aside the red stray hairs that covered her eyes, and slowly scanned Han Xiao. "Seems like EsGod didn't give you much trouble. None of your limbs are missing."

Han Xiao raised his brows before sniggering. "Were you worried about me?"

"This is my duty as the Black Star Guards captain." Hila remained expressionless.

Han Xiao smiled, turning back to bid goodbye to Feidin and the others, before leaving. He gestured for Hila to follow.

"By the way, I've brought you a present."

"Not interested." While Hila said that, her body was more honest, immediately following behind Han Xiao.

The two of them came to a combat room, and Han Xiao locked the door before turning to Hila, who was hugging her waist.

"I got something interesting from EsGod. It seems like it can strengthen Esper Abilities. With your Beyond Grade A potential, this gift could make your road to Beyond Grade A even smoother, increasing your upper limit."

Hila fiercely pursued strength, so she immediately felt emotional. "But such a good thing, won't you give it to my teacher to use?"

"Oh, she probably can't utilize it." Han Xiao shook his head. "Furthermore, you're my first choice. The first person I thought of was you."

[Esper Ability Strengthening] from EsGod Character Summon Card only had a total of three uses. Han Xiao had already thought about it. Hila's potential was exceedingly high, and coupled with the fact that she was his close aide, he would also obtain the benefits.

"Humph." The corners of Hila's mouth curled up in an arc of joy, and she put her hands behind. "Ok. What I need to do?"

"Don't move. Let me handle it."

Han Xiao activated the Character Summon Card [Esper Ability Strengthening]. The shadow of EsGod appeared behind him, and dazzling white energy particles floated around his palm.

He came up to Hila's side and tapped on her forehead. The energy particles streamed into Hila's seven orifices and circled around in her brain.

Hila groaned and shivered, immediately fainting. Han Xiao moved fast and caught her.

After checking her condition, he estimated that she would not wake up for a period of time.

"To actually faint, I thought it would be the same as the Esper Ability Potential Enhancing Fluid."

Gazing at Hila who was leaning on him, Han Xiao shook his head and carried Hila off like a sack of potatoes on his shoulder.

After leaving the combat room, he approached Hila's room, and hacking into the system, he unlocked her door and went in.

Hila's room was as sparse as Han Xiao's, and after he placed her on the bed and tucked her in, he caught sight of three photo frames on her desk.

He took a closer look. The three were respectively Hila and Aurora, her with Ames, and a picture with him. Other than that, there were no other decorations.

Standing silently for a while, Han Xiao stretched out his hand, taking the photo frame and lying it on the desk. He then switched off the lights and exited the room.

...

After a while, Hila finally opened her eyes and discovered that she was in her room.

"Did he bring me back?"

As her hazy brain cleared, Hila stood up and rubbed her eyes.

She revolved her Esper Ability, feeling the changes, and her eyes widened.

"This is as amazing as the Evolution Cube. The pathways are much smoother, and my upper limit has also increased... Oh, not sure how long I've slept. Better go find him."

As Hila prepared to leave, she noticed an incongruity in her room. Gazing at the three photo frames, she noticed that one of them had fallen.

She realized that it was the photo of herself and Han Xiao upon closer look.

Hila's eyes twitched, and the good mood she had gotten from strengthening herself dissipated in a flash.

"...Humph!"

[1] Original Poster Back

Chapter 900: [Eternal Power Source]

In the following month, Han Xiao remained within the headquarters to sort out his gains.

His Contribution Points in the dynasty had increased by another ten thousand or so, and with his original eleven thousand, he had more than twenty-two thousand. He used that to purchase one new Ultimate Knowledge from the dynasty.

Right now, the tumor that was EsGod had already been removed, and the external environment had also settled down and entered a stable development period. The pressure on him was greatly decreased, so he did not have to rush and gather more knowledge.

Han Xiao had currently grasped three Ultimate Knowledges: [Endless Material Science], [Mechanical Life Tinder], and [Virtual Creator]. There was one from each of the branches.

The Materials, Information, and Energy Branches had always been the Three Chariots of the Mechanic Class. He had obtained both material and information branches, so he chose to fill up the final branch with [Eternal Power Source].

This Ultimate Knowledge's title was just a sham. Its effect was not so exaggerated as to provide an 'eternal' source. It was not literally inexhaustible energy. The name came from the significance it held toward a Mechanic's combat strength.

The Cutting-Edge Knowledge [Abnormal State Energy] allowed a Mechanic to master the technology for safely extracting Psionic, dark matter, antimatter energy, and more. [Eternal Power Source] allowed these new energy sources to be utilized to elevate a Mechanic's abilities. At this point, one would see that technology and magic had started to blend into one, and like a mage, a mechanic would also begin to wield multi-dimensional energy.

However, this did not mean a difference in energy levels. Multi-dimensional energy did not mean that it was stronger than Psionic energy. It was just an increase in the variety of energy that a mechanic could wield.

The real focus of [Eternal Power Source] was not mastering new energy but improving the technology of the mechanic such that it was able to welcome the energies.

Just like the progress from nuclear fission to fusion, learning a more advanced energy extraction method would create a new generation of Psionic and dark matter energy reactors, which would increase the power output and stability.

The result would be a comprehensive increase in weapon power, shield durability, and machinery performance, which was the improvement brought about by energy technology innovation.

The new Ultimate Knowledge also gave Han Xiao a new talent and ability.

[Advanced Energy Control]: When utilizing advanced energy, x1.15 Attack Power Bonus, x1.2 Shield Durability Factor, +30% Machinery Core Efficiency, +20% Output Efficiency.

[Energy Innovation]: Passive Ability. This Ability will only be upgraded with each increase in level for [Eternal Power Source]. Every level up will unlock additional advanced energy technology as well as reactor blueprints.

Energy was just too important, so no matter which Mechanic branch one belonged to, they had to max out the level of [Eternal Power Source]. This was also one of the culprits behind the players' Enas hemorrhaging.

If one did not choose to specialize in the Energy Branch, the tripled cost of Potential Points needed would make people feel like dying!

Even Han Xiao himself felt the difficulty. Even at Level 280, he only had twenty-one spare Potential Points. Learning this knowledge would require twenty-four points, and even if he maxed out a few of his abilities to make up for the lack of points, maxing out [Eternal Power Source] from Lv.1 to Lv.5 would require another ninety-six Potential Points, which was equivalent to raising the level of ninety-six blueprints to the maximum.

The experience needed for this was even more frightening than what was needed to level up!

The strength of a mechanic was derived from knowledge, and blindly levelling up was insufficient. Only by stacking up the various knowledges would they then have a stronger combat capability among their peers. This was the foundation of a mechanic.

Han Xiao's four Ultimate Knowledges were all at Lv.1. After raising his level, he had to consider raising his Ultimate Knowledge level. Because of his unique advantage of having leeks, he had decided to raise all the levels of his Ultimate Knowledges as much as possible. This was destined to be a long project, but upon completion, his combat capability would be off the charts.

In addition to his own growth plan, Han Xiao also took care of the officers. The [Ability Enhancement] Character Summon Card was utilized on both Hila and Aurora, as the former had a Beyond Grade A potential, whereas the latter had a strategic level ability.

The last usage was left behind. Because both Ames and him were in the S grade, it was impossible for him to use it on her. He prepared to save this chance for another time.

In the next month, Han Xiao settled a few more official matters. The most important was the business cooperation with the Federation of Light. This was the deal that they had agreed upon.

Their method of cooperation was to help Black Star by opening a branch in the Abyss of Stars. Han Xiao coordinated with a deployment team and arranged for several satellite bases to be sent over.

Those who went over as the deployment team did not include the players, however. The Great Mechanic Han did not have the habit of transplanting his own leeks into another person's farm.

Currently, there were two major events for the players to participate in—the Gulal Civilization war and the exploration of the Flickering World.

Moreover, the promotion for the Pro League had already begun, and because Version 3.0 was the time where the volume of players shot up rapidly, there were far more newcomers. The volume for this Version's Pro League was much greater than in the past, and every player that intended to participate was actively preparing.

Based on Han Xiao's estimates, the enthusiasm of players had risen by 47.5%.

Thus, the players could be left alone. Han Xiao had recently been more concerned with the follow-up events of EsGod's fall. The impact of the event had already begun to ferment, spreading to the whole universe.

The three Universal Civilizations had begun a new wave of cleaning up the evildoers, and the Fallen Ark that had threatened the entire Central Galaxy had now completely disbanded and scattered. Many of the criminals had left the Central Galaxy, choosing to roam through the universe. Some of the other organizations were actively recruiting such criminals, dividing up EsGod's manpower.

The Fallen Ark was one of the most famous criminal organizations of this era, but it was not the only one. With the vastness of the universe, there were other large criminal organizations active in the major star fields, and it was these people that were taking in EsGod's manpower and legacies.

The Black Star Army had also received the same treatment. From Sylvia's report, there was a spike in newcomers registering, and this should be because of his reputation in the universe.

While the majority of them were victims of EsGod, there were two people who attracted Han Xiao's attention.

...

In the reception room within the Black Star Army Headquarters, Shazik and Lothaire sat in front of Han Xiao. The three of them sized up each other.

Han Xiao's gaze swept across the two of them. His expression was unreadable as he spoke. "Both of you are Calamity Grade Supers. Are you serious about joining the Black Star Army?"

Shazik nodded and solemnly said, "EsGod destroyed my entire hometown, and my reason for living was to take revenge on him. I once swore that if someone could help me take revenge, then I would follow him."

Lothaire had half of his face covered, and he only coldly nodded in response. He did not talk much.

"If that's the case, then on behalf of the Black Star Army, I formally welcome you two aboard."

Han Xiao smiled. A Calamity Grade was a high-level combatant and could live a life of luxury in any organization. Thus, he definitely would not reject them.

The reason these two caught his notice was not just because they were Calamity Grade but because they were famous NPCs.

In the past, EsGod had rampaged in the universe for many versions and made many enemies. Both Shazik and Lothaire were people who appeared in the storyline of EsGod, and they were both enemies of EsGod.

Shazik ran a gray transit station in the Central Galaxy's desolate universe belt, and while it looked like it provided services to the criminals, it was actually a venomous snake in hiding.

During the time he was in business, he secretly bribed the people in Fallen Ark, collecting intelligence to disclose to EsGod's enemies while also quietly sheltering the various organizations that sought to take revenge against EsGod. He provided them with weapons and spaceships, and players who had joined the universal civilizations could accept missions from him.

Shazik used all sorts of methods to nibble away at the influence of the Fallen Ark, but what the universe did not lack was crime, and thus, his speed of destruction could not overcome the speed at which they recruited.

In the end, because players who accepted asylum from him posted about it on the forums, his behavior alerted a player of the Fallen Ark faction, who then revealed his identity. He died at the hands of a bunch of criminals.

As for Lothaire, he was even better. This was a madman that dared to try assassinating EsGod. He had a mid-level Luck Glow around him and was a revenge-type template of a main character.

Lothaire was a bounty hunter who specialized in assassinating members of Fallen Ark. In the middle versions, he had established a secret organization named 'Assassin's Society'. It was not a large organization, but all its members were elites, possessing some reputation in the universe.

This was a hidden faction, and only players who had passed the test would be able to enter. Within, they would be able to obtain the subclass [Galactic Assassin] and could learn all sorts of assassination related skills from the members present. There was also an S ranked mission, [Assassinate EsGod].

In the past, the Assassin's Society had high popularity because a large portion of lone wolf players liked the feeling of being assassins. This was especially so if one was an assassin in the universe, as they could assassinate all sorts of great characters, then watch the chaos it brought.

Lothaire had the strength of a Beyond Grade A seed at his peak, and he appeared and disappeared like a specter. As an assassin known for his lethality, his deterrence force was even stronger than a normal Beyond Grade A seed. He far outstripped Hadavy in terms of strength and was ranked at the forefront for assassination in the universe.

A pity that, because he could no longer withstand the fear he got from his nightmares of EsGod, he finally attempted to assassinate EsGod alone. With that, the strongest assassin never returned, dying at the hands of EsGod.

Based on their past records, Han Xiao looked more favorably on Lothaire's strength. If he could obtain his loyalty, there was a lot of value in grooming him.

Upon recalling Lothaire's past, Han Xiao had an idea.

I can create a small squad within the Black Star Guards, which need not stay near me, but move out on black ops. They will only answer to me, and I can call them the Shadow Guards or Shadowers...

This would allow Lothaire to once again create an assassin group similar to his past life. This might allow him to attract lone wolf players and use them to complete some shady objectives.

Just as Han Xiao was absorbed in his thoughts, Shazik took out a data storage device and placed it on the desk.

"Your Excellency Black Star, this is my greeting gift for you."

Hearing his, Han Xiao tilted his head, asking curiously, "What's inside?"

"A portion of EsGod's legacies," Shazik said in hushed tones. "Before we left the Central Galaxy, I mobilized all my undercover agents and seized a few of EsGod's research bases. From there, we took their inheritance. This is my offering for joining the Black Star Army."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled, and he looked at Shazik with praise.

This leek truly knew how to do things and even brought fertilizer for him.

He was reliable in doing things, a talent!

The various organizations are now trying to divvy up EsGod's inheritance. I didn't expect that by sitting at home, I would also receive a copy.

Pointing with a finger, he shot out a ray of nanoparticles, which entered the port of the data storage, directly linking to the stored data within.

"Phillip, read the data inside."

"Roger, hum..."

Han Xiao closed his eyes, reaching into the quantum network. His brain, under the guidance of Phillip, quickly downloaded all the various information within.

There were quite a few goodies within, such as intelligence on certain civilizations, blueprints from lost civilizations, and special technology research reports.

After browsing for a while, Han Xiao found traces of the Evolutionary Civilization and was overjoyed.

With the instructions from the Evolutionary Civilization, he could now manufacture the containment block by himself, which solved one problem. Now, he need not be afraid of destroying the containment block to release its actual shape, and there were more methods to utilize it.

This information was priceless to him!

"What good stuff." Han Xiao suppressed his excitement, quickly flipping through other reports.

Suddenly, his eyes narrowed. A certain report had captured his attention.

Oh, this is... a Super High Risk Esper Ability‽

Chapter 901: Clue on [Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy]

Han Xiao frowned and scrutinized the report.

"This is the observation record and prediction coordinates of the [Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy]..."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

EsGod had been conducting research on mastering Super High Risk Esper Abilities for many years. One method would be to synthesize the abilities, and the other would be to directly find the whereabouts of such an ability.

Within the Super High Risk Esper Ability Restriction Treaty, not all abilities were derived from self-awakening. There was a super high risk Esper ability that was rare and unique, known as 'Primal Energy Body', which could exist as a life form in the form of an energy field. It had its own independent consciousness and was an ancient existence that flowed through the universe.

This kind of ability allowed a biological user to harness its power in the form of a possession, and they were called 'hosts'.

However, the screening conditions were extremely harsh. If the strength of their energies conflict, no matter how powerful the Supers were, they could not bear the original energy body. Therefore, only Espers or ordinary people had the opportunity to become hosts. If the host was unable to carry the energy body, there would be a backlash.

Biological creatures below the Calamity Grade would be completely unable to withstand its strength and would implode due to the immense energy.

If successfully possessed, the host could use the power of the energy body. The host's power would then come from an external source, and they would act like a launcher. The stronger one's body, the more strength could be utilized, and the host would not need to develop the strength. This alternative ability was rare and much stronger than self-awakening an ability.

[Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy] was one of these 'Primal Energy Bodies'. It was a compound ability, covering multiple abilities such as physical fitness, firing radiation beams, and super speed. It could also allow the host to travel in space and extract the energy cores of stars, as well as possessing spatial and mental attribute abilities. It was well rounded and extremely powerful.

In history, there had been a few cases where hosts of [Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy] were recorded. All of them left startling records, pushing this ability onto the list of Super High Risk Esper Abilities.

In his previous life, the [Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy] was one of the Super High Risk Esper Abilities that EsGod grasped in the later versions. He did not become a host but rather managed to rip off part of the [Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy] body and obtained a portion of the [Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy].

This storyline was quite interesting, as it was unknown if the piece ripped off was the reproductive organ of the energy body, but the energy body went berserk and tried to reclaim that piece at all costs, searching for hosts to fight against EsGod.

Thus, there appeared two hosts capable of using the [Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy], and as though it was some drama where one sky could not hold two suns, they would fight. As for the host, he was also one of the important characters in EsGod's storyline.

The [Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy] shuttled through the secondary dimension usually, only occasionally appearing in a corner of the universe. This report recorded where the [Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy] had moved and predicted its next location.

"Since EsGod obtained that ability in the future, out of the predictions here, one should be accurate."

Han Xiao stroked his chin, feeling a little moved.

While he could not possess any Esper Abilities, he could always use it to nurture his followers. Although they were bound by the Super High Risk Esper Ability Restriction Treaty, the specific implementation varied from person. With his current status, as long as he did not allow his people to abuse their ability, the Universal Civilizations would not care about him. After all, there was something known as 'privilege'.

As for the method of capturing the Primal Energy Bodies, it was not an issue at his current stage. It was more than enough to create a containment device that could restrict an energy life. Many civilizations had this technology.

However, the time stated for the [Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy] was still far away. He had plenty of time to prepare.

Han Xiao nodded.

According to the data, he had decades before the next return. Preparing it now would be too early. As long as it had not appeared, going to the coordinates would be useless.

However, this time would not be as relaxed as obtaining the Spacetime Amber. It was likely that not only Shazik had managed to obtain this data, so there would be competitors.

Let's think about it more when it comes. If push comes to shove, I can just snatch it... Han Xiao did not care much.

With his current strength, he was not afraid of clashing with any organizations, let alone decades later. Who knew how much the Black Star Army would have developed by then?

Retreating from the quantum network, Han Xiao renewed his gaze on the both of them, nodding.

"I'm very satisfied with this gift, Shazik. I feel that you have some ability in the area of intelligence gathering and intend to put you in that department. How about it?"

"I will accept any position." Shazik did not have any objections.

Han Xiao nodded. He felt that Shazik was a talent in intelligence and might be able to lead it in the future.

He then turned toward Lothaire, and after pausing for a moment, he said, "As for you... I will not give you any positions at the time being. Just follow at my side for now."

This main character was quite strong, so he decided to allow Lothaire to lead a special ops team in the future... but not at the moment.

This guy had just entered and required a period of observation.

"Okay." Lothaire's words were like gold to him.

"Then you two may go rest up and familiarize with the headquarters."

Both nodded and left the room.

Han Xiao sat on the sofa, sending them off with his gaze before leaving the room himself.

He went straight to his grand, exclusive machinery factory before allowing Phillip to arrange the information on the Evolutionary Civilization.

He had only glanced at it just now and finally had the time to study this in depth.

The Evolutionary Civilization's technology had long been lost, and even the information on EsGod's hands was incomplete. It could not explain the principle behind the Evolution Cube and only acted like an operation manual.

After reading it, Han Xiao realized that his usage of the Evolution Cube was actually very rough.

As a Universal Treasure that a semi Universal Civilization had created, its purpose was not that simple. The Evolutionary Civilization had used it as a special energy source and had developed a variety of devices for it to be utilized differently.

For example, one of them acted like a totem device, where it used the energy of the Evolution Cube as fuel, and the influence of the totem could be adjusted to cover up to the entire planet. Unlike the one-time improvement of the Evolution Cube, the effect of the totem device was gentler, similar to a buff. If maintained for a long period of time, it would slowly increase the talent and potential of a planet's inhabitants so that the awakening rate of the planet's supers soared. This was equivalent to transforming the planet, allowing the newborns to become stronger.

There was only one Evolution Cube, but one could create as many Evolutionary Totems as they wished. They just had to be charged to be used. The Evolutionary Civilization had utilized this to great effect to improve the talents of their civilization; the efficiency was high and results controllable.

"This is good!" Han Xiao's eyes turned into dollar signs.

With such totem blueprints, the Evolution Cube's value would rise several times in the eyes of the other civilizations. The value could not be estimated.

But this was also useful to the Black Star Army. This could be used to slowly enhance the talents of all their soldiers in the subbases.

There was also a device worn on the body, called the Ovitan Badge, which used Evolutionary energy as fuel. It could carry out an ultimate evolution of the wearer when activated regardless of the consequences, turning a normal person into a biological aberration. Their combat power could even reach Grade C or B just from the evolution. This effect was more potent than any strength enhancing drugs, and the duration ranged from hours to days. However, when the effect ended, the user would collapse and die.

There was also a chance to break through the genetic locks and become a perfect evolutionary being, but the chance was so miniscule that it was not considered at all.

Only when faced with great danger would the Evolutionary Civilization resort to this method.

Han Xiao immediately thought of the perfect users for these—the players!

The army's nuclear explosion backpack had always been a hot product, and eighty percent of the players would definitely ignore the effects of the Ovitan Badge.

"With this thing, the death-strike gameplay is going to become famous again."

When his players next went out to fight, if they all transformed into monsters, this might give people the impression that his people were undergoing some human genetics experiment, viewing them as an evil faction camp.

This function also has a long-range method of attack. The data from EsGod recorded an offensive method as a special missile that carried the evolutionary energy similar to that of the Ovitan Badge. After hitting the surface, the energy would spread and contaminate all living beings within the range, and they would all turn into aberrations, waiting to die.

The Evolutionary Civilization only needed to wait for their genes to collapse and die, and they could easily capture the territory without damaging any structures. These were simply biological weapons that could kill creatures with the utmost precision.

"What a frightening weapon," Han Xiao remarked. In the exploration era, the Evolutionary Civilization did not utilize such weapons at all.

At the back of the document, various techniques for connecting one's soul with the Evolution Cube were also recorded. In the words of the Evolutionary Civilization, this was known as 'resonance'.

Every Evolutionary Civilization guardian of the Evolution Cube had to form a soul connection with the Evolution Cube, and this was a skill passed down every generation.

"This has made it easier for me." Han Xiao's eyes lit up.

Since Psyker had removed his Soul Connection, the quota had been vacated.

Another Soul Connection to a Universal Treasure would also increase his strength.

Speaking of which, this little Evolution Cube seemed to have had many owners before and was technically a spoiled flower.

It was unlike the Spacetime Amber, which had given its first time to Han Xiao.

Han Xiao immediately shook his head, throwing these weird thoughts out before clapping his hands.

"There's now a job for me to do. Let's first do a mass production of these containers."

Chapter 902: Evolutionary Totem

A couple of days later...

Within his dedicated machinery factory, Han Xiao had constructed a production line for the totems and Ovitan Badges based on the instructions, and he had set it to run automatically. During the assembly, new products would be released all the time, and they were automatically delivered to the warehouse specially designated by Han Xiao. As for the Gene Collapse Missile, he has not put it into mass production for the time being but had just created a test product.

Han Xiao took out three samples for a test.

The Evolutionary Totem was a black cylinder with a height of five meters and a diameter of two meters. Its surface was inscribed with a silver energy circuit. At this time, it was in an inactive state because it was not charged.

The Ovitan Badge was the size of half a palm and the shape of a diamond. It looked unassuming at first glance.

Han Xiao used his finger to trace the pattern of the password on the base of the totem device. With the sound of gears connecting, the base rotated to reveal a black lacquered groove, which was the interface of the energy circuit where the fuel was located.

Taking out the Evolution Cube, Han Xiao activated it, and a thin stream of evolutionary energy flowed into the groove.

The next instant, the totem shuddered.

Hum!

The totem device activated as fuel was put in, the silver lines lighting from bottom to up and beginning to slowly flash at a frequency like breathing. The evolutionary energy underwent an invisible process of dilution, which was then released in an invisible radiation wave with a constant output power.

"The current energy is enough to be used for more than ten days. The more fuel I put, the longer the duration, with an upper limit of twenty years of operation."

Han Xiao carefully scrutinized the operation mode. From his senses, he could see that the device had turned into a radiation source. It continuously radiated the diluted evolutionary energy, which would cover the entire Black Star Army headquarters.

He was included in the influence range, and his interface refreshed with a new buff.

[Continuous Genetic Optimization]: You are enveloped by evolutionary radiation, and your potential qualifications will slowly increase, which will add more options when sublimating into a new life level.

Han Xiao nodded to himself. Directly using the Evolution Cube enhanced the potential qualifications, and these were hidden attributes that were directly related to one's attributes. Each time they improved, their attributes got closer to perfection.

Because the totem device slowly altered one's genes, the advantage was that the effect was not restricted by one's strength level. Furthermore, there was no side effect like Exp Penalty.

As long as one was within the influence of the totem, the buff would not disappear.

Han Xiao stretched out his hands and touched the totem device, and a series of words popped out.

_____________________

Evolutionary Totem (Active): A special product of the Evolutionary Civilization, utilizing energy of the Evolution Cube as fuel to optimize the genetic structure of the organism on a large scale. It enhances the potential of biological creatures and increases the awakening probability of Supers.

"While we have grasped the method of evolution, I firmly oppose the Vice President's concept of custom population and extreme evolution. Evolving should be done step by step, and big supplements are not as good as moderate supplements." — Usain, Evolution Cube Technology Institute, Project 'Totem' Supervisor

_____________________

"This thing can be utilized on a large scale, but I need to first report this to the dynasty."

Following the division of EsGod's inheritance to many forces, the information of the Evolutionary Civilization was bound to be circulated. While it would not be disclosed in the universe, most advanced civilizations would be able to get their hands on the intelligence, so concealment was impossible.

Furthermore, as an ally, it was only natural to share it with the dynasty. Only then would he be able to gain greater support and attention.

The Evolutionary Totem technology, once spread out, would make the attractiveness of the Evolution Cube rise several times. Only by helping the dynasty would they then continue to help him block the people coveting it.

Selling the Evolutionary Totems to other civilizations would also have to be discussed with the dynasty. Both sides were allies, and he could not decide everything on his own. Large scale sales would cause dissatisfaction with the dynasty, as they did not wish to see their opponents enjoy the benefits provided by the Evolutionary Totem.

As he thought of this, Han Xiao picked up the Ovitan Badge, and another series of words popped out.

_____________________

Ovitan Badge: The special product of the Evolutionary Civilization. Allows for Evolution Limit: Aberration to occur through extreme modification of the user's genes, and the user has a high probability of turning into a biological aberration, where their basic attributes have been greatly strengthened. When the duration of the energy ends, the user will be unable to suppress their own genes collapsing and will inevitably die.

"Countless failed extreme evolutionary experiments have cost us a lot of money, and the upper echelons have accused us of not producing results, so we created this based on the experience of our failures. Cr*ppy by-products they were, originally intended to deceive our investors, but they seemed to be very satisfied with this, causing our funding to increase by 40% the following year." — Banjadi, Evolution Cube Technology Institute, Vice President]

_____________________

Han Xiao toyed around with it for a while before putting it back.

The side effects of this toy were too great, and he was not interested in testing it out himself.

The Ovitan Badge possessed no lethality to Beyond Grade As, who would control their own bodies extremely well. Even if the energy entered their bodies, they could excrete it given some time. Just like detoxification, this level of biochemical toxin was not even able to kill a Calamity Grade, let alone a Beyond Grade A.

Compared to the Evolutionary Totem, the value of the Ovitan Badge was far less, but it was still useful.

"I can change the appearance of the Ovitan Badge to serve as the new Black Star Army emblem. Other organizations' emblems are purely for decorative purposes, but mine has an added insurance within." Han Xiao stroked his chin. "I should first find a few players to test it out before selling it."

As for the Gene Collapse Missile, Han Xiao did not bother charging it, only looking through the introduction.

_____________________

[Gene Collapse Missile]: A special biochemical weapon of the Evolutionary Civilization. It can cause the collapse of biological genes and is often used to occupy planets.

"This weapon is suitable for clearing the resistance of a planet's surface but is useless in interstellar wars. In contrast, I still prefer the small portable gene collapse bombs." — Molin, Evolution Cube Technology Institute, Head of Weapon Research and Development

_____________________

Taking out his communicator, he sent the Evolutionary Totem's report to Urranrell's private number, and his communicator rang after a short while.

After connecting, Urranrell's long distance projection appeared in front of Han Xiao.

"Black Star, you've created the Evolutionary Totem?"

"Yes, and I've tested it. It works perfectly. This is my reason for contacting you."

"Very good!"

Urranrell was overjoyed, but her face did not reveal her happiness.

She paused for a while, as though suddenly realizing a problem, and her tone grew solemn.

"There are many organizations that have obtained EsGod's inheritance."

"That's right, but there's only one Evolution Cube that can supply the energy." Han Xiao nodded. "I'll send a batch of Evolutionary Totems to the dynasty, and I'll only begin sales of the Evolutionary Totems to other civilizations but on the premise that they will not harm the dynasty's benefits. I'll mainly sell to the other civilizations that have a closer relationship with the dynasty."

Urranrell's eyes lit up.

"That's great. I understand."

The Evolutionary Totem would be a great attraction to all civilizations, and the dynasty had the ability to hoard it all, but doing so would only incite resentment, which was unfavorable to Han Xiao."

Han Xiao's intentions were for the Evolutionary Totem to be used as a bargaining chip. The civilizations that wished to obtain it must be part of or allied to the dynasty, and this would attract more political allies, which would also allow him to harvest more contacts and money.

Rather than restricting it, the dynasty would have the meat, and its allies would get the soup. If they opened a channel for the other civilizations to obtain, then the pressure would be a lot less.

Furthermore, this was not a one-off transaction. The Evolutionary Totem required fuel to operate. Otherwise, it could not be used, so the civilizations that purchased this would have to maintain long-term cooperation to renew the contract with Han Xiao again and recharge the totem. This created a passive income flow for him. In addition, even if the Evolutionary Totem appeared on the black market, the civilizations that purchased it could not use it forever.

Urranrell considered it for a while before accepting the proposal.

After all, the Evolutionary Totem was not some mass weapon of destruction, and it was something that would benefit the people. All advanced civilizations studied genetic technology, but it was not as powerful as the Evolutionary Civilization. Thus, the totems would not be a need but a want. While it was good to keep it for themselves, the dynasty was not the strongest civilization, with the Federation of Light and the Arcane Church on the same level, so it was better to consider an option that would be a win-win.

After disconnecting, Han Xiao thought about it before opening the faction interface and releasing a task.

_____________________

Trial Tester Needed

Mission Introduction: Black Star has manufactured a new product and requires volunteers to help test out the product (risk of death).

Mission Requirements: Help Black Star test out the new product.

Reward: 100,000 Experience, 500 Black Star Army Contribution Points, and 50,000 Enas.

Remarks: The mission is only restricted to 10 people. The test will begin in three hours. If not present by the testing time, -1,000 Contribution Points and -20 Black Star Favorability.

_____________________

Because only ten people were needed, the moment the mission was released, it was immediately snapped up.

...

Three hours later, the ten players arrived at the venue, guided by Phillip, looking around.

One of them was Bun-Hit-Dog.

The Fall of EsGod had made him smell a scoop, so he immediately ran back to the headquarters in hope of meeting Han Xiao and managed to come across this mission.

"Bun-Hit-Dog, you're also here."

"You piece of sh*t, hurry and update your stream!"

"Will you be afraid if I pull out my blade and threaten you now?"

The other nine players greeted Bun-Hit-Dog passionately.

Because the Black Star series had gone through so many updates, it had long attracted many fans, and Bun-Hit-Dog was like a celebrity in the eyes of these players.

After bantering around, the door suddenly opened, and Han Xiao walked in with his hands behind his back.

"Good day, Army Commander!" Bun-Hit-Dog immediately pulled himself away from all the others and saluted Han Xiao with an ingratiating smile.

"Oh, it's you. Long time no see." Han Xiao patted him on the shoulder.

Bun-Hit-Dog could not help but feel touched at this camaraderie.

Han Xiao then turned to the rest and dryly coughed. "Since everyone has arrived, let's begin. But let me warn you. The side effects are pretty severe this time."

As he spoke, Han Xiao took out ten fully charged Ovitan Badges with the Black Star Army emblem on it.

The ten players took a badge each, browsing the item introduction.

Seeing the introduction, the eyes of Bun-Hit-Dog lit up, and he began the recording function.

The players also knew that the Evolution Cube was in the hands of their own Army Commander, but Black Star did not allow the players to use it freely. The appearance of the Ovitan Badge could be an omen that the Evolution Cube was going to be spread to the players soon.

"Whenever you're ready." Han Xiao nodded.

Everyone looked at each other and did not hesitate, pinning the badges on.

While the introduction told them there was a high risk of death, the reward was 50,000 Enas, which was no small amount for the players. It was worth it.

The first player who activated it underwent a heaven shaking transformation.

His flesh multiplied, and bone spurs burst out from his body as he swelled up like a balloon. He quickly turned into a biological aberration more than five meters tall, looking like a monster with sarcomas all over his body. The muscles all over his body and face were torn apart.

The other nine players were stunned and unconsciously stopped their activation.

Before they could speak, the transformed player noticed his appearance and yelled, "The f*ck! Just what sh*t did I transform into‽"

Chapter 903: Transformation

"Woah, what a large lump!"

"This item is a little interesting. This looks a little like an Ultraman transformation."

"This looks like a biochemical transformation!"

"Wow, he really looks a little like a Creeper..."

"No, no, no, this is a Ravager!"

"Bullsh*t, look at his sexy bone spikes. He is obviously a Skeleton Horse!"

"I didn't study much, but don't lie to me. This is obviously a monster from Balala the Fairies."

The players all gathered around with curiosity in their eyes.

Their height was only up to the transformed player's crotch, and they were like dwarfs surrounding a giant. The players then stretched out their hands to touch the body of the transformed player.

"Oi! Watch where you're touching! You're touching my ass! Why don't you transform yourself if you're so curious‽"

That player was exasperated and swung his palm out like a heavy hammer. The few players surrounding him were immediately sent flying and crashing into the alloy walls.

The players who were sent flying were not angry at all. They all stood up and puked out a mouthful of blood before crowding forward again excitedly.

"Wow, that attack dealt a lot of damage. How powerful."

"Hurry up and check your attributes."

The other players pestered him by the side.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled as he watched the scene before him.

The Ovitan Badge was an item that had been through many rounds of improvements and modifications. The Evolutionary Civilization would not create soldiers that lost all reason. Thus, the transformed being would maintain a certain degree of their consciousness and would not enter a [Chaos] state. It was just that their intelligence level and mental resistance would fall, and they were only capable of making some basic judgement. However, because of the uniqueness of the players, they would not experience any changes to their mental state after using the Ovitan Badge.

This meant that his theory was right. The players were the most suitable bunch to use the Ovitan Badge!

They did not lose their rationality and could fully utilize their strength after the evolution!

Han Xiao coughed and interrupted the players. "How are you feeling right now? Can you still control your body freely?"

"I can." The transformed player performed a few actions curiously and displayed his stunning dexterity. His nails transformed into sharp claws to scratch his bald head.

Han Xiao nodded, and nanoparticles gushed out from his sleeves to form a golden needle.

"Don't move, let me check your body."

As he said that, Han Xiao stabbed the needle into the transformed being's body, and combat information popped up.

The Ovitan Badge seemed to exist in the form of a buff, and this player was currently experiencing the buff.

_____________________

[Evolution Limit: Aberration]: Your genes have been reconstructed by the [Ovitan Badge], and your Class has been temporarily changed to [High Grade Biological Aberration].

Basic END boost will be transformed to 1:200, +30% STR, DEX, and END. -50% INT, MYS, and CHA.

Additional attribute changes: +240 STR, +200 DEX, +200 END, -300 INT, -300 MYS, -500 CHA.

1.3x physical resistance, 0.4x mental resistance, +200% Health and Stamina recovery speed.

You will lose 300–600 Health every minute, and your Health will fall by 30% – 60% every half an hour. Your Health limit is reduced by 10,000 – 20,000 every hour.

-90% effectiveness of any close combat equipment (including but not limited to mechanical equipment and magic tools). A portion of incompatible skills and talents will be frozen (unusable). +100% energy and stamina consumption of skills. Your close combat attacks will have [Hack] and [Sweep] effects. +70% close combat damage. +25% [Suppressing Force] and [Crushing Force] success rate.

Remark: Dance to your heart's content before your death!

_____________________

Woah, how ferocious!

Han Xiao excitedly analyzed the effects of the badge.

The transformation had obviously prioritized close combat strength, and the gene evolution path that the Evolutionary Civilization had set leaned toward strengthening the body while weakening the mind.

After all, the initial motive of designing the Ovitan Badge was to scam investments... cough cough, create a suicidal civilian army. Thus, strengthening the body was the fastest way to raise an individual's strength.

After the transformation, their biggest improvement was in their tankiness!

During Version 3.0, the player's level limit was 120. When he was at level 120, his health was about thirty thousand, and the players, who did not have any Molding Talents, should have about ten thousand health with their basic Endurance boost being one to fifty. After the transformation, the player's health was increased by four times!

Just this extra boost provided by the transformation would provide the players with forty thousand more health, and together with the few hundred points of Endurance that a level 120 player had, it was possible for their health to break the hundred thousand mark. Just from their health alone, it was sufficient to be compared to an ordinary Calamity Grade Super!

An ordinary level 120 player would have their attributes in the range of the hundreds. As such, the boost to their Strength, Dexterity, and Endurance would be almost doubled.

Thus, the benefits of the transformation were extremely obvious. If a player transformed when their HP was low, there was definitely a chance to turn the entire battle around.

However, the weakness was also extremely obvious. An individual's Intelligence and Mystery would be greatly reduced, and their mental resistance would be frighteningly low. Furthermore, a lot of the frozen skills would be the long-ranged skills, resulting in the transformed being's long-range combat capability being extremely poor. If the transformed being could not drag the enemy into a close ranged battle, it was very likely that the transformed being would end up becoming a live target board.

Just as he was viewing the combat information, Bun-Hit-Dog and the others also saw the attribute panel being shared by the transformed player.

"F***! This is too overpowered!"

"Although he is extremely ugly, I can accept it!"

Everyone then activated the badges excitedly, and eight more beasts appeared in the room. Feeling their powerful strength, they jumped around the room like monkeys. Bun-Hit-Dog was the only one who did not transform.

Bun-Hit-Dog swallowed a mouthful of saliva and asked Han Xiao with agitation, "Army Commander, will this item be sold to everyone after this test?"

Han Xiao looked at him and said, "Hmm, although the side effects of this item is extremely large, it is very useful. I will produce it in large quantities and sell it to the members of the army. As for whether they want to buy it or not, that will be their personal choice."

Bun-Hit-Dog's eyes widened, and he instantly knew that this matter would be world shaking news.

This was his exclusive content!

I am going to be trending for sure!

Following which, Han Xiao got the players to perform a few tests and obtained valuable research data. Finally, the players' health dropped to zero, and they revived back into their original forms.

After confirming the usage of the Ovitan Badge, Han Xiao could also be at ease and gave the ten suicidal players their mission reward. He then watched as they left excitedly, and he got Phillip to place the Ovitan Badge in the army's store. At the same time, he had also refreshed the interface of the faction store.

The product name was also changed, and it was not called the Ovitan Badge. Instead, it was called 'Black Star Army Badge: Evolution'. The picture on the badge was the Black Star logo of the Black Star Army.

Because the core technological skill required was the Evolution Cube, the production cost of the Ovitan Badge was extremely low. Furthermore, it could be reused as long as it was refilled with energy. Han Xiao set the price of such a powerful equipment at 150,000 Enas and 2,500 Contribution Points. The price of the Ovitan Badge was akin to that of a spaceship, and his profits were sky high! The price that he had set was mainly to target the player group.

After all, to an ordinary member of the army, using the badge meant instant death. The frightening side effects and price would keep them far away from the item, and not many of them would buy one. But in the player's eyes, this item was like a divine item, and dying meant nothing to them at all!

Not just in Version 3.0, the Ovitan Badge would be extremely useful before the players reached the Calamity Grade!

Of course, there was another reason for setting such a high price: to control the combat capability of the players. Furthermore, it was impossible for all the players to have the money to purchase such an item. Han Xiao was even planning to charge a fee for refilling the energy of the badge, and this would spur the players unable to afford it to do more missions...

What a perfect cycle.

The only problem was that the image of their army would be affected. After all, which proper organization would create so many transformed creatures?

...

At the same time, Bun-Hit-Dog left the testing room and immediately posted a thread on the forums.

'Shocking! The Black Star Army's new item is actually...'

The thread included the entire testing process and a large number of pictures and videos. At the same time, the [Black Star Army Badge: Evolution] also went on the shelves of the faction store, and Bun-Hit-Dog's thread became extremely popular!

The players all began to reply to the thread.

_____________________

Strange Things: Shocking! The product was just placed on the shelves, and you already have a review‽

Vice Commander's Spaghetti: How frightening. Is this the speed of the army's reporter?

Sandy Wind: I am currently at headquarters and just got off the spaceship. Did I miss some big news‽

Sprouting Melon: My goodness. The effect of this tool is too perverse.

Use Tyrant If You Want to Be Bald: The price is also equally perverse. My liver is crying out for help...

Zhang Weiyu: The wealthy players are very happy. Hang in there! You have almost emptied my entire wallet.

Maple Moon: How ugly. I would rather be killed by a boss than use it!

Rat Who Likes to Eat Bamboos: It isn't ugly at all! This is called the beauty of violence!

Bi Bi Bear: Would you rather be a handsome boy for your lifetime or a powerhouse for a few hours?

White Jewel: I'm sorry, but I choose to be a handsome boy.

Army Commander's Big JJ: Too awesome! The Army Commander made such a frightening item, so his class should be Mad Scientist, right?

My Wife Is Called Feidin: Upstairs, you really changed your name!

I'm Really Not Too Bad: This tool is like the item of an antagonist. I finally found out that the Black Star Army is actually an antagonist faction. We should change our name to Protective Umbrella Army.

Elephant Waving Whip: Black Star's ratings have been affected

Germinal Organization Leader: I am smiling at all of you in heaven.

Wind Colt: I think that the 'Black Star Army Badge: Evolution' is truly a treasure for fight dungeons. It is the best item for the main tank. We can finally kill all the bosses that have been torturing us.

Jupiter: Guild of Gods is purchasing Enas in large quantities, and the price is negotiable. Please contact the guild's customer service players if you are interested. They are online 24/7. Guild of Gods has a good reputation and is definitely reliable.

Jade Green Sky: Temple of God is trash. There isn't a need for explanation.

Jupiter: Haha, your Long Sky should wait for your deaths during the upcoming Pro League! Defend your title if you can!

Jade Green Sky: How sour, how sour. Some club didn't even make it into the top eight–

Sun Eggplant: ?

Dancing Fish Dragon: ?

Perfumed Bear: ?

Jade Green Sky: Wtf! The three powerhouses of Fried Eggplants with Fish, this is definitely unintentional!

Sun Eggplant: NMSL[1]

Second Prince: Hahaha! I am going to die from laughter!

Li Ge: +1

_____________________

Apart from some useless banter, the majority of the players were discussing the effects of the [Black Star Army Badge: Evolution].

Every player only had ten chances to revive within six days, so this side effect was still acceptable to them. Many players could see the value of this tool.

Because of the high price, only some wealthy individuals and squirrels were able to afford it. After looking at the thread, many players were tempted and immediately placed an order with Phillip.

There was a limited number of badges available, and they could only pre-order them at the moment. Han Xiao planned to launch the product officially in a few days and got the logistics department to first set up an assembly line.

Han Xiao and the Dynasty Ruler came to a verbal agreement on the business for the Evolutionary Totem. The actual details of the cooperation would only be confirmed after an official response from the dynasty was given. A Universal Civilization was extremely large, and even if the power structure was simple, there would still be plenty of red tape.

Han Xiao could make use of this time to form a connection with the Evolution Cube based on the methods recorded by the Evolutionary Civilization. This was a long-term process, and it could not be rushed.

Han Xiao merrily viewed the forums and went back to his room. He suddenly thought about something.

"Right. Phillip, show me the footage of Shazik and Lothaire. I want to see how they are blending into the army."

"Hum."

Han Xiao entered the quantum network and checked on how Shazik and Lothaire were getting along with the old members of the army.

Shazik was extremely normal and was still familiarizing himself in his new environment. He was getting along pretty well with the people from the intelligence department, but he did not have a great sense of presence. However, this was not a disadvantage for an intelligence officer but an advantage.

The situation with Lothaire was a little different. Lothaire was used to being alone and did not interact with the other officers. He would be either training in the training room alone or sharpening his blade in the room while staring at the wall in a daze. He was like a loner.

Han Xiao thought for a while and headed toward Lothaire's room.

When Lothaire first joined, he was rushing to take a look at the Evolutionary Civilization's information and did not communicate much with the other party. Han Xiao decided to head over and have a good conversation with Lothaire.

Based on combat strength and potential, Lothaire was definitely ranked among the top five in the army and had even exceeded Hadavy. He was only second to Hila, Aurora, Feidin, and Nero. He was a peak expert below the Beyond Grade A realm. Han Xiao placed great importance on Lothaire's potential and thus felt the need to care about his mental health.

After all, EsGod was his nightmare, and he was now freed from his nightmare. Since he had snatched the enemy from the other party, Han Xiao felt the need to take responsibility for that. If not, a loner like Lothaire might end up losing himself in the future.

[1] This is Chinese slang. It's the initials for "Ni Ma Si Le", which means your mom's dead. Back

Chapter 904: Ames' Invitation

With his gaze fixed on the edge of the blade, his finger glided lightly across the sharp edge of the blade, and he could clearly feel the sharpness of the blade.

In the room, Lothaire was seated beside the table, stroking his black blade that had accompanied him throughout his entire life as an assassin. The light from the table lamp was not reflected by his black blade as his weapon was created from a special material that absorbed all light.

Lothaire's mood was completely unlike his calm expression.

He had been in the Black Star Army for a few days, and he was like an invisible individual. He could not fit into the boisterous atmosphere of the army and maintained his usual style.

Lothaire had chosen to come to the Black Star Army from afar because EsGod had been caught. First, he wanted to see what kind of person Black Star was, and second, he was currently at a loss.

EsGod had stolen his innate talent and had been a recurring nightmare to him. Lothaire did not like to sleep as he would be always shocked awake by his nightmares. Assassinating EsGod had been his only target.

Now that EsGod had been defeated by someone else, Lothaire no longer had the chance to take his revenge. Lothaire did not have any hobbies, and his friends had all passed away. His lone wolf personality meant that he did not like interacting with anyone else. He did not have any ambition and did not know what to do next. Should he continue hunting the fugitives of Fallen Ark, or should he sheathe his blade and drift around? Perhaps he should find a planet to lead a secluded life.

Lothaire felt that life had no meaning, and thus, he had decided to come to the Black Star Army and serve Black Star for a period of time to repay his debt. When he felt that he had repaid his debt to Black Star, he would choose to leave.

Just as he was in a daze, the doorbell suddenly rang, and Lothaire snapped out of his daze. He subconsciously gripped the weapon in his hands before realizing that he was in a safe place.

He then returned his blade to its sheath and stood up to open the door. It was Black Star who had come to visit him.

They looked at each other for a while before Lothaire said, "Do you need something?"

"We haven't had a proper chat before. Since I am free now, are you going to stand at the door to have a chat with me?" Han Xiao replied.

Lothaire paused for a moment before stepping aside to let Black Star in.

Han Xiao walked into the room and casually looked around before sitting on the couch. He then raised his chin at the seat opposite him to ask Lothaire to sit down.

After Lothaire sat down, Han Xiao looked at him and said, "I have been paying close attention to you, and from the resume that you've given me, you are a powerful Calamity Grade assassin. I think very highly of you and thus wasn't in a rush to assign you a job."

"Ok."

Han Xiao then said, "You don't like speaking, right?"

"Yes," Lothaire replied calmly.

Han Xiao chuckled and said, "It doesn't feel good to be lost, right?"

Upon hearing that, Lothaire trembled slightly.

"Trust me, I understand your thoughts. You are different from Shazik. He truly wishes to repay my favor, but I can tell that you are different. Your target was only EsGod, and now that you have lost your enemy, you do not know what you should be doing. Thus, you decided to work for me for a short while. Am I right?"

Lothaire did not write his past experiences on his resume, but because of the information from his previous life, Han Xiao was extremely clear about Lothaire's experiences and character, so he was able to easily deduce what he was thinking about.

"Right." Lothaire let out a long breath and nodded.

"I can see your insistence toward EsGod and thus guessed that your hatred toward EsGod isn't as simple as him destroying your homeland. You may have met EsGod personally before and witnessed how frightening he is. Furthermore, he has become your nightmare."

Lothaire looked at Black Star with his eyes widened in shock. These were the secrets hidden deep within his heart, and he did not include them in his resume. He rarely revealed these experiences of his to outsiders, and he truly did not understand how Black Star could tell.

They rarely spoke to each other, so could it be that Black Star's observational skills were truly so terrifying? Black Star was able to guess his own thoughts just by meeting him a few times?

"... You are right. I met EsGod, and I was an Esper who had my ability stolen by him." Lothaire suppressed the shock in his heart and spoke with a calm expression.

"Then you are really lucky to still be alive."

He knew that Lothaire's hatred toward EsGod was carved deep into his bones. After all, the innate Esper ability that he had been born with had been stolen, and even if Lothaire managed to turn his fate around to obtain a similarly powerful strength, he still felt hatred toward EsGod.

"You must have suffered a lot to obtain the strength that you currently have." Han Xiao comforted him.

Upon hearing that, a trace of agitation could be seen in Lothaire's eyes as though he recalled some unpleasant memories. However, he quickly snapped back to his senses and lowered his head silently with a strange feeling in his heart.

He had spent many years alone without any friends or comrades. At this moment, he realized that Han Xiao understood him, and after hearing Han Xiao's consolation and seeing his sincere smile, Lothaire felt a little moved.

It has been a long time since someone cared for me...

If it was an ordinary person who said those words, Lothaire would not have thought about it too much. As a Calamity Grade Super, he was not so easily swayed by the words of others. However, Black Star was a Beyond Grade A, and he was no more than a little boy in front of Black Star. Black Star was a powerhouse far above him, and Lothaire was moved by the concern shown by this powerhouse.

In truth, there was another reason. In order to get Lothaire to open up to him, he activated Chen Xing's Character Summon Card while talking.

_____________________

[A Flirtatious Smile]: +688 CHA.

_____________________

It seems like it was useful indeed.

Lothaire let out a long breath and replied with a hoarse voice, "It is all over now."

Han Xiao shook his head and said softly, "You don't need to keep it all in your heart. Perhaps you have been alone for far too long, but you must understand that regardless of what the future holds, you are no longer alone. I am your superior, and I hope to understand your experiences."

Lothaire fell silent for a while. He originally rejected the idea in his heart, but upon remembering that Black Star was his benefactor, he gradually began describing his past.

Because he had not spoken so much for such a long time, speaking felt a bit foreign to him at the start. However, he was very quickly overwhelmed by his emotions.

He did not have anyone to pour his heart out to in the past, so Lothaire kept everything bottled up. Letting out those feelings, he was truly in a much better mood.

Han Xiao listened silently. In truth, he already knew all this; he only wanted Lothaire to feel better by letting all his emotions out. At the same time, he could also increase the Favorability that Lothaire had toward him. Since Lothaire had just joined the army, loyalty would not fall from the sky without any relationship between them.

"This is the way. I think very highly of you, and I will be willing to listen to you if you are willing to speak." Han Xiao nodded.

"Thank you." Lothaire let out a long breath and felt his entire body loosen up. At the same time, the fear in his heart toward EsGod also decreased a great deal.

He was truly overwhelmed with favor as a bigshot like Black Star was willing to sit down and talk to him.

"Let's end here today." Han Xiao stood up with a smile. "I hope that I can trust you with ease one day."

"Hmm." Although Lothaire still did not say much, his tone was completely different and was no longer as cold as before.

"I will give you a mission soon, and I hope that you won't be so listless at that time. I'll be going now."

Han Xiao turned around and walked out.

Lothaire leaned against the door and watched Han Xiao's departing figure.

It seemed like his decision to join the Black Star Army was not too bad.

...

A few days later, the Logistics department created a large batch of [Black Star Army Badge: Evolution]. After Han Xiao filled them all up with energy, they were ready to be sold.

Some of the players who had nothing better to do returned to headquarters for the goods. As for the players who were dealing with the Gulal Civilization, they could only wait for the Logistics department to send the badges to them.

Very quickly, the first batch of players personally experienced the effect of the tool, and many new posts were created on the forums.

The players participating in the civil war in Gulal used the badge in actual battle and recorded the scene of the battle. Han Xiao then opened one of the posts and watched a video.

The video showed a scene of the players clearing up a city from all resistance. There was an artillery tower being erected in the plaza with a large number of Ancient Emperor Party ground troops. The powerful firepower of the enemy decimated all the attacking players and forced the players to hide.

The players participating in the war then communicated with each other, and ten players wearing the [Black Star Army Badge: Evolution] stood up and raised their badges toward the sky.

"Ultraman, transform!" one of the Pugilist players roared, and their bodies began expanding rapidly.

"Roar!"

The ten transformed players charged out to tank the incoming firepower while charging at full speed.

They used their powerful life force to withstand the firepower of the enemy, and looks of fear could be seen on the enemies' faces as they saw the approaching monsters.

Two of the transformed creatures were killed along the way, but the others managed to charge into enemy lines and rip through the defenses of the enemy

_____________________

Testicle Fist (Poster): Personally experiencing the effect of evolution. My body became outrageously tanky, and it is super useful for charging.

Maple Moon: Although it is a little ugly, it is truly useful...

Moon Shadow: The quality-price ratio is pretty high. However, it is still extremely expensive. Refilling it requires another 5,000 Enas. This is extortion!

Starry Sky: Think about it. How can you be strong if you don't spend money?

_____________________

Most players used the badges in dungeons. The transformed body was extremely suitable to be a main tank, and it was perfect for handling bosses.

The badge immediately became a popular tool used to fight dungeons, and every party would have at least one member with the badge.

Some of the players immediately saw the business opportunity hidden within and gathered money to purchase the badge. They then collected fees to enter parties and provided their service to the players that could not afford one.

Very quickly, many different ways of using the badge were discussed on the forums, and after looking at it for a while, Han Xiao closed the forums. There was something else for him to do right now.

The Crimson Dynasty had already decided to sign an agreement with him, and he would be providing the Evolutionary Totems to them long term. He would have to provide a hundred million Evolutionary Totems within five years.

Because of the relationship between the two, Han Xiao would not be able to make any money from the dynasty, so his targets to make money would be the other civilizations. An important part of their agreement was the authority for Han Xiao to sell the Evolutionary Totem to other civilizations with the profits belonging solely to the Black Star Army.

The dynasty did not wait for EsGod's properties to be slowly exposed but took the initiative to announce to the entire universe about the Evolutionary Totem. A huge commotion was immediately created, and countless civilizations were stirred up!

The civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring that already had a cooperative relationship with Han Xiao were also shocked. The way they saw it, the value of using the Evolution Cube could not even be compared to the Evolutionary Totem!

Countless civilizations could no longer sit still, and the contact numbers of the army were engaged throughout the day. Many people tried to contact Han Xiao, hoping to purchase an Evolutionary Totem.

Han Xiao got Phillip to inform all the civilizations about his agreement with the dynasty. As long as they received approval from the dynasty, they would be able to purchase the Evolutionary Totem. As such, he managed to successfully push all the problems onto the dynasty.

As for the allied civilizations that had already joined the alliance, Han Xiao traded with them directly and signed a large number of orders. The sales figure of the totems reached the millions, and his business was spread across all the Star Fields.

He would not set the price of the Evolutionary Totem as 'cheaply' as the Ovitan Badge. As such, the Black Star Army made huge profits.

The Evolutionary Totem became a staple faction product of the Black Star Army, and the high profits from the product naturally attracted the jealousy of many organizations. However, the Black Star Army and Crimson Dynasty combination made many organizations forget about the idea.

The larger the business, the greater the strength required to protect it. The Black Star Army already had the strength to enjoy this cake all by themselves.

The Black Star Army was already a tyrant in the Shattered Star Ring, with many local civilizations in a cooperative relationship with them. A Beyond Grade A organization of such a level was already at the top of the food chain in the universe.

Furthermore, after the battle on Planet Lighthouse, everyone knew that it was incredibly difficult to deal with Black Star. Even the Arcane Church and EsGod had failed, and not many were confident that they would be able to deal with Black Star.

Furthermore, Black Star's organization was not alone in the Shattered Star Ring. The Shattered Star Ring had another four Beyond Grade As, and three of them were in a cooperative relationship with him. The network of his was truly frightening.

On top of that, the Shattered Star Ring was located right beside the Flickering World, and the dynasty had millions of battleships stationed in the Flickering World, ready to reinforce the Shattered Star Ring at any moment. Even the nominal owner of the Shattered Star Ring could only close one eye. Not many organizations dared to do as they wished in the Shattered Star Ring.

With the many considerations, no organizations would make a rash move at the moment and had to agree to the trade conditions set by the dynasty.

Han Xiao naturally would not forget about his own people. Every army division and training camp had the Evolutionary Totem, and Bennett also received the benefit of having the Evolutionary Totem. He did not forget about the Black Spirit Race either, and Han Xiao sent an Apostle Weapon to pass an Evolutionary Totem to them. At the same time, he sent some mechanical soldiers to guard the planet that the Black Spirit Race was located on.

Seeing their archnemesis earning such a huge fortune, the Star Pupil Holy Race was extremely frustrated. Originally, the members of the Star Pupil Holy Race no longer blamed Psyker as much, but after seeing the immense profits being earned by the Black Star Army, many of them felt their hearts ache and blamed Psyker for losing the opportunity to develop the civilization.

The wave of scolding within the civilization made Psyker extremely frustrated.

Heber also felt extremely bitter. He could clearly feel his status in the Shattered Star Ring becoming unstable. However, he did not have any ideas and could only watch as Han Xiao roped many organizations over to his side. His heart was as sour as a lemon at this moment.

Just when everyone's attention was focused on the Evolutionary Totem, Han Xiao received a special invitation for battle.

It came from Ames.

Chapter 905: Floating Dragon's Warning

The challenge letter was sent personally and not a public one, but it was not as casual as the usual interaction between the two. Instead, it was an official challenge and included the location and time of the battle—in five days on a desolate planet in the Godora Star System.

The news was too sudden, and Han Xiao was truly puzzled.

The relationship between them should not be a problem, and he did not understand why Ames would issue him a challenge letter without informing him beforehand. Furthermore, she did it in such a solemn manner.

Just what was she thinking‽

Han Xiao was currently in discussion with one of the civilizations about the trade terms of the Evolutionary Totem, and the moment he received Ames' invitation, he immediately hung up the call with the representative of the civilization and contacted Ames.

He did not wish for the alliance between them to go wrong.

The call went through quickly, but the one who picked it up was Jenny, not Ames.

"Why is it you?"

Han Xiao was a little puzzled. He had dialed Ames' personal number.

"Where's Ames?"

"You received her challenge letter, right?" Jenny asked.

"Yes, just what are her intentions?" Han Xiao frowned.

"Just like what is written on the challenge letter, before fighting you, she does not wish to speak with you, and she wants me to tell you that she will fight you seriously this time."

"Why did she suddenly decide this?" Han Xiao asked.

"You can ask her yourself if you have any doubts. Remember to arrive on time." Jenny snorted coldly and hung up.

Looking at the black screen on the communicator, Han Xiao could not help but scratch his head.

It was extremely normal for Beyond Grade As to spar with each other, but with their relationship, all Ames had to do was give him a heads up. There was no need to have such an official challenge letter at all.

Forget it, this isn't the first time Ames has behaved willfully...

Han Xiao shook his head with resignation and felt that Ames was once again behaving willfully.

...

At the same time in the main palace of the Floating Dragon Island, Jenny placed down the communicator and looked at Ames, who was seated on the floating throne.

Ames was listening by the side during the communication, and she nodded with a smile.

"Good work. Thank you."

"In truth, I don't really understand..." Jenny could not help but speak up. "Although I dislike Black Star, his strength is undeniable. Pardon me for being direct, but I don't think your chances of victory are high. Why do you want to do so?"

"You don't seem to have any confidence in me," Ames said with a teasing voice.

Aesop, who was by the side, could not help but interrupt. "This has nothing to do with confidence. After the battle on Planet Lighthouse, Black Star has already proven his strength, and your chances of victory are very low. Why do you have to issue a challenge that you will lose for sure?"

Ames kept her smile upon hearing that.

"We have to fight before knowing whether or not I can win."

She then paused for a while and let out a soft sigh.

"Perhaps I am no longer a match for Black Star, but I want it to be proven..."

...

Five days went by in a flash.

Situated in the Godora Star System was Planet G-S7058, a gigantic planet with an obvious asteroid belt revolving around the planet. This planet was not too far from the headquarters of the Black Star Army and Planet Aquamarine. It was the location of their battle.

A ray of light approached from afar and stopped outside the atmosphere of the planet. Han Xiao was the one piloting the spaceship, and he had come alone.

"Detecting a large unknown target. Matching it with the database... Match found. The target is Floating Dragon Island, hum..."

Phillip's voice sounded in the spaceship. Without his reminder, Han Xiao could also see the scene outside the window.

A gigantic Floating Dragon Island floated outside the atmosphere of the planet, and the entire planet was protected by a golden yellow shield.

Ten large alloy satellites were lined up beside Floating Dragon. These were the weapons that Han Xiao had given to Ames.

The eyesight of a Beyond Grade A was shocking, and Han Xiao could see that Floating Dragon Island had already activated their armed mode. All the buildings were retracted underground, and no one was moving around on the island. Ames was the only one standing on the dock, looking at him from afar.

Han Xiao's face contorted slightly upon seeing that.

She actually brought Floating Dragon over? Does she really want to go all out?

He then tried calling Ames' personal number, and Ames picked up this time.

Ames' calm appearance appeared on the screen.

"You're here."

"Since you sent me an invitation, how could I not come?" Han Xiao said with a helpless look. "You only need to ask me if you want to have a spar. It's not like I will reject you anyway. Is there really a need to make things so solemn?"

"You misunderstand me. This isn't a simple spar," Ames said slowly. "I will use all my strength to fight you, and I hope that you will also give it your all. You may lose your life if you are careless."

Han Xiao kept his smile upon hearing that and asked with a frown, "Just what is this about?"

"Ever since you entered the Beyond Grade A realm, I've fought alongside you against Heber and EsGod, but we have never had a proper exchange between us. Thus, I want to fight you officially for once until one side loses the ability to fight back."

"Is there a need to use such a method to see who is stronger between us?" Han Xiao did not understand.

"During this period, word of your actions has spread throughout the universe," Ames replied softly, "and in less than two years, you've gone from a new Beyond Grade A to your current status. I've watched you changing every day. Do you know that the feeling of being caught up to really isn't nice?"

When Han Xiao first entered the Beyond Grade A realm, both of them had a relationship of equal status, and Ames was willing to help Han Xiao, who was a new Beyond Grade A, overcome his difficulty.

In just two short years, Han Xiao had grown at a rapid speed, and the organization that he had set up had already far exceeded Floating Dragon.

Ames could feel that their status and strength were gradually becoming further and further apart, and their relationship was no longer on equal grounds. As such, her mental state also experienced a subtle change.

Ames was a carefree individual and could not be bothered with many things. At the same time, she was extremely stubborn toward the people she cared about. This point could be clearly seen when she had stubbornly searched for Aesop.

And Han Xiao was one of those whom she cared about.

Ames had once watched as Han Xiao rose to prominence, but the status between them was now reversing. She did not wish to see Han Xiao overtake her by too much and was not satisfied by only seeing Han Xiao's battle records on the news. As such, she decided to issue a challenge and personally experience Han Xiao's strength.

She wanted to see just how big the difference between her and Han Xiao was!

The next moment, the alarm in Han Xiao's spaceship rang.

"Detecting a powerful energy source!"

Han Xiao then looked over and saw that it was Ames releasing her energy.

Ames stepped out from the dock and into space.

The energy level in Ames' body was increased to the peak, and her tone became solemn.

"Don't hold anything back. Come!"

The next moment, she raised her arms, and the ten satellite bricks and Floating Dragon shot toward Han Xiao.

At this moment, a notification popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

You have triggered the S ranked mission ['Dragon Emperor' Ames]!

Mission Requirements: Last for as long as possible under Ames' attacks. (The battle method isn't restricted. You can only leave battle mode for 30 mins at most. There are no restrictions to the number of times you leave battle mode.)

Reward: You will be able to attain the corresponding reward by fulfilling the corresponding requirements. (Only 1% of the time out of battle mode will be counted toward the mission.)

This was the same mission that he had when facing the Tyrant. The longer he hung in there, the higher the reward.

Apart from experience, he could obtain Legendary Points, Character Summon Cards, and the opportunity to draw one of Ames' talents or skills.

However, Han Xiao was not in the mood to see the mission at the moment.

How can I go all out against you?

Han Xiao let out a sigh but did not say these words.

With his current strength, his attacks would be too lethal if he went all out.

She probably would not be able to tank his attacks.

Han Xiao shook his head. He did not plan on injuring Ames. No matter what, they were allies, and he would not go too far.

Seeing Ames' blazing battle intent, Han Xiao instantly made a decision.

Let me drag this battle out. My tankiness will be enough to exhaust all her energy so that she cannot carry on fighting. This is the only way to prevent me from injuring her and ruining our relationship...

The distance between them shrank rapidly, and Han Xiao no longer hesitated. He then activated his mechanical suit and opened the secondary dimension to summon a portion of his mechanical army.

"Lord." Psionic Prime appeared with various other Apostle Weapons.

Han Xiao then said with a deep voice, "Attack. Your main focus should be exhausting her. Do not go all out."

"Understood." Psionic Prime nodded, and flames shot out from his thrusters. He then charged at Ames with the mechanical army behind him.

The glow in Ames' eyes grew brighter and brighter as she inched forward slowly.

Force Field: Floating Dragon Planet Destroying Hammer!

The force field surrounding Floating Dragon rapidly expanded, and Floating Dragon accelerated like a gigantic meteoroid, smashing down toward the densely packed mechanical army.

This scene was like a brick slamming down toward a bunch of ants.

If Floating Dragon crashed down on a planet at such velocity, it would probably be able to destroy an entire planet.

Using her force field to swing her weapon around was the Dragon Emperor's style of combat!

The proper method for dealing with such an attack would be to destroy Floating Dragon. However, Han Xiao did not wish to destroy the other party's home and was truly helpless against Ames swinging her base around.

The mechanical army did not open fire toward Floating Dragon but followed their orders to allow Floating Dragon to break through their defensive line.

The outcome was obvious.

The gigantic Floating Dragon swung down on the tiny Han Xiao!

The shadow rapidly grew larger and covered everyone's view.

Looking at the gigantic continent-like brick smashing down toward him, Han Xiao could feel his balls aching.

Ames had once used Floating Dragon to save him, but now he had to endure being smashed in the face by Floating Dragon.

This was truly retribution!

Chapter 906: Exchanging Blows

In the universe, her force field was able to accelerate an object without any limits, and this was the battlefield most suitable for Ames. Her Force Field Esper Ability leaned toward defense and control, and it was extremely powerful in Ames' hands.

Under the control of the force field, Floating Dragon's speed continued to increase, and its gigantic body was like a super large scale attack. If Han Xiao allowed Floating Dragon to speed up without limit, it would be incredibly difficult to avoid it and become extremely powerful.

However, Floating Dragon still was not fast enough, and it was like a tortoise in Han Xiao's eyes. He had more than ten different ways to avoid the attack.

However, Ames was not an individual who only knew how to use bricks to smash others. Her eyes glowed brightly, and she released a force field to trap Han Xiao's body and pull him toward Floating Dragon.

Force Field: Gaze of the Dragon!

The space around him seemed to have frozen up, and Han Xiao's body endured a tremendous amount of pressure. He found it difficult to even lift his arm, and he was dragged toward Floating Dragon.

"I used this attack before in the past..." Han Xiao's mouth contorted.

With his current strength, he was not afraid of Ames' control ability and could easily break free from the force field. However, he was not planning on avoiding this attack. He wanted to obtain combat information through this attack and test the upgraded effects of his health and mana conversion.

Floating Dragon approached him rapidly, and Han Xiao could already see the various structures on the surface of Floating Dragon.

A powerful pressure assaulted him from the front, and he could feel a sense of danger approach him.

Han Xiao raised up his arms, and nanoparticles flowed on the surface of his mechanical suit to form a shield generator. A blue psionic shield then appeared in front of him, and he took a defensive posture.

The next moment, Floating Dragon smashed down on his shield and sent him flying far away while being stuck to Floating Dragon.

Ames then twisted her palm, and Floating Dragon's trajectory was aimed at the nearby planet, prepared to smash Han Xiao into the planet.

At the same time, the mechanical army led by Psionic Prime approached Ames and began to open fire.

Ames' ten satellite bricks were not idle either. Six of them surrounded Ames in different directions and were covered in a layer of force field to form a defensive formation.

The gaps of the defensive line were filled up by her force field and it can be said that her defensive formation didn't have a single blind spot.

The other four satellite bricks were then shot toward the formation of the mechanical army under Ames' control.

The mechanical soldiers were not so gentle toward the satellites and unloaded their firepower without restraint. The satellite bricks were immediately riddled with holes and craters with scrap metal floating around. These scrap metals then formed a metal whirlwind under Ames' control and roamed unhindered around the mechanical army.

The Apostle Weapons ignored these attacks and rapidly approached Ames' defenses. Psionic Prime waved his spear and struck the force field shield to create a hole in it.

The very next instant, a new force field filled up the hole. Just when Psionic Prime was about to continue attacking, Ames raised her finger, and a force field engulfed the Apostle Weapons and threw them out. Following which, an even more powerful force field was formed, and the mechanical army formation was split in two like Moses parting the red sea.

Ames' Force Field Esper Ability could restrict the Human Wave Tactic to a certain extent.

Right at this moment, a light flashed behind Ames, and Mad Sky Hunter appeared behind her. He opened his mouth and revealed his alloy teeth, biting down at her waist.

However, he only managed to bite air.

A white, sleek finger then tapped on Mad Sky Hunter's head. Ames avoided the attack by using Void Hyperdrive. After being strengthened by the Evolution Cube, her mobility had increased by a great deal.

Violent force field energy then entered Mad Sky Hunter's body through her finger.

Force Field: Seismic Wave!

Cracks immediately began to form on Mad Sky Hunter's body, and a large amount of spare parts dropped out from his body. His body was severely injured, and he immediately ran away in fear.

The Force Field Esper Ability had a wide range, but the strength of the force field would be more powerful the closer Ames was to the target.

All of a sudden, Ames felt fluctuations in the Void Dimension. Looking up, she saw Han Xiao, who was originally stuck on Floating Dragon, disappear.

Han Xiao swung his slightly numb hands and was shocked by the combat information.

"She was actually able to deal Crushing Force damage to me. Only a pugilist like Heber would be able to use his head to smash Floating Dragon up."

Although the damage was high, Han Xiao did not mind at all. There was a limit to how powerful Ames' AOE attack was.

His recovery speed was extremely high at the moment, and as long as the enemy's burst damage did not reach a certain extent or deal him a [Severe Wound] status, he would not be afraid.

Floating Dragon did not continue smashing down toward the planet but turned around to hammer down on Han Xiao. Its gigantic body brushed past the side of the planet and formed a huge sandstorm.

Ames, who was far away, used Gaze of the Dragon again, and Han Xiao could feel the force field restricting him again. He had already obtained the combat information and was not prepared to receive the attack again. He then placed his palms together.

Hum!

His mechanical suit vibrated and generated an endless stream of energy to form a small field around him.

This field successfully blocked Ames' force field on the outside, and Gaze of the Dragon became ineffective.

This was 'anti-Dragon Emperor' equipment that he had created especially for this.

This was equipment after all and had a limited effect. However, the strength of Ames' force field could be increased further, and she would definitely be able to break the field if she had enough time. Thus, Han Xiao did not plan on approaching Ames but played hide and seek with her from afar while controlling his mechanical army to attack.

Upon seeing that Han Xiao did not dare approach her, Ames took the initiative to move and flew toward Han Xiao while dealing with his mechanical army.

Upon seeing that, Han Xiao also retreated and maintained the gap between them. After getting out of the control of the force field, Floating Dragon Island was not able to catch up to him, and his mobility was higher than Ames'. Thus, he had the initiative.

Upon seeing that a single Floating Dragon Island could not do anything to Han Xiao, Ames' palms turned into claws, and she performed a grabbing motion toward one of the satellite bricks attacking the mechanical army.

This satellite brick then froze in place as though it was being trapped, and the layers of force field began to contract rapidly, which made the satellite brick vibrate violently.

Ames pulled her arm back slowly, and the force field continued to contract, accumulating a powerful rebound force. The next moment, her eyes shone brightly, and she clenched her fists. Like an arrow being shot out, the rebound force accumulated within the satellite brick exploded forth!

This satellite brick shot out toward Han Xiao at high speed!

Force Field: Satellite Cannon!

The terrifying acceleration took off a layer of the metal shell and almost disintegrated the satellite.

Han Xiao saw the satellite brick approaching him rapidly but did not bother dodging the attack.

At the same time, Silver Flash, who was waiting in the distance, transformed into his Planetary Obliteration Cannon main body and opened fire at the satellite.

The thick silver light accurately struck the satellite brick and penetrated through the satellite like a knife slicing through a meatball!

The next moment, the satellite began expanding from the inside, and a brilliant red light exploded from within. It exploded right in front of Han Xiao like an orange!

The satellite was instantly melted by the high heat of the Planetary Obliteration Cannon, and all the fragments transformed into red colored molten metal like orange juice spraying in all directions.

With the gigantic satellite exploding in front of him, Han Xiao casually avoided the molten metal spraying in all directions.

This seemed to have been a signal. A few more satellite bricks reached the limit of their durability, and another three had been destroyed by the mechanical army.

The number of satellite bricks that Ames had left was six. They were also riddled with damage and looked as though they would disintegrate at any moment.

"What will you do next?" Han Xiao muttered to himself, looking at the scene from afar.

Ames' attacks were extremely ferocious, but they did not cause much damage to Han Xiao. After many rounds of upgrades, his mechanical soldiers were extremely tough and no longer the inferior products easily crushed by the force field. Although Ames seemed to have the initiative, Han Xiao still had plenty of tricks up his sleeves and was in control of the battle.

Ames could also feel this, and her eyes narrowed.

My attacks aren't able to do anything to him and have all been neutralized...

She could tell that Han Xiao was on the defense and did not plan to attack. He was obviously going easy on her.

But even so, she could not do anything to him!

Has he grown to such a stage?

Ames' eyes narrowed, finally understanding Han Xiao's strength. The gap in their strength was already extremely obvious, and Black Star was much stronger than her.

However, she was not too affected by this revelation. The battle had not ended, and she would not give up halfway.

Ames then grabbed toward the planet, and the asteroid belt became her new weapon.

Force Field: Dragon's Breath Shooting Star Fist!

The asteroid belt was a large weapon stash!

No wonder she chose this place as the battlefield, Han Xiao thought to himself.

The asteroid belt became her weapon and smashed down toward the mechanical army. The mechanical army also destroyed the incoming asteroids, and the battle became a drawn-out battle under Han Xiao's commands.

...

Just when both of them were battling around the planet, a fleet was parked far away from the battlefield. This fleet belonged to Floating Dragon.

Because their base was taken by their boss as a weapon, these battleships could not remain on Floating Dragon Island. As such, it ferried everyone to watch the battle by the side.

Although house prices on Floating Dragon were extremely low because of the high risk, there were still some who would purchase property on Floating Dragon Island. At this moment, they watched as the property that they spent money to buy was being used as a weapon in the fight, and many of them could not help but be extremely anxious in their hearts.

In the main flagship, the Floating Dragon officers were looking at their leader fall into a passive state, and all their expressions were ugly.

It was true that Black Star was an ally, but they naturally wanted Ames to win since they were members of Floating Dragon.

Apart from the officers, there were another two projections watching the battle from afar. They were Hila and Aurora.

There was no need to make the battle a complete secret, and Vilna had informed Aurora and Hila. As Ames' students, they had a right to know.

"Our teacher isn't an opponent for Black Star," Aurora said with a bitter expression.

Hila also had a complicated look in her eyes and nodded.

Their status was much more awkward. They were the officers of Black Star and Ames' students. Both sides were people who they were extremely close to, and they did not know who to support.

Hila had followed Ames for ten years and was extremely clear just how powerful Ames was. She was filled with respect toward Ames, and upon seeing her respected teacher being suppressed by Black Star, she had a complicated feeling in her heart.

The energy fluctuations of the battle also made her understand that this was a battle that she could not interfere with. It was still far away from her current level. Regardless of how stubborn Hila's personality was, she could not help but doubt herself at the moment.

Beyond Grade As are truly too frightening, and a planet is only a toy to them. Can I really possess such strength?

...

Countless asteroid fragments and metal scraps floated in space. The battle between the two had lasted for a long time.

After utilizing her force field over such a long period of time, Ames' stamina and energy had been largely depleted, and her head was covered in sweat. She was obviously no longer in her peak condition, and the strength of her force field had decreased.

On the other hand, Han Xiao was still extremely energetic. He had [Advanced Energy Absorption], and his recovery rate was not something that Ames could compare to.

Since he did not lack any energy, he could use [Advanced Machinery Construction] and [Waste Modification] without any limit to revive his mechanical army and limit his losses.

As Ames began to slip up, Han Xiao gradually gained control of the battlefield. Ames' force field defenses had already been broken by the Apostle Weapons, and she had to deal with the harassment of the many Apostle Weapons. She could not even take care of herself and no longer had the strength to attack Han Xiao.

Psionic Prime then stabbed out toward her waist. Ames avoided the attack, and Psionic Prime's spear brushed past her force field to produce sparks.

Gold Sovereign then ambushed Ames from the front, and his punches were blocked by the force field.

Ames' leg then swung out like a whip, and her kick smashed a hole in Gold Sovereign's armor, sending him flying.

All of a sudden, another Apostle Weapon shot out a psionic cannon toward her. It shattered the force field at her back and struck her body. Ames' eyes then squinted as she felt the pain.

Upon seeing that, Han Xiao, who was watching the battle from afar, said, "That's enough. Her energy is already exhausted."

Right at this moment, Ames looked up at Han Xiao, who was slacking off by the side. A large suction force suddenly gathered toward her and sucked all the Apostle Weapons in her surroundings toward her.

Being caught off guard, all the mechanical soldiers were lumped together in a pile.

Han Xiao then felt fluctuations in the Void Dimension.

Without any hesitation, Han Xiao turned around and raised his arms to block the incoming kick from behind him. This kick came from Ames, who had used Void Hyperdrive.

"You actually dared approach me? Are you staking everything on a final, desperate attempt?"

Han Xiao's eyes glowed, and he pulled Ames' leg toward him with his other palm striking toward Ames' abdomen.

Bang!

Ames gathered her force field to block Han Xiao's attack and chopped down at Han Xiao's neck with her palm.

However, her palm had not found its target yet when Han Xiao grabbed Ames' neck. The thrusters behind him then activated fully and smashed Ames into a nearby asteroid.

The asteroid was smashed immediately, but Han Xiao did not stop there. He grabbed her and charged into the asteroid belt while using her body to smash up every asteroid in their way.

Their bodies transformed into a ray of light and did a lap around the asteroid belt. Who knew how many asteroids they had destroyed along the way? In any case, Han Xiao could feel Ames' force field becoming weaker and weaker, and it almost disappeared.

Han Xiao slowed down and smashed into an asteroid. This time, the asteroid was not destroyed, and both of them stopped.

A gas ring then shot out from the mechanical suit and enveloped both of them. Han Xiao removed his helmet and shook his head.

"Your energy is almost all exhausted. You've lost."

Ames' brows were furrowed at this moment as she endured the pain from Han Xiao's attacks. Her skirt was cut in many different areas to reveal her fair skin. Her neck and legs were still being held by Han Xiao, and she could not struggle free.

Upon hearing that, Ames revealed a smile and said, "No, I still have the strength for one last attack."

"Alright. Let me see what other methods you have," Han Xiao replied calmly.

Ames then raised up her arm and flicked Han Xiao lightly on the forehead.

It was an attack without any strength.

A look of surprise could be seen on Han Xiao's face.

Ames then retracted her arm and dissipated her protective force field. She then said with a smile, "Alright, I used up my final bit of strength. You win."

Han Xiao let go of Ames's neck and rubbed his head helplessly.

"So mischievous."

Chapter 907: Interest

One leg was still trapped under Han Xiao's arm, and the skin was plastered to the cold Mechanical suit.

Ames tilted her head.

"Please let go of my leg."

Han Xiao released his hold and retreated a little bit, allowing Ames to retract her long, snowy legs into her black dress.

After sizing up Ames's dress that was badly damaged in the battle, Han Xiao raised his palm, and nanoparticles flowed out, turning into a material that filled in the torn places of the fabric.

Kacha!

Ames used her Force Field to pull herself out from the meteoroid before dusting herself and stretching. Knocking into numerous meteoroids had given her quite a few bruises.

"Quite painful." Ames rubbed her slim waist and frowned. "Forget it, I suggested this spar. I was asking for it."

"I already stayed my hand." Han Xiao shrugged.

"Oh, indeed, you're now stronger than me."

Ames sighed, but her expression looked calm, as though she had expected this.

Black Star had a firm grasp of the battle situation from start to the end, and Ames had a more profound understanding of his strength now.

"There's no need to be discouraged. I..."

Before Han Xiao could finish, Ames cut him off and blandly smiled. "That's enough. Who do you think I am, needing to be pacified after I have lost?"

"It's a habit developed after I kept sparring with Hila." Han Xiao rubbed his chin in embarrassment.

He then turned to signal to his mechanical army to clear up the battlefield. Seeing the debris and wreckage floating around the universe, he commented, "The weapons I made for you are broken. I'll ask the logistics department to manufacture another for you later... Of course, you have to pay for it."

"I know." Ames nodded without objections. She had initiated this battle and even destroyed the weapon that Han Xiao had sent her. She could not allow him to just give her a new one. As a Beyond Grade A, she still had to maintain a level of pride for herself.

After the battle ended, the Floating Dragon fleet in the distance slowly approached. Ames took a deep breath, revolving the little strength she had recovered to control Floating Dragon Island to stop.

The protective shield of Floating Dragon was then opened, and the fleet landed at the docks.

The fighting mode of Floating Dragon was lifted, and the building structures that were hidden underground started to pop back up. Many of them rushed to check on their houses, assessing the damage.

The logistics team led by Haier also began their jobs to repair the houses.

Han Xiao and Ames adjusted their clothing before flying straight toward Floating Dragon Island. On the way, they attracted the glances of everyone present.

The members of Floating Dragon had all seen Ames losing to Han Xiao, and their boss seemed to have been taken advantage of. Thus, all their hearts were filled with some dissatisfaction.

Jenny rushed over impatiently, and after glaring at Han Xiao, she turned around to size up Ames, anxiously asking, "Are you okay?"

"Not really injured. Just consumed a lot of strength." Ames waved her hand and turned her head. "Black Star, let's go to my palace for a chat."

As she spoke, she started walking toward the main hall. Han Xiao removed his mechanical suit and followed.

After entering Floating Dragon's palace, Ames brought Han Xiao to the back garden, where they sat on the stone benches.

She manipulated her Force Field to pour two glasses of wine on the table. After taking it up to drink a sip, she saw Han Xiao not moving, and the corners of her lips curled up.

"This is the Dragon Bone Wine that was brewed by Aesop using the Void Dragon bones. I rarely take it out to entertain guests."

"To actually use those to brew wine, what a dark recipe," Han Xiao commented. Still, he lifted the glass for a sip. He only felt like a line of fire trailed down his throat, as though he was drinking lava itself. After this, a strong aftertaste surged back up, and he smacked his mouth as he savored the taste.

At this moment, Ames opened her mouth to speak, her tone a little emotional.

"Your strength now has surpassed me, and you only took twenty years... I've basically wasted all that time. Compared to you, I've been stagnant."

"It's not at the level of wasting it. You're just lazy," Han Xiao teased. "However, if you were to actually be hardworking, that would not be you anymore."

"In your heart, am I such a lazy person?" Ames rolled her eyes.

"Are you not?" Han Xiao laughed.

"Huh... I suppose, if I compare myself to you, I really don't have much motivation." Ames shook her head, unable to retort.

The fact that she had lost made her attitude toward Han Xiao have a slight chance. Every Beyond Grade A was clear on the difficulty to improve further, and the rule of the strong was always to respect those stronger than them.

Ames put down her glass, gazing at Han Xiao as she softly said, "To have reached this level in just twenty years, you must have suffered a lot."

Han Xiao paused, suddenly feeling as though this sentence was very familiar.

This phrase... now where did he hear that before[1]?

Suppressing the weird feeling in his heart, Han Xiao dryly coughed. "It was still ok."

"Now that you've already carved out an area for yourself in the universe, what other plans do you have in the future?" Ames changed the topic.

"Continue to develop, accumulate strength."

Hearing this, Ames paused, blinking her eyes rapidly.

"You feel that your ability now is still insufficient?"

"Before reaching the limit, strength will never be enough." Han Xiao shook his head.

"... There's actually something I don't understand."

Ames crossed her legs, holding her chin with one hand as she stared at him, and slowly spoke.

"Around eight to nine years ago, I asked you why you did not stop moving forward, and you said that you did not have the qualifications to do so yet refused to tell me the reason. What exactly are you afraid of? You're a powerful Beyond Grade A Super with great influence and have the Crimson Dynasty as a backer. What could make you so afraid?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao hesitated.

What he was afraid of was the ultimate boss of the later versions, the World Tree Civilization.

Eight to nine years ago, when he was still a Calamity Grade, their statuses had been different, and thus, he did not tell Ames. However, now that their statuses were similar, there was a certain gravitas to his words. Pondering about it, he finally made a decision and opened his mouth.

"I've received some news, and in the future, there will be a calamity of epic proportions in our universe. No one will be able to avoid it, and there will be nowhere to run."

Ames was a little surprised at his reply. "Such a calamity will be for the three civilizations to worry about. What's there to fear?"

"When the calamity strikes, Beyond Grade As will just be greater ants. How can the people below us be spared?"

Ames subconsciously stroked her wine glass as she muttered, "So, it turns out that you had this sort of premonition... I thought your drive came from your insatiable ambition."

She did not doubt Han Xiao's words. Everyone had different information channels, and just his position in the dynasty would allow him to grasp many of the secrets that she could not obtain.

Furthermore, there was no reason for Black Star to lie to her.

The atmosphere turned heavier, and Ames seemed deep in thought, whereas Han Xiao did not talk, instead appreciating the wine.

After swirling the wine around for a few rounds, Ames finally raised her head, her voice soft.

"Seems like I cannot laze around anymore. If there's such a day, I'll stand beside you to fight."

"That would be the best." Han Xiao smiled.

In the past, due to Floating Dragon Island being destroyed, the life and death of Ames during the World Tree version was not known. However, since Aesop had stayed in Floating Dragon and did not go out to roam the world, the previous tragedies that happened to Ames would not appear this time.

The influence Han Xiao brought about had changed Ames' fate. She should be able to last till the era the World Tree showed itself.

At this point, Jenny walked over and, pointedly ignoring Han Xiao, spoke in a low voice. "Your Excellency Dragon Emperor, the damage estimates are out. I need you to review them."

"Got it." Ames nodded and turned to Han Xiao. "There's some stuff I need to do, and my energy has not fully recovered yet. I need to rest."

Han Xiao stood up. "No problem, go ahead. I'll be on Floating Dragon Island until you recover. It's on the way for me to visit Planet Aquamarine anyway."

"Okay."

Ames knew that this was Han Xiao's way to showing concern and smiled.

Han Xiao nodded and turned to leave.

Sending Han Xiao off with her gaze, Jenny's cold face slowly thawed. She turned to look at Ames, her expression complex, and opened her mouth. Yet, she was seemingly hesitating over what to say.

"Hmm?" Ames glanced at her. "What do you have to say?"

Jenny opened and closed her mouth, finally gathering her courage.

"Your Excellency Dragon Emperor... do you like Black Star?"

Hearing this, Ames raised her brows.

"Why do you care?"

"I... I'm curious." Jenny gritted her teeth. "And I don't like Black Star."

"I knew the last part. You didn't need to emphasize it." A helpless laugh came out from Ames.

But Jenny shook her head seriously.

"Your Excellency, I hate Black Star not for the reasons you are thinking... Initially, no one came to provoke us due to our position as a neutral force. Our days were leisurely, and while our influence was limited, it was fine. But after he appeared, Floating Dragon has undergone so many dangerous situations, and I always think that without Black Star, there would not be such issues. He is not a simple man and will bring us into great danger one day."

Hearing this, Ames also smiled, and she thoughtfully asked, "So... you're thinking that Black Star and I are allied because I like him?"

"I've also observed your attitude toward him and cannot ignore this possibility," Jenny replied.

Ames nodded and laughed.

"Not bad, I have some feelings toward Black Star. What do you intend to do? Dissuade me?"

"I..." Jenny was shocked and did not know how to react.

"Ok, I'll stop joking with you." Ames waved her hands helplessly. "I do have some favorability toward Black Star, but who told you that was love? Just how old am I? Am I the kind that hides my emotions because of embarrassment?"

Ames then stood up. Her back was toward Jenny as she mused and looked out at the universe.

"Among the Beyond Grade As, Black Star is the only one whom I find pleasing to the eye. He beat me and has the qualifications to reproduce with me... but from the beginning till now, I've never entertained the idea of allowing a man within me to pass on his genes.

"My favorability toward him comes from the help he has rendered toward Floating Dragon and my admiration of him. My relationship with him is close, but he's at most a good friend and comrade I can trust. When have you seen us talk about love?"

Jenny breathed a sigh of relief.

Right, how could Her Excellency and Black Star have any relationship? She was probably mistaken.

However, Ames' next sentence shattered her hopes.

"However, the days are still long. If I ever change my thoughts of having descendants in the future..."

Ames thought of getting along with Han Xiao and shook her head as she laughed.

"Black Star is the only candidate."

Ka-cha!

The communicator in Jenny's hands was snapped in two.

...

Meanwhile, Han Xiao recalled his mechanical army and metal plates, allowing Phillip to control his spaceship to dock at Floating Dragon.

As the door closed, Han Xiao opened his interface.

The mission ['Dragon Emperor' Ames] had been completed. They had fought for over twenty minutes, fulfilling all the requirements.

And the best reward that he could obtain was a talent or ability from Ames!

Endure, endure...

Han Xiao breathed out and calmed himself down.

Feidin and Nero were not beside him, and he was definitely not going to use his bad luck to gamble.

Suppressing his itchy fingers, Han Xiao turned toward his other mission rewards—a large amount of experience, one Legendary Point, and one Character Summon Card of Ames.

[1] Han Xiao spoke the same phrase to Lothaire in Ch.904 Back

Chapter 908: Old Friend

The amount of experience rewarded was about the same as his mission for fighting against the Tyrant. Completing all the objectives netted him more than twenty billion experience, and this was basically the standard when faced with a Beyond Grade A task.

With the addition of political assets, Han Xiao's actual experience almost doubled, and his savings rose quite a bit.

Other than that, he also received a Legendary Point and a Character Summon Card.

Star Field Legendary Point (Shattered Star Ring): [Battle with the Dragon Emperor]—Your battle with the Dragon Emperor will be added to your battle records, and your reputation will be passed on.

Character Summon Card—'Dragon Emperor' Ames: [Force Field - Dragon Body]—Your body will be covered with a force field, and you will get additional shield durability equivalent to 300,000 HP and +3,000 defense. The shield regenerates at a speed of 30,000 per second, and if the shield is broken, there's a cooldown of ten seconds before it will reform. At the same time, each melee attack brings about 20,000 – 26,000 points of additional physical damage. When there is a STR judgment test, +1,500 points.

Duration: 30 minutes

Uses: 0/3

"Quite a strong effect. It should come in handy during close combat." Han Xiao nodded and switched off the interface.

After cleaning up the battlefield, Floating Dragon returned to its main base, and Han Xiao followed along.

The battlefield used for the spar was not too far from Planet Aquamarine and did not need much time to journey back. Floating Dragon Island soon reached Planet Aquamarine and stationed itself in outer space.

Spaceships could be seen rising from and descending to the blue planet. Right now, Planet Aquamarine had integrated with the interstellar society, and the development opportunities brought about by the financial groups also helped their civilization progress quickly. Now it also had the appearance of a galactic city.

After returning to his hometown, Han Xiao slowly looked over the changes in Planet Aquamarine, and after thinking about it, he invited Ames along.

Although Ames did not care much for her loss on the surface, Han Xiao needed to remove any negativity and maintain their relationship as allies. He would take this chance to properly interact with her, solidify their relationship, and reduce the friction to the minimum.

Ames looked at Planet Aquamarine every day, but she seldom went down to visit the surface city in person. With his invite, Ames obviously did not reject.

New Western Capital was situated at one of the original Six Nations, Stardragon.

Bennett's Black Star City was where the Black Star Army's sub-base was situated and also the political core of the Planet Aquamarine Federation. It continued to expand on the original Karst wilderness, attracted countless people, and had long become saturated. Later on, because the financial groups decided to focus their attention on the other cities that were not controlled so tightly, many other economic and financial cities were created around it, and the New Western Capital developed quickly, coming into the ranks of the first-tier cities of Planet Aquamarine.

It was just past noon, and the bright sunlight injected vitality into the city. The bustling streets were full of people, and voices clamored. There were not only natives but also many galactic citizens. With anti-gravity vehicles, public transportation carried people in an orderly manner across the city's midair cross-track network. This was a picture of peace.

Han Xiao and Ames hid their presence and aura, not letting anyone discover their presence.

The two of them walked side by side down the streets, observing the situation as they chatted.

Two kids chasing each other ran past Han Xiao, a carefree smile plastered on their faces.

Han Xiao kept his gaze and spoke emotionally.

"With the Mutation Disaster gone for almost a decade, the people in Planet Aquamarine have also walked out of the shadows, embracing their new life and producing a new generation. This kind of feeling is indeed good."

"This is the result of your effort. Are you feeling a sense of accomplishment?" Ames smiled.

"Just a little."

Han Xiao was not so humble. In the first place, he saved his mother planet purely out of the benefits of the Planet Aquamarine players. But seeing the results now, he was actually quite satisfied. No one disliked beautiful scenes.

"During the Mutation Disaster, you once invited me to view your mother planet, and at that time, I felt that it was full of despair and hopelessness. The people were confused about the future and did not know if they could survive past tomorrow. However, it's now another extreme." Ames shook her head. "It was you who gave the planet a new life."

"Then it's estimated that I'm probably the turning point in history, haha." Han Xiao laughed. When interacting with people he was closer to, he could not be so humble.

As they walked and chatted, they unknowingly arrived at the central area. Towering buildings clustered around the areas like pigeons waiting for food. This place used to be the old site of the Dragonhorn Tower in Stardragon. It had been remodeled into a new one, which was built by a financial group.

Seeing all these buildings, Han Xiao's footsteps stopped as the memories surged, and he could not help but have a sense of aloofness from this world.

At this moment, Ames seemed to have spotted something and tugged at Han Xiao's sleeve as she asked, "Hey, what's that store?"

Turning to where she was looking, he saw a shop across the street with the sign 'Black Star Heritage Exhibition Hall' written on the signboard!

"I've actually... become a cultural relic. It's not even been two decades..."

Han Xiao felt like vomiting. However, his curiosity overwhelmed him, and he walked over with Ames.

The automatic glass doors opened as they neared, and they walked into the exhibition hall. They saw that it had various glass showcases with various objects within.

However, the entire hall seemed to be cold and empty, without a single person present. There was a counter at the door, with a sign erected and the price of the ticket written. A woman sitting behind the counter seemed to be a clerk with her upper body lying on the table napping. She did not even hear the two of them enter.

With his Beyond Grade A eyesight, Han Xiao glanced toward the inside of the shop and instantly saw what was within the display cases. His mouth twitched.

"What sort of nonsense is this?"

The exhibition hall was filled with all sorts of messy stuff, such as 'Chair That Black Star Has Sat On', 'Slippers Black Star Has Worn', and 'Bread That Black Star Has Bitten'. There was even one that read 'Toilet Seat Thich Black Star Has Sat on'.

Han Xiao swore that he had never seen the toilet in the display case!

Ames blinked a few times, pointing toward one of the cases, and curiously asked, "Did you really like to wear diapers in the past?"

"You're the one who likes it!"

"Who didn't wear them when they were babies?" Ames opened her hands as she retorted.

Their voices woke up the clerk by the counter, and she raised her head, rubbing her eyes sleepily before showing herself in front of them while yawning.

"This is a small establishment, so we don't accept Enas as currency. One ticket requires 400 Aquamarine Credibility Points. I can explain the history behind each artifact if you're interested... eh‽"

The woman finally took in their appearances after she yawned, and her mouth, which had not closed, hung open like that as she revealed a shocked expression.

Han Xiao originally wanted to question where these 'cultural artifacts' came from, but after looking at her appearance, he suddenly felt that she looked a bit familiar. "Wait a minute..."

Before he finished speaking, the woman suddenly got excited and opened her arms wide, as though she wished to give him a hug.

But just as she got into the pose, her face froze as though she had thought of something, and her entire body paused in mid action.

The next instant, she put down her hands, and her expression became cramped, as though she did not know where to place her hands. She tentatively asked, "Han... no, Your Excellency Black Star, do you still remember me?"

Han Xiao frowned slightly as he closely looked at the woman. There were fine wrinkles around her eyes, and she seemed a little old, but she still had her womanly charms and had probably been extremely beautiful when she was young. She still maintained a good figure... but under the scrutiny of a Beyond Grade A, this sort of beauty did not have any attractive appeal.

With each advancement, it was a sublimation of life level. At the Beyond Grade A level, one could see the minutest of details, and most creatures were covered with dirt in a Beyond Grade A's eyes. Only others who were at the Beyond Grade A level would appear uncontaminated by dirt and dust.

Han Xiao scanned through the faces in his memory and matched with one of them. He said in a surprised tone, "You're... Li Yalin?"

The woman in front of him was actually his colleague back when he was working as an agent in Stardragon.

Seeing that Han Xiao recognized her, Li Yalin was overjoyed and nodded like a chicken pecking on millet.

"That's right, that's right. You really still remember me!"

"It's harder for me to forget things than to remember now," Han Xiao explained. "Turns out, you're still alive. I thought you died in the Mutation Disaster. Since you were alive, why didn't you go to the Black Star Army to find me?"

"I only survived out of luck, and later on, when the Six Nations were disbanded by you, I also lost my job and took the severance payment. I didn't want to fight anymore, so I didn't go to you. I bought a house here and opened this exhibition hall."

She suddenly remembered all the nonsense around them and let out an awkward smile. "Oh... that, I got all those things from the flea market and marketed them as things you've used before. No choice, life is hard..."

"... Relax, I'm not going to make trouble for you."

Seeing an old friend, Han Xiao's mood was very good.

"Old friend?" Ames suddenly spoke out.

"Yeah, an old comrade more than twenty years ago." Han Xiao nodded.

Because Li Yalin had focused all her attention on Han Xiao, she did not notice Ames. She snapped back and bowed. "To not notice Your Excellency Dragon Emperor, I'm sorry. Please forgive me."

Ames smiled as she nodded.

"Ai, we're already old friends. There's no need to be so polite." Han Xiao waved his hands.

"How can I?" Li Yalin was a little embarrassed. "You're such a famous character now."

With more than twenty years, her friend had now reached a level that she would never obtain and was a great planetary character that appeared on the news. Li Yalin had to withstand the urge to hug him after thinking of the gap between them.

Han Xiao also noticed this point and could not help but sigh that one's status truly differentiated people. After thinking for a while, he suddenly smiled.

"Now, come to think of it, I seem to owe you money."

Li Yalin paused before waving her hands. "That was so long ago. You don't need to be bothered about it..."

"Too late, already transferred." Han Xiao cut her off.

Ding!

From within the room came the sound of a communicator pinging.

"Hey, I didn't tell you my account number. How did you know..." Li Yalin was surprised, and she took out her communicator. After glancing, she froze in shock.

"Th—This..."

"One million Enas, enough to compensate for the interest accumulated for more than twenty years."

Han Xiao smiled and felt that he was radiating the aura of a wealthy wastrel.

"It's too much!" Li Yalin was helpless.

"This is not even a large sum for me, pocket money at most. You can rest easy and not worry about life in the future..." Han Xiao glanced around and dryly coughed. "So, find a time to close this shop."

Ames could not help but start laughing.

"You look like those galactic pirates that paid me a protection fee in the past."

"No one will think you're mute if you don't talk." Han Xiao spat back.

Seeing Li Yalin still standing there with a dumbfounded expression, Han Xiao looked around and fished out a paper and pen from behind the counter, writing down his communicator number and passing it to her.

"Next time if you have problems, call me. You can come find me anytime."

Li Yalin slowly regained her wits and solemnly folded up the paper before replying in a serious tone, "Thank you."

"There's no need. The money is a small matter."

"It's not about that." Li Yalin took a deep breath before bowing. "I'm thanking you for whatever you did for the entire Planet Aquamarine, for all the people you've saved, including me. I did not have the chance to tell you that previously... you'll always be the hero in my heart."

Ames also smiled at that and joked, "What about me?"

"Ah, you're also the heroine in my heart." Li Yalin hurriedly bowed toward her as well.

At this moment, some other guests walked in, and seeing the scene, they felt a little surprised before suddenly exclaiming.

"Your Excellency Black Star‽"

"Goodness, it's really him!"

Everyone rushed forward with excited expressions.

Among a hundred Aquamarians, probably only one would not know what Han Xiao looked like. A portion of them benefitted from the statue of him situated in Black Star City, while the other benefitted from the textbooks.

"I... Can I take a photo with you‽" One of them excitedly took out his communicator.

"Of course." Han Xiao smiled. Anyways, he had nothing to do, so taking a bit of time did not matter.

As they took pictures with Han Xiao, their ruckus attracted more people, which started to form a queue in front of the stall. The tiny exhibition hall became crowded, and it was extremely rowdy, as though there was a fan meet within.

Han Xiao did not refuse anyone and took photos with all the happy citizens of Planet Aquamarine. The lights flashed continuously, and group photos were posted on Planet Aquamarine's social network constantly.

The appearance of their 'Savior' spread quickly and attracted countless people to swarm to this location.

By the sides, Ames looked at Han Xiao and how he was welcomed by everyone, and the admiration in her eyes was apparent.

Chapter 909: Half a Year

As he was leaving the exhibition hall, Han Xiao went back to find Li Yalin to make up for the unfinished hug. In that moment, there was no status difference between them, just a reunion of friendship.

Twenty years had passed just like that, and his first group of friends all had their own personal experiences. Everyone had the freedom to make their own choices, and he would not interfere. Thus, after repaying his 'debt', he did not say anything else to Li Yalin.

After bidding goodbye, Han Xiao and Ames spent another ten or so days touring Planet Aquamarine's major cities. When they were spotted, numerous people would rush up to take pictures with them. This happened all the way until they met up with Bennett.

Since there were a multitude of photos posted on social media, Bennett knew that Han Xiao would definitely go to him and only waited, not disturbing him this time.

Since Han Xiao and Ames had a cooperative relationship with Planet Aquamarine, Bennett also prepared himself to meet the two.

After they finished discussing the formal matters, Bennett could not help to ask about Nero. Han Xiao told Bennett about Nero's heavy study load, but this reassured Bennett that Han Xiao valued Nero a lot and was interested in grooming him.

After finishing the inspection work on Planet Aquamarine, Han Xiao went back to Floating Dragon, with the intention of sneaking into Aesop's wine cellar to get some Void Dragon Wine to share with Hila, but it was foreseen by Aesop, who had moved his bed and toilet to the wine cellar, guarding it with his life. Thus, he could only return to the headquarters empty handed.

In her palace, Ames watched the spaceship fly toward the horizon and let out a breath, muttering to herself, "I can't be lazy anymore..."

When he returned to the headquarters, the first he did was look for Feidin and Nero, and after molesting them, he went to his room to collect his mission random reward.

You have received a Random Reward Draw of one of Ames' skills (Ability/Talent).

Alert: Ames is an Esper, part of the possible abilities have been automatically adjusted to your class.

Randomizing... complete.

Please select one from the five options below as the reward:

Pure Bloodline - Talent: Improve one's Racial Talent to a certain degree (cannot be quantified due to individual's talents being different)

Advanced Charm Aura - Talent: +120% CHA

Caretaker of the Stars - Ability: Passive Ability that is randomly triggered. One will be favored by the Stars and obtain a [Strong Luck] status, +90% LUK. Lasts for 15 days.

Activate Potential - Ability: Unleash one's potential, +10 – 15% Attack and +200% Crit Rate. Energy is continuously consumed in this state.

Heroic Wrists - Talent: You have frightening wrist strength, a strong body, and vigorous cell activity. As your character's overall level rises, your STR, END and Attack will increase.

- Lv1 – 100: Every 10 levels will give +30 STR, +15 END, and +0.6% increase in attack.

- Lv101 – 200: Every 10 levels will give +45 STR, +25 END, and +0.9% increase in attack.

- Lv201 and above: Every 10 levels will give +60 STR, +35 END, and +1.2% increase in attack.

"Whoa, jackpot!" Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Feidin and Nero were really his lucky stars, allowing him to draw all decent rewards.

[Advanced Charm Aura]'s bonus was quite impressive, and any talent with the word 'Advanced' would not be bad, but Han Xiao's demand for Charm was not high.

[Caretaker of the Stars] was a powerful skill, and its Luck bonus was high, but he had no demand for that, and besides... with one point of basic Luck, no matter how great the bonus was, it would still be around the same.

[Activate Potential] was a practical skill that would increase one's output, but it was lacking compared to the other two.

Han Xiao particularly favored the [Pure Bloodline] since it was a rare racial talent boosting skill as well as [Heroic Wrists] since it was a growth type talent.

However, there was only one reward that could be chosen, so after pondering for a while, Han Xiao made the decision.

You have been awarded with the talent Heroic Wrists!

Current additional states applied: +1230 STR, +680 END, +24.6 increase in attack.

He favored this sort of growth talent more as it was stable, strong, and full of potential.

In contrast, [Pure Bloodline]'s effect was too uncertain, and based off Ames' ability, the bonuses of this talent should be limited.

Moreover, his Racial Talent would undergo an improvement every time he underwent a Race Evolution. He was not lacking in this area. Furthermore, his main force of combat was his mechanical army, and Racial Talent could only be applied to his true body of mechanical host.

Currently, he only had the skills [Superhuman] and [Supreme Power] directly increasing his attack, which already brought forth a totally different dimension of attack strength, so the [Heroic Wrists] skill that directly increased one's strength was rare.

Han Xiao looked at his attributes in satisfaction before turning off the panel and tilting his head to consider the current situation.

Right now, it's the middle stages of the version. The external environment can be considered peaceful, and the three civilizations need time to quell their contradictions with each other. I've also established my position, and there should be no major events during this time... I can focus on my stable development till the end of the version.

In the past year, Han Xiao had been sharply driving up the organization's power, causing it to soar rapidly. Now was the time to slowly digest the various achievements he had gained, such as the greater attention the dynasty had on him, the deterrent power he had, and the profits from the Evolutionary Totems.

The army needs to be low-key and digest our fruits of victory, consolidating our businesses while waiting for the next opportunity for development.

In his plan, the next opportunity would be the end of the first phase of the Flickering World development. The dynasty had allowed him a portion of the territory within, and that would be the time to vigorously develop his mechanical civilization as well as the Black Spirit Race.

At the same time, that was also the opportunity to seize the advantage for Version 4.0. It would be the time when the global service would be opened, and the players of the major star fields would gather and begin the faction war. It would also be the time when the Fourth Calamity, the Cancer of the Universe, would be born.

It was inevitable that players would cause trouble in the next version. Thus, it would be a great advantage for himself and the players in the Black Star Army to secure a site within the global service area. At that time, the Black Star Army, as the largest player faction in the Shattered Star Ring, would not be able to avoid being involved in the battle between players. There were advantages and disadvantages, but there was no way to avoid the storm.

The players in the Shattered Star Ring had experienced too many things in Version 3.0. From the secret war early on, to their commander breaking through to Beyond Grade A, the alliance with the Crimson Dynasty, and even the exploration in the Flickering World and the battle of Planet Lighthouse. There was still the Gulal Civilization civil strife, which had yet to end.

Han Xiao estimated that, with the remaining time left, the Shattered Star Ring would likely not have any major events happening, so he could use this time to rest.

Fighting the Arcane Church and then EsGod had tired him out. It would be good for him to use this period to absorb the players' experience and rebuild his mechanical army.

It had been less than two years since he had become a Beyond Grade A Mechanic, and his mechanical army had yet to reach the level of Manison's. Let alone to Manison, his army was still quite small compared to the other senior Beyond Grade A Mechanics.

I'll do some low-key farming and not go around to cause trouble.

Under Han Xiao's strategic direction, the Black Star Army temporarily slowed down its development and turned inward to stabilize itself, consolidating its current scale and businesses.

The transaction of the Evolutionary Totem had set off ripples in the universe, with many civilizations deciding to reach a cooperative relationship with the dynasty in various ways, in order to obtain the qualification to purchase the Evolutionary Totem.

The Crimson Dynasty gained unprecedented political influence, and Han Xiao gained a large number of customers from the various civilizations. This resulted in an abundance of funds, achieving a win-win situation for the both parties.

This sort of monopoly resulted in envy and dissatisfaction among the financial groups, but it was pity. With the Crimson Dynasty as a backer and the Black Star Army's status as a local tyrant in the Shattered Star Ring, no one dared provoke them.

On the other hand, due to their previous issues, the three civilizations chose to consciously reduce friction with each other. Thus, the Arcane Church and Federation of Light chose to wait and see the effects of the Evolutionary Totem.

Due to their peaceful actions, the galactic environment became stable again. The impact of the Crimson Tide lasting for more than ten years also gradually faded.

The division of Fallen Ark also gradually settled. Some criminals were arrested by the three civilizations, while others went to join other criminal organizations in other star fields, and some became mercenaries.

The leftovers were reintegrated by other people and continued to act as Fallen Ark. Their leader seemed to be Fakisen, the once deputy under EsGod. The new Fallen Ark had shrunk in size dramatically and entered a dormant state, acting low-key.

As for the players in the Black Star Army, they were focused on two events, the exploration of Flickering World and the Gulal Civilization war. They helped the Pioneer Party occupy more land step by step, ousting the Ancient Emperor Party. Their influence on the war was growing larger, and they never grew tired of war.

Under this peaceful environment, more than a year passed quietly.

Version 3.0 had finally entered the final stages.

Chapter 910: [Ultimate Mechanical Engineering]

The metal bulkhead of the battleship was full of ridges and holes, and its exposed energy lines were badly damaged, constantly sputtering sparks. The cabin looked like it had experienced a fierce battle, where flames crackled and raged inside, and the ground was covered in the broken bodies of the crew members.

A group of warriors wearing full body armor carried energy guns around to examine the bodies, and whenever they found a survivor, they would fire.

The killed crew were all Rock Sprites, an older race with rough, tawny skin, an average height of about three meters, and covered in hair. Although they were made up of flesh and blood, they had naturally rock-solid skin and were good at uncovering rare ores. With their metal resources, they were a relatively powerful star system level civilization in the Sea of Star Spirits.

The uniforms of all the crew members had the symbol of their civilization, proving that this was a regular unit belonging to their official civilization. Yet, it was attacked, and the entire crew was annihilated.

At the very end of this battleship was a huge metallic warehouse door, and at this moment, the leader of the attackers stood in front of the closed warehouse door and took out a specialized tool to crack the code. The disc-shaped device was pressed on the operation panel of the door, and a high-frequency beep sounded.

Buzz!

The next instant, the door rang loudly and released its locks, slowly swinging open.

The leader strode in and saw hundreds of Evolutionary Totems neatly arranged in the warehouse.

"We've got the goods. Clean up and bring them back."

The people nodded in satisfaction, waving their hands as they brought their subordinates over.

The Rock Sprites had purchased a batch of Evolutionary Totems from the Black Star Army, and when this news was leaked, their attackers set an ambush, with the goal of snatching these Evolutionary Totems.

To be able to clear out the guards of a star system level civilization so easily... it was obviously not a small bandit group.

These attackers were also interstellar mercenaries, but their nature was different. Mercenaries were separated into three types: regular mercenaries registered under the Mercenary Alliance, such as the Black Star Army; independent mercenaries, who are not registered; and the last belonged to black market mercenaries, who worked to supply the galactic black market.

'Black Jobs' referred to criminal jobs that violated interstellar law, and these were normally posted only on the black market. They included looting, kidnapping, and assassination of officials. Black market mercenaries were usually criminals... In fact, the majority of people in the industry were originally wanted criminals.

This group of attackers belonged to a black market mercenary group that was one of the top organizations in the black market—the Blood Gold Organization.

The Blood Gold Organization was a black market mercenary group that operated around the Sea of Star Spirits, Ancient Star Desert, and Primeval Star River, and the whereabouts of its members, spaceships, and bases were kept secret. Their style of action was also low-key, which led to their exact size being a secret, but it was obviously a behemoth to be able to conduct business in three different star fields.

At the same time, the Blood Gold Organization was also one of the upper echelons in the black market.

Wherever there were controls for trade, there would exist black markets, which would continue to breed and eventually form a huge chain.

There were also different levels within a black market, distinguished by one's region and business scope. From planetary level to star systems to star fields, slowly increasing in scope until the highest level, which was the galactic black market that practically dominated all other black markets.

And this black market of the highest level knew how to make a fortune, or else they would not have given themselves the name 'galactic black market'. Those who did not do this might still think it was a term and not an actual organization.

Of course, not all independent black markets followed under the orders of the galactic black market, just like how some hooligans did not know who the kingpin of their underworld was.

The galactic black market was humongous, and its business covered the entire universe. There were always some civilizations that wished to obtain certain restricted technology and would turn to the black market. Thus, everyone turned a blind eye to its actions, which acted as a cover for it. The galactic black market also acted as a communication platform for a huge underworld society.

However, not all criminals existed for the sake of being evil; a large number were only in it for the benefits, so they also required order and credibility, and they required someone to formulate rules for them. Therefore, the administrators of the galactic black market came into being, with representatives from the mercenaries, intelligence organizations, smuggling trades, contraband production, and other gray industries.

The Blood Gold Organization was one of the administrators of the black market, and they were equivalent to one of the tyrants of the underworld.

The Fallen Ark was not an administrator of the black market, as the administrators typically fell on the Lawful Evil side. They also disliked EsGod, who was a Chaotic Evil. While both of them were criminal forces, they did not belong on the same side. After Fallen Ark fell apart, the Blood Gold Organization accepted a large number of criminals and helped them achieve re-employment.

An officer came to the side of the leader, and watching his subordinates carry away the Evolutionary Totems, he could not help but smirk.

"The price of the Evolutionary Totem on the black market is extremely high now. As far as I know, there are many civilizations that are secretly purchasing. How much do you think we can get if we swallow this batch?"

"Don't even think about it. This is what our employer wants, and our job is to deliver it. To think of swallowing the goods, are you thinking that you've lived too long?" The leader shook his head.

After a year and a half of sales, the business of the Evolutionary Totem had basically stabilized. Some civilizations that relied on the Federation of Light as well as the Arcane Church could not have a relationship with the Crimson Dynasty, and so, they could only start moving now.

No one had forgotten Black Star's battle records a year and a half ago, so the difficulty of stealing from the Black Star Army's spaceships was too high. As such, they aimed at the other organizations that transported the Evolutionary Totems, focusing on the civilizations that purchased them.

Because this violated Galaxy's laws, the black market mercenaries represented by the Blood Gold Organization now came in handy. The Evolutionary Totem was near priceless on the black market and always in short supply.

After stealing the Evolutionary Totems from the Rock Sprites, they destroyed the spaceship completely before they left.

In recent months, such scenes had taken place many times in various corners of the universe.

"Another buyer got robbed midway?"

Within his office in the Black Star Army headquarters, Han Xiao closed the player forums, looking at Sylvia's long-distance projection as he frowned.

"Yes, if we count the Rock Sprites, then there are already thirteen star system civilizations that have been robbed. Thousands of Evolutionary Totems have now appeared on the black market."

"Where did this happen?"

"Sea of Star Spirits. The identity of the robbers is unknown, and preliminary judgment points toward it being under the same organizations as the previous few."

Han Xiao stroked his chin. "Pay attention to the black market. If there are no Evolutionary Totems on the black market for some time, it should be the black market mercenaries. They usually hand things over to their employers."

"Teacher, do we need to deal with this problem?"

"No need to care. I'm not in charge of after-sales. Whether they can protect what they bought, it is not my problem... of course, if they choose to hire my machinery troops, then it would be a different problem." Han Xiao waved his hand. "What did the Rock Sprite tribe say?"

"They're hoping that you'll give him another batch?"

"Give? Not buy?"

"That's right. They know that the Evolutionary Totem has a low base cost, and they are unwilling to buy another batch at high costs, so they hope you can send them a batch. You also know that the Rock Sprites are direct with their words." Sylvia helplessly shrugged.

"Tell them that I don't run an insurance business. If they want to buy, they can buy another batch. There's no such thing as a replacement batch. This is a matter of principles."

Han Xiao shook his head. If he agreed to this, who knew if some civilization would choose the method of 'robbing oneself' to obtain a replacement. He would not do anything that would bring him a loss.

This sort of thing was hard to predict. There might be civilizations privately reaching agreements with other civilizations who were not close to the dynasty, indirectly helping them to purchase these Evolutionary Totems.

Moreover, Han Xiao did not mind the Evolutionary Totems being stolen. The more they were robbed, the more he would sell, and a larger market would help to ease the pressure off him. He was not losing money at this rate anyway.

The only problem would be the dynasty, not him. As long as it did not reach the Black Star Army side, he did not really care.

"Understood, I'll relay the message to them." Sylvia then switched off the projection.

Han Xiao spat out a sigh, leaning back in his chair as he pondered.

In the past year and a half, the Black Star Army had gradually stabilized and consolidated their businesses and operations. They had been developing well. His style of doing things was finally akin to a mechanic. He stayed at home to build machinery and expand his legion while his mechanical army went around to hoard missions for random rewards, using them to draw his Mission Completion Cards.

His experience reserve had also slowly accumulated, and a part of his accumulated Potential Points were used to upgrade his Ultimate Knowledges. During this period, he got his fifth Ultimate Knowledge, [Ultimate Mechanical Engineering], from the Dynasty for six thousand Contribution Points.

This knowledge was related to the manufacturing of machinery, greatly improving one's manufacturing technology and production line capacity. He also unlocked a large number of blueprints, giving him the talent of [Ultimate Manufacturer] as well as an ability [Inspirational Creation].

[Ultimate Manufacturer]'s effect was simple and practical, increasing the base performance of his machinery by 25 – 30%, as well as his production speed by 300 – 500%. Obviously, this was the talent needed for creating an explosive number of soldiers.

As for [Inspirational Creation], it was an inactive ability. The activation condition was for [Ultimate Mechanical Engineering] to achieve the max level of five. Its effect was to combine an unlimited number of blueprints in any combination to undergo Blueprint Refinement, creating new improved or merged blueprints. One could also choose advanced settings such as focusing on certain aspects such as attack or defense, which was more stable than random blueprints.

Levelling up this ability just needed experience... an ocean worth of experience.

For players who were unable to change their blueprints manually, this skill was akin to magic, but Han Xiao could improve his own blueprints, so this skill was not very useful. However, it was not completely worthless, as it had an irreplaceable role.

[Inspirational Creation] had a slight chance to synthesize the blueprints of Universal Treasures and was the only way for a Mechanic to create Gold Equipment!

Right now, Han Xiao possessed two Universal Treasures, but he would definitely not complain about having more. It was just that synthesizing a Universal Treasure was not that easy, as it was not like gambling for blueprints. There was no fixed combination, and even if two people combined the same blueprints, the synthesized final blueprint would still be different due to randomization.

In his previous life, there were players that indeed created Universal Treasure blueprints, but there were two problems with it. The first was that they did not disclose the combination, and the second... none of the blueprints were for Mechanics.

The prerequisites were too harsh, and there was basically no possibility of manufacturing it below the Beyond Grade A level, so many players could not even satisfy the prerequisites.

Thus, Han Xiao temporarily placed [Inspirational Creation] at the back of his mind. To even reach max level for [Ultimate Mechanical Engineering] required too many potential points, and while he had a large experience reserve, trying to synthesize the blueprint of a Universal Treasure would mean less experience in other areas, particularly since he needed to leave a reserve for during the version upgrade period. Thus, he did not dare waste his experience.

The overall situation in the Gulal Civil War had also been stabilized, and they were progressing step by step. There were no issues in the process as the Pioneer Party was about to taste the fruits of victory. However, the attention of the players had already shifted to the Pro League.

Because of the increase in players, the popularity of this version's Pro League had also risen, attracting much attention. This time, they were similarly separated into the nine major regions, and the schedule had already undergone fine tuning.

For example, the heats and qualifiers started earlier, allowing for ample time and enabling more players to participate in the Pro League. At the same time, this also allowed them to decide the wildcard quota, as well as the Pro League regular season list.

Han Xiao just watched the video of the qualifiers through the forums, appreciating the weird antics and idiocy of the players.

During the official competition, in addition to the ring, group, individual, and team survival battles, there would be three special battle types added.

The first was Capture the Flag, which was a free for all, and each player would be resurrected indefinitely. The winner would be decided by overall points.

The second would be a team dungeon game, where many teams would enter the same dungeon and challenge missions to earn points.

The last would be the survival game. Just like its name, it competed on which team could survive longer in the dungeon, which was also referred to by the players in his past life as the 'competition to see who could hold their pee back the longest'.

The competitive form was much richer this time round, and the goal of the Pro League was to enhance the competitiveness and interest in the players. The goal of adding the dungeon battles was also to attract more PVE players.

The rules of this Pro League were also much stricter, with a 'Prohibited Items List' being released. Not out of his expectations, the [Black Star Army Badge: Evolution] was placed at the top of the list!

The Black Star Army players did not feel much about it since everyone in their faction could use it, but the clubs in other star fields heaved a sigh of relief. This equipment was too overpowered, and if the Shattered Star Ring all had one in their hands, they could just directly admit defeat!

However, Han Xiao did not think that this was the reason. He believed that because the aberrations were too ugly, it would be easy to scare off the ladies...

If one was ugly, they would have no rights. What an accurate saying!

Chapter 911: Opening of the Pro League

The Black Star Army Badge: Evolution was a divine tool for completing missions and dungeons. In addition to this item, there were several items within each region that were banned.

"The qualifiers are almost over, and the Pro League opening is close."

Han Xiao rubbed his fingers before reopening the forums, browsing through the information of the qualifiers.

All players were eligible for the qualifiers. After three versions, there were already many players signing for the third Pro League season. They were competing for forty team spots and sixty-four individual tournament places during this regular season, so the competition was fierce.

The saying 'every version has its own generation of Gods' was apt. With the compression technology, the Mechanic class that was originally weaker now started to rise in Version 3.0. Their average record in the team and individual games also improved significantly.

This was especially so for the individual matches. The mechanics that were originally limited in the individuals now shone in the qualifiers. Their rating was re-evaluated as a T1[1] profession.

The combat capability of a mechanic had started to shine. Unfortunately, it was too much of a money burner, and the players finally experienced this happy problem.

Throughout all the competition regions, the most powerful mechanics all came from the Shattered Star Ring, which had become a feature there. The Black Star Army was indeed one of the best camps for Mechanics.

Along with the rise of the Mechanic profession, many dark horses also appeared.

However, this did not include Maple Moon like in Han Xiao's previous life, as she only took part in the Pro League for the first time in Version 3.0 back then. In this life, she had participated in the previous Pro League and had even finished in the thirties, so the effect was different.

Because of her good relationship with Frenzied Sword, Rivervale had offered her an olive branch early on and chosen to sign her up before the Pro League started. Thus, Maple Moon was not considered a free player now but rather part of the professional players.

Regardless of her character attributes, equipment, or skills, Maple Moon was one tier higher than in her previous life, and she firmly gained a seat in the top sixty-four in the individual category, allowing her to qualify for the Pro League.

What was worth mentioning was that the Australian and Russian clubs that were based in Shattered Star Ring tried to send some of their club players to form a team to participate in the qualifiers, to try and eliminate the stronger teams of China.

While this was not considered outsourcing, it still triggered a lot of dissatisfaction among the Chinese players.

Your own professional players remain in their regions to play, but you actually sent over some ruffians to try and make a scene? And you dare claim to be some big club? You're actually just like a kid!

The Australian and Russian teams were targeted heavily by the Chinese players because they were not professional players and ended up being quickly eliminated during the qualifiers.

The candidates for the qualifiers in each region were mostly decided, and the Pro League would be their stage. Thus, a large number of players were analyzing the performance of these players in the qualifiers and posting their analysis videos.

Han Xiao was also deeply engrossed in this as he had received similar treatment.

After scrolling through the forums for a while, a new post suddenly appeared, and it was pushed to the top, attracting Han Xiao's attention.

A glance at it told him that this was the new episode of Galaxy Times, which was the final promotion for the opening of the Pro League.

This was something our Great Mechanic Han had always kept tabs on, so he immediately entered.

"Hello players, this is Galaxy Times, dedicated to sharing first-hand game information. Your gaming career is our top priority," the male host greeted.

"Now that the qualifiers are about to end, the countdown for the Pro League begins," the female host said. "Today, we have the honor of inviting various professional players from the clubs in the Shattered Star Ring for an interview. Please give them a round of applause."

Claps and cheers played in the background.

Everyone came online and faced the camera, introducing themselves.

"Welcome everyone to the Galaxy Times," the female host said. "On behalf of the majority of players, I congratulate you for qualifying in the Pro League. We have a lot of new faces in this version, and many say that this version is one where the dark horses will shine. Let me ask those players first, what do you think?"

The host began to interview a batch of newcomers. All of them were familiar faces to Han Xiao. In his previous life, these newcomers were people who rose up in Version 3.0, and a considerable number later joined as professional players, becoming important players or even the aces in their respective teams. Their future statuses were equivalent to Li Ge and Hao Tian. Looking at all these young people in the group, Han Xiao liked this fresh perspective.

After interviewing the newcomers, it was the turn for the professional players. This interview was the highlight, and the teams interviewed were Long Sky, Dynasty, and Rivervale.

"Hao Tian, King Admiral, and Frenzied Sword, the three captains. You achieved an excellent international ranking in the previous league. Now that the third Pro League is about to open, do you feel any pressure?"

Frenzied Sword nodded. "The pressure is real. The better one's results, the more eyes will be on you. A small mistake will be magnified infinitely, but that's where we have more motivation. We have a potential rookie, Maple Moon, and the team is good, so we are confident of going further in the competition and earning greater glory."

"That's great, and we wish Rivervale all the best. How about Long Sky and Dynasty? As the Champion and the Second Runner-up, what goals do you have, and where do you hope to finish?"

"We only have one goal, to defend the championship," Hao Tian replied. "Anything else is considered regressing."

King Admiral smiled. "Coincidentally, our only goal is obtaining the Championship."

"Seems like both captains are confident, and they wish to win the champion's position for China." The hostess quickly rounded off as the smell of gunpowder grew heavy.

After finishing this episode, Han Xiao glanced down at the players' responses.

[If You Lick to the End, You Get Everything]: "We took three of the eight quarterfinal spots last version. If not for the fact that Dynasty had bad luck and fought twice with our country's people, maybe even the Runner-Up position would have been ours!"

[Twin Lotuses on a Stem]: "What would be called a strong battle team?"

[A Cart of Bread]: "We have a great chance of defending our title. This version, the Mechanic profession rose sharply because of the Black Star Army, and our Mechanic profession is the most powerful! This is our advantage, and our overall ranking will definitely be better."

With optimistic people, there would better be ones that badmouthed them, and however small they were, their existence could not be covered up.

[Rewind]: "Can you stop boasting? They were lucky and got the championship, and now they're all arrogant. Hehe, don't even know if they can get into the quarter finals."

[Father of DuDu: "I really find it revolting that they put these professional players on a pedestal. I don't get what's so good about them."

Scrolling through all the comments, Han Xiao could not help but raise his thumb inwardly.

These people are really good at inciting hatred!

A few days later, the opening ceremony came as scheduled, and the long-awaited moment for the players finally arrived, causing the forums to go wild with excitement.

Before the competition officially started, the number of viewers on the live broadcast channel skyrocketed. Han Xiao, who was at the headquarters, also opened the forums to watch the opening battle.

[1] T1 = Main Tank, T2 = Sub Tank, and so on. The author mentioned this very early on in his series. So, this should be gauging the mechanic as being able to tank a lot now. Back

Chapter 912: Warning

"Welcome to the opening match of the Third Galaxy Pro League. I'm the commentator of this game, Wind Chimes."

"Hello everyone, I'm a guest commentator, Bun-Hit-Dog."

"I'm a guest commentator, Li Ge."

The three of them were being filmed in a studio. This studio was located within a spaceship that hovered above the competition planet, overlooking the scene.

As soon as the live broadcast was connected, there was a barrage of pop-up comments flying across the screen. It was really lively.

Han Xiao took out a bag of nibbles, and reclining in his chair, he ate as he watched in comfort.

"The two teams against each other this time are Long Sky and Dynasty," Wind Chimes said. "They were the Champions and Second Runners-up in the previous Pro League. They last met in the semifinals, where Long Sky defeated Dynasty and made them miss the final, so there will definitely be some grudges. Their fans have been giving off the smell of gunpowder before this match. One side are the champions, who have to secure the first win, while Dynasty wish to wipe away their previous humiliation, so this match will be one of epic proportions. What say you two?"

"I feel that Long Sky might win," Bun-Hit-Dog said. "Hao Tian is a typical example of a competitor who grows stronger the stronger his opponents are. I'm very optimistic about him."

"There was some luck factored in during Long Sky's last win," Li Ge countered. "I'm more optimistic about Dynasty, as they will definitely have done more research after losing the previous time."

The three commentators debated for a few minutes before Long Sky and Dynasty finally entered the battlefield, waving to the audience and doing the self introduction before the match.

The hero who won the previous glory for China appeared, and it incited a large wave of pop ups, so much that Han Xiao could barely see the screen.

"Okay, we can see that both sides have already gotten on the battlefield. If that's the case, then the Pro League officially... begins!"

The moment the voice sounded, both sides moved, akin to a lightning strike or a volcanic eruption. Compared to the previous version, the tactical methods and destructive power of these professional players had obviously risen to a whole new level, so the battlefield range had also become larger.

Long Sky had a sharp penetrative force, but Dynasty was more balanced overall. Their teamwork was nigh perfect, and they were skillful in team battles as well as capturing the flag. However, in terms of individual strength, Long Sky—which had Hao Tian, Sleepy Winter, and Twinkle Fried Rice, three god-level players—slightly overwhelmed Dynasty. While King Admiral slightly exceeded all his opponents, it was difficult for him to support the entire team.

In this Pro League, the new formats for team battles and dungeon survival games also made their debut. Han Xiao was no stranger to this, but players found it new since it was their first time.

The selected dungeon was not fixed, and it was different each game. Before the game, several dungeon options would be taken out to allow players the time to study before one of these options was randomly selected. However, professional players were on a different level. When this rule was announced a year ago, the teams had already begun to do dungeon training and were familiar with most of the dungeons in this region.

The team battle would be held in a normal level dungeon, while the survival battle would be held in a high-level dungeon. Coincidentally, the dungeons that Long Sky and Dynasty chose all had to do with Han Xiao.

The team battle was held in the secret war dungeon series, and both parties would be thrown into the same dungeon. The goal was not a time attack but rather to complete some special mission tasks, such as assassinating certain characters or drawing out hidden missions, testing the comprehensive quality in each team.

As for the survival battle, it was a copy of [Warfare: Defense of Planet Aquamarine], where the Calamity Grades of DarkStar ganged up against Han Xiao. Even though it was in Version 2.0, this dungeon copy was still a difficult one for the players.

The focus of the dungeon battles was to test the wit and bravery of the teams. Utilizing everything within the dungeon to defeat their opponents would make the Pro League more interesting than just a basic battle. As for the survival battle, it was more of who could struggle longer to survive. Watching the professional players get abused was quite entertaining for the audience as well.

Long Sky's battle style was more reckless, as Hao Tian's specialty did not lie in strategy and was not suitable for the intricacies of team dungeon battles. While Sleepy Winter was accustomed to pretending to be a pig to eat the tiger, he was unable to shake the stability of Dynasty and was completely led around their nose by King Admiral, hammered flat.

When it came to the survival dungeon, the dungeon copy replayed the battlefield at that time, where the two teams came face to face with the three Calamity Grade DarkStar supers. The threat level was basically dying once they encountered them. Luckily, the copy of Black Star was also projected according to the original history.

Long Sky and Dynasty both materialized outside of the Sanctuary, with protective shields, and had to withstand the aftermath of the three Calamity Grades as well as the bombing of the mothership. The survival game allowed them to fight each other as well, but neither side had the luxury, only scurrying around with their heads tucked low. This was the complete opposite of the image of arrogance the professional players typically showed, which delighted the viewers to no end. The live broadcast was full of lively cheers and comments.

Both teams died in quick succession, and it was Long Sky that died first. They were not that good at dodging and were turned to ash by Ember.

The first victory of the opening game was thus won by Dynasty, which directly destroyed the chance for Championship for Long Sky. Han Xiao had to admit that King Admiral was a really good representative of the Chinese professional players, and he had once admired him. This guy was a true god-level player.

Leaving the live broadcast, he could see many more posts on the forums about the battle previously. The fans of both clubs were busy badmouthing each other, and Han Xiao only swept past them before closing the forums. As he put his snacks away, his mind started to reminisce.

In his past life, China was faced with a devilishly tight schedule, and their final result was dismal, not even squeezing into the semi-finals. There was no Black Star Army in his past life, so the strength of Shattered Star Ring was pretty weak.

The situation is different now. China has won the championship once, and with the increase in power for the Mechanic profession, the odds of defending it are not small at all.

Ring ring!

At this point, the communicator on his table rang. With a hook of his finger, he dragged the communicator over. The caller was from the Crimson Dynasty, and it was someone responsible for the Evolutionary Totem project.

"Your Excellency Black Star, I'm sorry to intrude." The other party's attitude was respectful.

"Any problems with regards to the business?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Yes, as you know, some bandits recently snatched the Evolutionary Totems that were purchased by our allies. Some of these stolen Evolutionary Totems are now in circulation within the black market, and some were taken away by their secret employers. According to our sources, we think that the Blood Gold Organization is one of the suspects involved."

Blood Gold Organization...

Han Xiao remembered the past details. This was a member of the Lawful Evil faction. They were in charge of the galactic black market along with other gray organizations. They were also a black market mercenary group that players could enter, usually for those players who liked to cause trouble.

"The Blood Gold Organization is unlike the Fallen Ark. They have a set of rules to follow. As long as we warn them in the name of the Dynasty, they should know how to behave." Han Xiao stroked his chin.

"That's where the problem exists." The tone of the officer dropped. "Based on our intelligence, our spies have discovered that there are radiation signals of the Evolutionary Totem on some planets of the Federation of Light and Arcane Church. They may also be buyers, and if that's the case, the Blood Gold Organization will have their support."

"Well... I suppose that's still within my expectations."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. The Federation of Light and Arcane Church could not get the Evolutionary Totem through conventional channels, so they searched for alternatives.

The Blood Gold Organization was also a large organization, with a wide scope of business, and they would definitely have their own agenda. But if the Federation of Light and Arcane Church approached them, even at the cost of them offending the Crimson Dynasty, they would still be willing to be chess pieces as it would allow them to get close to the other two Universal Civilizations.

Within the currently explored universe, the three Universal Civilizations were the biggest backers, so it was not surprising that the Blood Gold Organization was tempted by the olive branch thrown to it.

"So, you want to bring the knife to the Blood Gold Organization?" Han Xiao asked.

"That's right. We hope to give them a good warning and need your help to collect some intelligence."

"Got it." Han Xiao nodded.

They exchanged the respective intelligence and ended the call.

At the same time, a new mission popped up on his interface.

[Warning]

Mission Introduction: The erratic movements of the Blood Gold Organization have impacted the dynasty's important businesses, and the dynasty has decided to send them a warning, to kill the chicken in order to warn the monkeys.

Mission Requirements: Provide the dynasty with 3 high ranked members from the Blood Gold Organization.

Reward: 15,000,000 experience, +1,000 Dynasty Contribution Point, x1 Random Reward

Track the upper echelons of the Blood Gold Organization? It seems like the dynasty want to strike from the top. No wonder they asked for help. This is the expertise of a Virtual Mechanic.

Stowing his communicator, Han Xiao thought for a while before calling Sylvia.

"Sylvia, is there any news from the Rock Sprite Tribe?"

"They have decided to buy a new batch of Evolutionary Totems."

Han Xiao rapped on the table. "Tell them, in order to prevent similar incidents, I've decided to send some of my mechanical army to follow their fleet, providing a free escort service."

"Understood, I'll relay the message."

Han Xiao nodded and hung up before connecting to the quantum network and calling Phillip.

"In a while, hack into a black market account with a high credibility point, and anonymously hire the Blood Gold Organization to rob this batch of goods."

Against such mercenary forces, the simplest method would be to drop some bait.

...

Over the next few days, while Han Xiao was waiting for the fish to bite, he was watching the Regular Season battles that were in full swing.

After a round robin battle, the Regular Season finally decided the participants for quarter finals as well as the top sixteen individuals, and entered the finals.

Dynasty ranked first in the team battles for points, while King Admiral was the first in terms of individual points. Dynasty had obtained a double first and demonstrated their powerful strength, obtaining the qualification to enter the International League.

Temple of God and Thunder Storm ranked second and third, while Long Sky was placed fourth. This result was a little unbefitting of the former champion, and they were somewhat sluggish.

Following that were Fried Eggplants With Fish and Rivervale, ranked fifth and sixth respectively. The seventh was a new club, which explosively entered the scene, named Long River, while ranked at eighth was Sky Palace.

These were the top eight teams, and they would play in the division finals in best of five games.

Only the top four teams would be able to qualify for the International League.

For the individual battles, Maple Moon reached the top sixteen this time, obtaining the qualifications to compete in the International League, along with Frenzied Sword.

After the Regular Season, a buffer period was given.

During this time, the Blood Gold Organization finally bit on the bait that Han Xiao had cast.

Chapter 913: Entrapment

Near the borders of the Sea of Star Spirits, a fleet of over forty battleships was currently cruising. The battleships all had the logo of the Rock Sprite Civilization.

These spaceships were the long-distance spaceships created by the Rock Sprite Civilization. Their exterior looked a bit like a bloated mining spaceship with the main weapons of the spaceship being a lightweight Ion Cannon and a Particle Cannon.

A Star System Civilization would only be able to move around the Star System if they relied on their own technology, and even if they had a stargate from a higher civilization, a Star System Civilization needed to construct a special spaceship in order to conduct inter-Star Field travel. Resources and energy would be a huge barrier between the short-distance and long-distance travel spaceships.

To a Star System Civilization, long-distance spaceships were extremely precious, and the difficulty of constructing one was far more than that of a short-distance spaceship.

In order to transport the Evolutionary Totems from the Black Star Army in the neighboring Star Field, the Rock Sprite race sent out a long-distance fleet. Their previous fleet was ambushed by the Blood Gold Organization and was completely wiped out. This fleet was their second batch of spaceships, which had travelled in hyperdrive for a period by borrowing a stargate before reaching the Black Star Army base. After a long trip, this fleet had finally returned to the Sea of Star Spirits.

In the command room of the flagship, a Rock Sprite commander instructed with a solemn expression, "Everyone, remain on high alert. Our previous long-distance fleet was ambushed around the border of the Sea of Star Spirits. We have already received news of the enemy's operating region. Report any anomalies on the radar to me."

"Understood," the crew in the command room replied anxiously.

The civilizations of the Star Cluster grade and above were used to long-distance voyages, but to the fleet of a Star System grade civilization, every trip out of their own region represented unknown danger. After leaving their borders, they no longer had the protection of their civilization's fleet, and it was akin to entering the deep ocean.

The enforcement squad would not descend from the sky, and various galactic organizations were active within this region. They would never know how many eyes were looking at them.

"There are still another eighteen days until our next stargate, and we will be able to jump past three Star Systems to leave this border region. The border is the most dangerous, and as long as we do not meet any enemies during this region, we should be safe," the commander said.

However, right as he completed his sentence, an ear-piercing alarm rang.

Spaceship signals appeared all round them, and they entered an encirclement that the enemy had prepared.

"Again‽ Who leaked our whereabouts‽"

The commander gritted his teeth and cursed in his heart.

If not for His Excellency's Black Star help, we'd definitely suffer a huge loss this time.

...

The attackers had more than three hundred spaceships and were rapidly surrounding them. They immediately activated their equipment to jam hyperdrive and prevent their prey from escaping.

In the flagship of the attackers, a large crystal bodied organism was floating in front of the command room's window. His exterior appearance was a crystal with many edges, and he did not have any limbs or sensory organs. He only had two blue tentacles formed by Psychic energy that were wiggling around.

This crystal lifeform was the leader of the assault fleet and was named Kelansta. He was a Calamity Grade Psychic and an experienced mercenary of the Blood Gold Organization. He was once the traitor of a crystal lifeform civilization because he absorbed a large amount of his race's own mental energy to become a Calamity Grade Super. As such, a bounty was placed on him, and he joined the Blood Gold Organization many years ago.

The encirclement was rapidly formed, and Kelansta made use of his Psychic energy to form soundwaves to say, "Release the magnetized radioactive waves to weaken the enemy's defensive shields. The vanguard force shall approach the enemy and enter close-quarters combat. Do not bombard them from long range lest we damage the goods. Our objective is to snatch the Evolutionary Totems."

The Blood Gold Organization had been eyeing the Evolutionary Totems in the black market. Not too long ago, an account with a high credibility rating issued a mission to snatch the Evolutionary Totems and revealed the whereabouts of this Rock Sprite fleet. The Blood Gold Organization then accepted the mission immediately.

They were not interested in the reward of the mission; their main aim was the Evolutionary Totems. Handing an Evolutionary Totem over to the civilizations that needed them would give them even more money, and they would even be able to gain the support of a backer. Han Xiao made use of the Evolutionary Totems to gain huge political support, and the Blood Gold Organization and other organizations snatching the Evolutionary Totems wanted to share this influence.

It would not matter if they were unable to complete the mission; snatching the totems was their main goal. However, the Blood Gold Organization was not planning to swallow the entire batch of totems for themselves. They only needed to give a portion of the totems to their employer and claim that the rest were destroyed in battle. The remaining totems would then go into their pockets. This was a standard practice of theirs.

Because of the robberies over the past few months, the civilizations purchasing the totem made sure to keep the matter a secret. As such, it was extremely rare to come across such information on the black market. There were few transportation fleets that had their location discovered, and this employment mission had revealed the whereabouts of the Rock Sprite fleet.

Because the Blood Gold Organization had previously robbed the Rock Sprite fleet, they had a certain degree of trust toward this information. They had also gotten a large intelligence organization in the black market to verify the information before taking action.

The fleet of the Blood Gold Organization was many times larger than the Rock Sprite fleet, and they were like wolves surrounding a herd of sheep.

The next moment, a radioactive pulse was released from the Blood Gold Organization fleet, and the defensive shields of the Rock Sprite fleet began to flicker.

Such a radioactive pulse was generated by a powerful electromagnetic field. It was capable of disrupting electromagnetic and ion shields. However, it was useless against psionic and dark energy shields. However, most Star System civilizations would mainly use electromagnetic and ion shields.

The distance between both parties rapidly shrank, and the Blood Gold Organization made use of their electromagnetic chains to latch onto the Rock Sprite spaceships.

The image of the spaceships being latched on was displayed in the command room.

"Report, I have boarded the spaceship, and everything feels good. I am heading toward the control room of the spaceship, taking out any resistance along the way."

"Very good," Kelansta replied slowly. "Speed up, I..."

Before he could even finish what he had to say, the screens in the command room all shut down, and everyone was stunned.

The next moment, the sound of intense battle could be heard from the communicators, followed by the sound of miserable groans.

"Enemy attack! There are other troops on the spaceships!"

"My armor isn't listening to my commands!"

The sound of the battles lasted for a short while, and the communicator fell silent. The vanguard force was completely wiped out.

Everyone in the command room had a look of loss, and they looked toward Kelansta, waiting for his orders.

Kelansta was also in shock, and just when he was about to say something, a buzzing white noise could be heard from the screen on the command room.

Buzz!

The next moment, a human silhouette formed by white noise appeared on the screen and let out a mechanical voice.

"Following the orders of my Lord, I am taking over this region."

"Who... are you?"

"Formless Ghost."

After which, everyone in the room detected an anomaly. Something seemed to be flowing under the alloy walls around them as though snakes were slithering around their command room.

The members in the room immediately got away from the walls and stared at the walls with fear in their eyes.

"Just what is going... Argh!"

Before they could finish their sentence, the metal floor beneath them suddenly changed shape, and a cactus-like iron tree grew in the middle of the room with many bodies hanging down from the branches!

Boom!

Kelansta released his powerful Psychic force and smashed the iron tree apart.

The shattered alloy then collapsed onto the ground and was absorbed back into the ground like it was liquid. Following which, the command room changed shape, and the alloy walls seemed to have transformed into flesh, contracting inward. The entire room came alive.

Kelansta immediately used his Psychic force to destroy the windows and entered space. Only then could he see what was going on.

The entire spaceship seemed to have been transformed into nanoparticles, and the alloy was being molded like clay. The few spaceships in the surroundings also had the same phenomenon.

Kelansta was shocked.

Formless Ghost was one of the Apostle Weapons. He had an infective nanoparticle virus that could live in any alloy or machinery to control it. At the same time, he was capable of transforming alloy into nanoparticles and becoming one with them to increase his body mass.

At the same time in the Rock Sprite fleet, a black tide of mechanical soldiers rushed out. These mechanical soldiers easily destroyed the many spaceships of the Blood Gold Organization.

Upon seeing the Black Star Army insignia on the mechanical soldiers, Kelansta immediately understood what was going on and fell into despair.

"Black Star‽"

After realizing who his enemy was, Kelansta lost all motivation to fight back.

Formless Ghost led a long-distance fleet to escort the Rock Sprite fleet. With Han Xiao's current strength, he would be able to easily wipe out the few hundred Blood Gold Organization battleships without even using Lord's Descent.

The battle had no suspense, and all the enemies became his captives.

Kelansta also had nowhere to escape. Even if he was in the Calamity Grade, he was powerless against the mechanical army. He was captured, and his mental energy constrained.

Without his Psychic energy, he would even need help if he wanted to get up.

After the battle, Han Xiao's consciousness descended upon a complete Blood Gold Organization spaceship through the quantum network, and he shook his head with a chuckle.

"These fellows indeed took the bait."

"Lord, I completed your orders."

The ground of the command room then transformed into a human figure, and the human figure knelt on the ground. This was Formless Ghost. His main body was made of nanoparticles, and he could exist in many different forms.

"It's been tough for you." Han Xiao praised him. "I shall take care of the rest."

In the blink of an eye, Han Xiao's consciousness went through the quantum network of the spaceship and infiltrated the Blood Gold Organization's database. In the quantum network, physical distance lost all meaning.

In the eyes of a Beyond Grade A Mechanic, the firewall of the Blood Gold Organization was filled with loopholes everywhere.

...

Not too long later, Han Xiao opened his eyes in the Black Star Army headquarters, and he smiled.

"Found it."

"Lord, what should we do with the captives?" Formless Ghost asked.

"They aren't anything good. Execute them all. Oh, apart from that crystal lifeform. Bring him back to me. I want to see if I can squeeze any juice... er, crystal powder from him," Han Xiao replied casually and exited the quantum network. He then picked out the whereabouts of three Blood Gold Organization upper echelons and sent the data to the Crimson Dynasty official in charge of the totems.

The members of the Blood Gold Organization were extremely mysterious with their whereabouts unknown. But as long as Han Xiao set his sights on them, it would be incredibly difficult for them to escape.

If this mission was assigned to the players, it would be extremely challenging for them, and they would have to find clues from all around. However, it was an easy matter to him; he only needed a single clue to dig up all the intelligence.

After handing over the intelligence, a notification popped up on his interface.

[Warning] has been completed.

You have received 15,000,000 experience, 1,000 Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points, x1 Random Reward.

Not too long later, the dynasty replied to him.

"Thanks for your intelligence, Your Excellency Black Star."

"It's a small matter. How are you planning to deal with the three of them?"

"Haha, Your Excellency, you're asking the obvious."

"That's true. Using such a method to find them isn't an overboard method." Han Xiao then added, "How about this? Let me take care of one of them."

"Since you are interested, the dynasty has no issues with that."

"Alright then."

He then hung up, and Han Xiao sent the intelligence to Lothaire.

Lothaire had joined the army one and a half years ago, but he did not have much to do most of the time. After all, the army did not really have any assassination missions for him to do, so this was a chance for him.

Han Xiao was planning to let Lothaire go out and exercise a bit so that his assassination skills would not turn rusty.

Furthermore, after a year of observation, he felt that Lothaire was now sufficiently trustworthy to set up an assassin organization on the outside. This plan of his could be brought forward.

"I will set off immediately," Lothaire replied promptly.

He was not concerned about the reason behind the assassination. After a year and half of interaction, he already trusted Han Xiao and had a good impression of the army.

Chapter 914: Top Eight

Just as Han Xiao got Lothaire to assassinate a target, the Division Finals continued as usual.

After a series of battles, the top eight teams in the Shattered Star Ring had already been formed. Dynasty obtained their third championship and created their three-time championship era. Among the four great guilds, Dynasty had always been ranked first and did not have any obvious shortcomings.

The first runner up was Temple of God, and although the fans of Temple of God were considered satisfied, passersby could not help but lament with pity. The impression of Temple of God being a weakling during external battles was imprinted deep within their hearts, and sending Temple of God into the International League meant that China had one less team!

The second runner up was Long Sky. Although their performance was not good in the division matches, they entered into the International League and had the opportunity to show the world what they could do. The third runner up was Rivervale. Frenzied Sword, Evil Sword, and Maple Moon were the core of the team, and their strength was no less than the first three teams.

These four teams would be participating in the International League.

Of the four great guilds, Fried Eggplants with Fish had once again missed the chance to participate in the International League.

It was said that the boss of Fried Eggplants with Fish felt that the name of their team was not auspicious enough and wanted to change the team's name. They were currently seeking opinion from the public, and the names suggested were all like dishes on a menu.

Without mentioning the fans of Fried Eggplants with Fish who were entertaining themselves in their bitterness, the majority of the players were rooting for the four teams that had made it into the International League. They had a huge advantage in this version. The Mechanic class had risen to prominence, and many large events in the Shattered Star Ring increased the benefits of the Black Star Army greatly. Thus, the Chinese players were extremely confident about emerging as champions. The god-level players in the clubs were all in their peak state, and all the players thus placed huge expectations on the Chinese teams. They looked forward to them displaying their brilliance in the International League.

In the Singles, Maple Moon got into the top eight. In this season, four of the top eight belonged to the Mechanic class, and the Mechanics finally made up for their weaknesses in the first two versions.

The rankings for the eight other regions had also been released. Most of the teams were the usual teams that made it to the International League such as Devil, Key, and Thunderbolt Python from America; Tulips and Grapes from France; Rose Knight from Britain; Hydra and Vagrant from Japan; Kimchi and Samsung Bomb from Korea; Tomahawk from Sweden; Wings from Poland; White Emperor Sword from Russia; and Kangaroo Boxing from Australia. Many of these teams were the familiar faces from the previous International League. There was a total of thirty-six teams in the International League, and they were split into three divisions.

The division lineup truly excited the Chinese players this time. The strongest batch of overseas teams were all drawn into Division A, and only Temple of God was drawn into that division. Because the Regular Season relied on point accumulation, it would be difficult to pull apart the gap in points with too many strong teams in the division. As such, many of the strong overseas teams would not be able to arrive at the finals.

Long Sky and Dynasty got into Division B with only a few stronger teams such as Hydra, Rose Knight and Tomahawk. The two Chinese teams were hot favorites to win the championship, and it was highly likely for both teams to advance together.

Rivervale got into Division C, which was the weakest division of the three.

The random assignment of the teams was completely the opposite from the previous season. However, it was far more advantageous to the Chinese teams, and it was very likely for the scene of three teams in the top eight to happen again.

The Chinese players were overjoyed and almost set off firecrackers in the Shattered Star Ring to celebrate!

As for the unlucky Temple of God, the Chinese players were not bothered and even laughed at them.

You from Henan: "Sacrificing Temple of God to obtain three slots in the top eight. This deal is truly sweet!"

Li Ge's Life Is Filled with Darkness: "Sacrificing the noobest team to increase the average strength of China."

Praying Under the Moon: "Is this Tianji horse racing?"

Senior War Official: "Haha, what a divine grouping."

Amid the cheerful atmosphere, the short break after the Division Finals ended, and the International League began.

There were millions of players watching the competition from the forums and discussing the competition excitedly.

The opening battle of the International League was the faceoff between the champion and first runner up from the previous season: Long Sky vs Devil. Long Sky's fans and the other viewers were all worried about this battle. Long Sky's performance during the division competition was not satisfactory, and it was highly likely for them to lose this battle if they faced the previous first runner up. While it was not much to lose a single battle, it would dampen the team's morale.

Both parties used Dungeon Crystals to enter the battlefield. The Long Sky team was equipped with armor that had the Black Star Army insignia. The various armor types all had their own purposes, and this was akin to free advertisement.

Although the equipment of Devil was also extremely powerful, they did not look as uniform as Long Sky. In comparison, Long Sky felt a lot more like a proper army.

Black Star Army's fame was no longer limited to the Shattered Star Ring, and the other countries all knew that the Black Star Army was the largest player faction in the Shattered Star Ring. The Black Star Army had a complete monopoly and was the first faction that provided the players an opportunity to cross Star Fields. In the hearts of the various players, the Shattered Star Ring was akin to the Black Star Army's territory.

Usually, only a Universal Civilization or Super Star Cluster Civilization would have the privilege of being recognized as the ruler of a Star Field. Although the strength of the Black Star Army was far from being compared to these two factions, their fame among the players was no less than a Universal Civilization.

The curtains to the International League were drawn, and Long Sky revealed their fangs to fight an intense battle with Devil.

In this respect, Long Sky was the exact opposite from Temple of God. They were so-so in internal battles but extremely ferocious in external battles.

Long Sky beat Devil by a small margin during the previous season, but this time, because of the improvements to the Mechanic class and some players from Devil changing clubs, the difference between the two parties widened, and Long Sky seized their first victory in the International League.

The Chinese players all cheered with excitement.

The Regular Season of the International League then unfolded with many intense battles every day.

The rankings had only stabilized after they fought the first half of the season. Because of the many strong teams in Division A, it was extremely difficult for the players of that division to gain an overwhelming victory, and their points were not too high. As such, the rankings did not display the proper strength of the teams. For example, teams like Devil, Tulips, Key, and White Emperor Sword did not manage to make it into the top four.

Dynasty and Long Sky had an easy time in Division B and managed to obtain first and fourth place. Rivervale harvested a great amount of points in Division C and managed to take second. Among the top four, only third place was Korea's Kimchi, which was also a member of Division C.

To the Chinese players, the situation was extremely good, and Temple of God, which was being abused, was completely ignored.

The huge advantage of the Chinese teams was not only because of the groupings but also because Capture the Flag and two dungeon modes were added into the competition. These modes were far more suitable for a Mechanic to show off their skill, which gave Long Sky, Dynasty, and Rivervale a huge advantage. Their PvE strength was much higher than the other international teams, which allowed their scores to be pulled forward.

There was another reason... The dungeons chosen in the Regular Season would not be the dungeons from the respective regions of the participating teams to ensure that the teams did not have any disparity of information. As such, the Chinese teams would not experience the Black Star Army's perverse dungeons.

As for their friends from overseas, they could personally enjoy the usual life of the players in the Shattered Star Ring.

The difficulty of the dungeons issued by Han Xiao was not on the same level as the highest level dungeons in the other regions. Shattered Star Ring was the only region that had a Beyond Grade A dungeon!

Under Han Xiao's abuse, the Chinese players were used to being abused and could face the high-level dungeons of the other regions with ease. It was just like taking a vacation to them.

On the contrary, the teams from the other regions were abused to the point they wanted to puke when fighting the Black Star Army dungeons.

Being killed on the spot was commonplace, and their time spent in the dungeon would usually be the time of the intro clip.

Was this a dungeon for players to complete?

Was there a need to make the difficulty level so perverse‽

As long as the Black Star Army dungeon was picked, the fans from the other teams would cry out with agony. The team would die too quickly, and there was nothing to watch at all.

During the second half of the Regular Season, perhaps because of the large disparity in points, all the teams had given up, and the Chinese teams were not targeted by the other teams like in the previous season.

Long Sky, Dynasty, and Rivervale stabilized their position in the top eight, and it was impossible for them to drop out of the top eight.

After the end of the final match, the rankings were finalized.

Rivervale obtained first place with the other members being, Kimchi, Dynasty, Hydra, Long Sky, Devil, Key, and Tomahawk.

China had three teams entering the top eight again and maintained their glory from the previous season. Furthermore, it was the same three teams that had made it into the previous top eight.

Dynasty and Long Sky were well established clubs, so there was no need to mention them. Rivervale was a newly formed club that managed to get into the top eight two times in a row. Their status among the players had been cemented, and there was a chance for them to become a new super guild.

Temple of God had no fate with the finals, but no one felt any pity for them. Everyone's attention was only on the winner.

This time, the matchups in the finals were much better than the previous season!

During the second season, because of the lousy matchup, the Chinese teams needed to fight each other twice. Dynasty and Rivervale were both eliminated by a Chinese team.

According to the current scores, the first place Rivervale would be facing Tomahawk, the third place Dynasty would be facing Devil, and the fifth place Long Sky would be facing Hydra.

This matchup made all the players cheer with joy. Compared to their bad luck in the previous season, they were truly blessed by the goddess of luck this time!

...

After the Regular Season of the International League was completed, the dates for the International Finals were fixed.

Lothaire was sent by Han Xiao to the other Star Fields, and after the end of the Regular Season, Han Xiao received Lothaire's message.

"Objective cleared."

The message included a picture of the victim, and it was taken care of cleanly.

He only provided the intelligence, and Lothaire could work on his own without any help.

The Crimson Dynasty had also gotten rid of the other two Blood Gold Organization upper echelons.

With three upper echelons dead, all the upper echelons of the Blood Gold Organization were in shock.

The Blood Gold Organization could no longer sit still after being targeted by the Crimson Dynasty and Black Star Army.

Chapter 915: Surging Currents

In some secret conference room of the Blood Gold Organization, over ten upper echelons were meeting through long-distance projections. They were made up of organisms from many different races.

All those present in this room were not ordinary characters and were infamous in their respective regions. Most of them had high bounties placed on them by the various civilizations, and their combat capabilities were not weak in the Calamity Grade. They were now the leaders of the Blood Gold Organization and had various troops under their command. They rarely took action personally and were in a semi-retired status.

"I believe that everyone understands our recent situation. The Crimson Dynasty and Black Star Army have taken action against us. Marlowe, Vancesna, and Indir have been assassinated," the leader of the Blood Gold Organization said with a grave tone.

The current leader of Blood Gold was a male organism and a member of the Federation of Light. He was an elite being that went through genetic testing before. His appearance was extremely ferocious, and he was currently at the peak of his life.

As compared to the others present, his background was extremely clean, and he was not a wanted man. He was an elite brought up by the previous leader of the Blood Gold Organization. When the previous leader died, he took over the position as leader, and it had been thirty years since then.

The Blood Gold Organization was a pretty old organization, and he was the twelfth leader.

The existence of the galactic black market was even older than some Star System or even Star Cluster Civilizations. The managers had been changed over and over again, and the Blood Gold Organization had only taken up the role of manager of the black market two hundred years ago.

"Poor Marlowe, I still owe him 7,203,050 Enas. He is truly a good man and died at the best time." A squid like upper echelon rubbed his eyes to squeeze out some tears.

"This isn't the time to joke. The Crimson Dynasty is obviously trying to scare us by killing the upper echelons of our organization and punish us for stealing the goods of their allies. They want us to retreat and not think about the Evolutionary Totems anymore. The problem is, how did news about the upper echelons leak?" a member of the Andor Bee Race said.

The leader of Blood Gold then said, "Kelansta's fleet met Black Star's mechanical army a while back, and Black Star should have taken action personally to locate the upper echelons. It is usually us scaring others, but this time, some powers higher up have their eyes set on us. The Crimson Dynasty and Black Star Army aren't easily provoked, and we have to consider how we should deal with them."

"Humph, the Black Star Army is far away in the Shattered Star Ring, and the threat that they pose is limited. Furthermore, the Black Star Army is only a little bit more prominent in the Shattered Star Ring and does not have any forces in the other Star Fields. Their scale cannot be compared to ours; only Black Star is difficult to deal with. For now, we do not need to bother about them. The dynasty should be our main focus," a pirate-like man with a large beard said.

"I agree." The Blood Gold leader nodded.

Their Blood Gold Organization had operations across three Star Fields, and their scale was even larger than the Black Star Army. In their eyes, the Black Star Army was nothing to be afraid of; they only needed to be afraid of Black Star alone. It was the strict attitude of the Crimson Dynasty that truly worried them.

"The federation and church were the ones who approached us. If we continue to snatch the Evolutionary Totems, the Crimson Dynasty will definitely fight back. But if we stop, the federation and church will abandon us," the Blood Gold leader said slowly.

"I was against interfering in the Evolutionary Totems back then. We are no more than a chess piece in the battle between the three Universal Civilizations. Our fate was no longer in our hands the moment we joined. We should've just operated in a low profile manner," one of the upper echelons grumbled.

"Humph, the federation and church came to find us. Do you think they'd give us the chance to reject them? We still have some hope of advancing if we hug their thighs, but we would've lost everything if we rejected them," the Blood Gold leader said coldly. "Manager of the black market? You don't even need to think about it. We'd slowly become an insignificant black market mercenary group waiting to be wiped out. From the moment they came to find us, it was impossible for us to steer clear of the matter."

The galactic black market had plenty of benefits, and every manager was a tyrant in the various gray operations. Among the managers of the black market, the one with the largest authority was the one in the broker business. They used many different means to persuade different civilizations to provide protection to the other managers.

If the Blood Gold Organization dared incur the ire of the federation and church, the aftermath of the matter would not affect them alone. If the other managers of the black market ended up being affected, they would kick the Blood Gold Organization out of the black market and not provide them with protection or support.

Since the other party had chosen them, a gray organization unprotected by the galactic laws need not dream about maintaining neutrality!

The world was not that convenient!

"The Universal Civilizations are as tyrannical as always. This is the tragedy of a gray organization not protected by galactic law."

"Then what should we do? The federation and church won't just watch as we are all assassinated, right?"

Right at this moment, another two projections appeared in the room wearing the federation and church's uniform.

"I have already spoken to the federation and church about this matter." The Blood Gold leader stood up and said, "Let me give you an introduction. These two are the emissaries of the federation and church. He..."

Before he could finish, the Federation of Light emissary waved his arms and said, "Don't need to bother introducing us. Let's get straight to the point. The Federation of Light already knows about the price that you have paid and expresses our sympathy. As such, we will be providing protection to the upper echelons of the Blood Gold Organization. We will secretly bring all of you to the Abyss of Stars and Silver Arm. The Crimson Dynasty and Black Star Army won't be able to touch you in our territory. All of you can continue controlling the organization remotely and gather more Evolutionary Totems. We will provide you guys with resources as well."

The Ten Thousand Deity Scepter was a wedge between the federation and church. However, it did not stop them from working together for the Evolutionary Totems. After all, the Evolutionary Totems involved the improvement of their entire civilizations' genes. It had a huge strategic significance. In front of benefits, there was no such thing as an enemy forever. However, both parties definitely did not get along very well.

Upon hearing that, the upper echelons of the Blood Gold Organization all heaved a sigh of relief. They would only be able to become a chess piece at ease if their own safety was protected.

Right at this moment, the upper echelon from the Andor Bee Race said, "Pardon me for being straightforward, but I have a question. Robbing the Evolutionary Totems that the other civilizations purchase is an extremely inefficient method. If we rob too many civilizations, the same situation will probably happen, and Black Star won't allow us to keep robbing his customers.

The Federation of Light emissary smiled and nodded. "You are right. This isn't a long-term solution. Just robbing alone won't be enough to satisfy our needs. What are your plans?"

"After EsGod was caught, the method of making the Evolutionary Totem was discovered. The most effective way to solve this problem would be to snatch the Evolution Cube from Black Star!" a member of the Blood Gold Organization upper echelons said with a cold glint in his eyes.

"You are right, but this method will not work for now," the Arcane Church emissary said coldly. "With the presence of the Evolutionary Totem, the strategic importance of the Evolution Cube is much higher than before. If we snatch away the Evolution Cube, there won't be any room for negotiation like the battle on Planet Lighthouse, and the moment we succeed, it will mean war. Until the last moment, our three civilizations won't start a war and let others benefit from the side.

"Furthermore, do you think that it is that easy to deal with Black Star? It's easy for you to say! If not for us knowing about the existence of the Evolutionary Totem, do you think we would have risked offending the dynasty and starting the battle on Planet Lighthouse? We have tried before, and there are still a few Beyond Grade As sealed up in Spacetime Amber. Do you want to go give it a try‽"

"No no no." That upper echelon was completely speechless and coughed awkwardly.

What a joke. Black Star is a true powerhouse in the galaxy, and an ordinary Calamity Grade like me isn't even in the same league as him.

The Federation of Light emissary nodded and said, "He's right. We do not intend to risk stealing the Evolution Cube at this moment. That will be our final choice. There is still another approach for us to take at the moment. That is to get the dynasty to allow Black Star to openly sell the totems."

"Is this really possible?" the Blood Gold leader asked doubtfully.

"Humph, the current situation is like this. Black Star likely doesn't mind selling the Evolutionary Totems publicly, but because he belongs to the Crimson Dynasty faction, he cannot risk offending his ally and sells the totems privately. Thus, we should not be setting our sights on Black Star but the Crimson Dynasty.

"As long as the Crimson Dynasty gives in, we will have the chance to obtain a large number of totems.

"There are a few ways for us to force the Crimson Dynasty to give in. Suppress them with force, exchange benefits, work together to pressure them... You should also know about the dynasty's style. It would be a pipe dream to suppress them with force, and we will definitely suffer a huge loss if we want to exchange benefits with them. The dynasty will not agree unless we give them our core technological skills and resources.

"As such, we can only choose to work together to pressure them from the economical, trade, political, and security side. Your Blood Gold Organization will be a part of this plan.

"The Crimson Dynasty has invested a large amount of resources to develop the Flickering World, and they will be weakened in other areas. This is our best chance to pressure them, and we will be able to force the dynasty to compromise!"

One of the upper echelons then trembled. "Is it really okay to tell us such a secret...?"

"Ah, there is nothing secretive about this matter. The dynasty knew that this would happen the day they decided not to sell the Evolutionary Totems openly. Furthermore, you are working together with us, and there is no harm informing you about our plans," the Federation of Light emissary said casually.

The Blood Gold leader then frowned. "What if the plan doesn't work?"

The Federation of Light emissary then sneered coldly.

"If the dynasty refuses to give in, we will have to consider going for the source."

In the Sea of Star Spirits was the Limitless Financial Group's headquarters. Four figures were seated around a table in the personal guest room of the financial group's boss.

"I heard that the members of the Blood Gold Organization's upper echelons were assassinated recently. Your Federation of Light and Arcane Church won't ignore them after getting them to work for you, right?"

Sorokin took a sip of his drink and sized up the other three at the table. Everyone present was a Beyond Grade A bigshot who could easily shake various large organizations.

One of them was 'Mechanic Emperor' Manison, who appeared in the meeting with a mechanical host. The other was the doppelganger of 'Void Overlord' Kasuyi from the Arcane Church. The last was one of the protectors of the galactic black market, 'Beast Ancestor' Gorutan.

All three of them had a common identity. They were the shareholders of the Limitless Financial Group!

"Such a small matter has nothing to do with me," Manison said calmly.

Gorutan had a huge body, and he picked up his cup with his hairy hands. He poured all the drink into his mouth before saying, "I just received news that the Blood Gold Organization has met with the emissaries of the federation and church. They've come to an agreement."

With the sheer size of the galactic black market, they naturally had a Beyond Grade A to support them. A portion of the galactic black market managers were Beyond Grade A organizations. The galactic black market was an allied organization to protect the benefits of the evil factions and did not belong to a single person. There were many Beyond Grade As behind it, and Gorutan was one of them.

Sorokin's eyes then narrowed upon hearing that.

"If I didn't understand your words wrongly, the organizations behind all three of you plan to join hands?"

"You can say so." Kasuyi's voice had an ethereal feeling. "We have also sought you out because of this matter. You can treat us as emissaries."

Sorokin fiddled with the cup in his hands and said calmly, "I don't really want to interfere with this matter."

"Aren't you interested in the Evolutionary Totems?" Gorutan's voice rumbled like thunder.

"No, I believe that every organization in the universe is interested in the Evolutionary Totems," Sorokin said expressionlessly. "But according to my understanding of the Black Star Army, rashly intervening in this matter will be a huge risk. I do not like making a loss."

Manison nodded in response. "I understand. You don't only have business deals with the federation and church but also the dynasty. You do not wish to offend any party. Your Limitless Financial Group is different from those gray organizations and is protected by the law. You have the right to remain neutral."

"That's right. This is the case," Sorokin replied.

"Haha, don't worry. We will not ask you to do something too outrageous." Manison's mechanical host chuckled.

"Oh? Then, how can I help?"

"We hope for the Limitless Financial Group to invest in the Shattered Star Ring and compete with the Black Star Army using proper business means. This is only a small matter to the Limitless Financial Group. If you don't set your eyes on the Evolutionary Totems, the dynasty cannot disrupt your business."

Sorokin raised his brows and asked, "Why do you want me to do so?"

"This is a part of our plan to pressure the dynasty. The Black Star Army's opinion will influence the dynasty's strategy to deal with the Evolutionary Totems. We have to make Black Star know that he cannot think about swallowing such a huge business alone. Of course, other than these official matters, I also have a small conflict of interest with him," Manison said calmly.

Sorokin then chuckled and said, "So, it turns out that the Mechanic Emperor also has some conflict with Black Star. Ah ah, I also have some personal grudges with him."

"Does that mean that you agree?"

"I will definitely have to respect the views of three shareholders. However, it won't be so easy to snatch the Black Star Army's business," Sorokin said with a solemn tone. "I performed my research on the Black Star Army before. Their development is rapid, and they manage a few dozen different operations. Their four main operations are armed employment missions, mining operations for the local civilizations, the exploration of the Flickering World, and the sale of the Evolutionary Totems. Forgive me for being straightforward, but the latter three are specialized businesses that are difficult for an outsider to enter. It is difficult to deal a heavy blow to his core operations, and our Limitless Financial Group can only do so in other areas.

"Thankfully, the Black Star Army has only been around for twenty years or so, and their foundations aren't too stable. However, this will still require a great deal of investment... At the end of the day, what is my benefit for doing so?"

Manison then waved his finger, and a virtual screen appeared. A long list was on the screen.

"Resources, political support, and many more. The details are all written within the document. You only need to risk the Crimson Dynasty reducing their cooperation to you. However, we are in the interstellar era, and the dynasty will not be able to cut off all ties with you completely. You can gain a deeper business relationship with two other Universal Civilizations...

"You believe in benefits and risk. I believe that you will be able to make the right choice. I can give you a month to consider the matter, and you can reply then."

"I don't need that long. I can give you an answer now." Sorokin smiled. "This sounds like a good plan."

Chapter 916: High Grade Mechanical Sense

On the second satellite of the Black Star Army headquarters was Training Ground 001. This was a training plaza far larger than the training rooms and could support large scale battles. Furthermore, it was constructed with high tensile alloy and was capable of enduring even more powerful attacks. It was constructed like an oval-shaped sports stadium with a large mechanical roof covering the battlefield. The roof was made using a nano mimicry screen and could simulate various battlefields. There were cargo lanes underground that were connected to a warehouse of training mechanical soldiers.

Han Xiao sat at the side while watching the battle going on. Lagi, Feidin, Reynold, and the others were all beside him, either standing up or sitting down.

At this moment, there was an intense battle going on in the training ground. A few exits for the mechanical soldiers opened from the ground, and an endless stream of training mechanical soldiers came out from them. There were knights, mechanical beasts, Hovering Shield Shuttles, and many other types of mechanical soldiers charging at the two individuals in the middle of the training ground.

This battle was a D Grade battle, and the mechanical soldiers were all low grade ones. They used gunpowder and electromagnetic weapons, and the entire ground was charred black from the intense battle.

One of the two figures on the battlefield was clad in a black heavy mechanical armor while the other had magical shields floating around him. They were Nero and Tomar.

After learning from Reynold for a few years, Nero was now at Grade B. Apart from theoretical lessons, Reynold had also arranged for some combat training.

Nero was still young, and his body was still at the stage of puberty. But because he had consumed the Starry Spiritual Dragon blood and the life force potions bestowed to him by Aurora, his cell activity was extremely high, and his physique was comparable to an adult. Furthermore, the strength of his Mechanical Force had also exceeded his current Grade.

After two years of in-depth training, his [Middle Grade Mechanical Sense] had transformed into [High Grade Mechanical Sense] under the aid of his [Advanced Luck Glow].

He was not allowed to use any weapons given to him by Han Xiao during training, and all the equipment he was using had been crafted by him personally. Under the boost from his Mechanical Force, his weapons could unleash a powerful might, and the mechanical soldiers were all blasted into scrap metal by him.

Han Xiao had gone over to watch the battle so that he could check on Nero's progress.

Tomar was also a protagonist-level character who had Luck Glow and had an extraordinary talent in magic. Spells that an ordinary Mage would take seven days to learn took him less than a day to grasp. His learning aptitude was stunning, and he grew up rapidly under Lagi's tutelage. He was also a talent who had a great deal of potential.

Boom!

Han Xiao stroked his chin as he watched the battle and said to Reynold, "His Mechanic abilities aren't too bad, but his close combat skills are so-so. The moment the mechanical beasts approach him, he ends up being flustered. This is a result of a lack of experience."

"This is my oversight. I only had my sights set on his learning of machines but overlooked his close combat skills. I will definitely increase his training on close combat," Reynold said calmly.

"Increase it greatly," Han Xiao said with a deep voice. "But you cannot neglect his machinery training."

"Understood."

Bennett, who was present by using a long-distance projection, revealed a gratified smile.

Feidin could no longer stand it and said helplessly, "A Mechanic's weakness is close combat battle. Black Star, not every Mechanic can be the same as you. Don't set your expectations so high."

Han Xiao chuckled in response. "Dreams are necessary, and it isn't bad to have higher expectations of him."

He was truly happy in his heart. Nero's Mechanical Sense had already reached the high grade, and it was a matter of time before he obtained Perfect Mechanical Sense.

"Tomar's improvements are also extremely great." After thinking for a while, Han Xiao patted Lagi on the shoulder. "You've taught him well."

"What's the use of that? One day, he..."

Han Xiao's face darkened, and he covered Lagi's mouth. "You can keep quiet now."

Not too long later, Nero's ammunition was exhausted, and Tomar's magic ran out. The mechanical soldiers all stopped moving, and the training came to an end.

Both of them then returned to the viewing gallery while panting and sweat covered.

Han Xiao smiled and praised them. "Not bad."

"His Excellency Black Star has trained you well," Bennett added. "In a few years, I won't be a match for you."

Receiving the praise from his father and Han Xiao, Nero's face turned red, beaming with happiness.

Upon seeing that, Han Xiao nodded. He placed great importance in Nero not just because he wanted the [Perfect Mechanical Sense] but also because he hoped that Nero would grow to become a new pillar of the army.

After praising them for a while more, they all boarded the spaceship and returned to headquarters.

After two years of digestion, the Black Star Army had stabilized, and there were a few more satellite fortresses around the headquarters to hold the new members of the army.

After returning to his office, Sylvia came to find him.

"Teacher, many people are asking me when Black Star's Party will be held this year."

Han Xiao thought for a while before saying, "How about in a few months? We can start to issue the invites already."

The Black Star Army had already held two banquets to invite all those in cooperation with him to use the Evolution Cube. The banquet was becoming more and more solemn and influential. Many organizations were hoping to make use of this opportunity to build relationships with higher grade civilizations, and it was called Black Star's Party. It was in a competitive relationship with the Tyrant's Party.

The Evolution Cube did not only bring them money but gave the Black Star Army an opportunity to expand into other fields. The army had a powerful brand image, and there were few organizations in the Star Field that could compete with the army.

The benefits of the Evolutionary Totem created a snowball effect that allowed the Black Star Army to strengthen itself greatly. After two years of digestion, the operations of the Black Star Army had stabilized, and they were starting to look a bit more like a financial group.

Because of the Evolutionary Totem, there were more and more parties working together with the Black Star Army. The influence of the Black Star's Party grew, and they were gradually becoming a new faction.

If he released the restriction on the Evolutionary Totems, the profits obtained would increase many times over, but the pressure would also increase. Han Xiao was still satisfied with the current situation. The business pressure of the Evolutionary Totem was on the dynasty, and the army could avoid more than ninety percent of the risk.

"Alright, I shall go and prepare the invitations. There is something else. An organization that isn't cooperating with us wishes to participate in the Black Star's Party."

"The Black Star's Party will only invite those cooperating with us, and we can reject everyone else. This is a rule that we set a long time ago. Why are you bringing this matter up now?"

"Because the other party is a bigshot, so I cannot make the decision. Thus, I came to seek your opinion."

Han Xiao raised his brows, a little interested. "Who is the other party?"

"The Limitless Financial Group."

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao paused and fell into deep thought.

Sorokin's Limitless Financial Group?

Both parties had some conflicts before. Sorokin had once sent his subsidiary organization to probe the players of the army and had been warned by Han Xiao. It had been more than two years since then, so who knew what kind of objective the other party had for suddenly participating in his Black Star's Party?

"What's their reason?" Han Xiao asked.

"The Limitless Financial Group wishes to have business cooperation with our army and says that it is related to the Flickering World. They know that the dynasty will grant their allies some territory and want to work together with us."

"I see. That is reasonable," Han Xiao said.

Although the galactic financial groups could not be the first batch to enjoy the benefits of the Flickering World, their shadows could be seen in the future development plans.

The benefits of a new Star Field were extremely rich. Did the Limitless Financial Group want to seize the initiative?

Although the reason was believable, Han Xiao was still wary of the Limitless Financial Group because of their previous conflict.

After thinking for a moment, he said, "Send them an invitation if that's the case. Tell them that I want to make use of this opportunity to meet Sorokin."

The Pro League would finish in a few months, and Han Xiao was not afraid of the Limitless Financial Group creating any trouble.

Meeting the other party would be beneficial to him.

"Understood. I will take care of it." Sylvia nodded and left the room.

Han Xiao then poured himself an alcoholic beverage and drank while going about his business.

He managed to find the time to open the forums after a while.

Today was the first round of the International Finals, which was a best of five competition. The first round was Rivervale against Tomahawk, and the viewership rates of the match set a new record again.

With three Chinese teams making it into the top eight, the players from the Shattered Star Ring were all extremely excited. The way they saw it, if Dynasty, Long Sky, and Rivervale were all able to win the first round, there would be three Chinese teams in the top four!

At the same time, a portion of the players who did not think highly of the Chinese teams could not help but retort that all the three teams might end up losing in the first round, and not a single team would be able to enter into the top four.

At the finals, all the teams would no longer hide their trump cards, and the competition would be even more intense than before. Han Xiao was also pretty curious about the ranks that the Chinese teams could achieve this round.

Chapter 917: [Indestructible Body]!

The Rivervale and Tomahawk teams entered a jungle-covered planet for their battlefield.

The trees were as tall as the clouds and covered the skies. Only a bit of light could penetrate through the densely packed leaves.

Both teams appeared in different parts of the jungle, and the spectators could switch to different viewpoints of the players and teams.

"Good luck, Rivervale! Get rid of Tomahawk!"

"First place vs eighth place. Easy game."

"Go Maple Moon!"

The format of the finals was best of five, and they had to fight five matches every round. The five rounds were team fight, arena battle, capture the flag, dungeon competition, and dungeon generation.

The countdown of one minute came to an end, and the first round of the finals began. The two teams immediately sprang into action. Maple Moon from Rivervale threw out a compressed orb, which transformed into a pagoda-like base station. It was used to prevent the enemy from detecting their whereabouts and also to confuse the enemy. The logo of the Black Star Army was shining on the base station. It was a product of the Black Star Army, and the quality was guaranteed.

On the other side, Tomahawk had also begun hiding their whereabouts, but they used a magical tool instead. The leader of Tomahawk, Captain Viking, took out a black, magical scroll with golden inscriptions shining on it. He then tore the scroll apart, and a dense magical energy flowed out of it to cover the entire Tomahawk team.

"Eh, isn't this a sovereign mage scroll?" Han Xiao was also viewing the battle on the forums and raised his brows upon seeing that.

The materials used to craft such a magical scroll were extremely rare, and it was capable of storing even more powerful magic. It needed to be crafted by hand, and Han Xiao had seen Lagi craft one before. A grandmaster-level spell would be engraved on the scroll at the very least, and it was an expensive item. Tomahawk was obviously extremely rich for them to use such a scroll to carve a concealment spell.

"Now that it's the finals, all the teams are bringing out their trump cards," Han Xiao said with interest.

None of the teams would hold anything back in the International Finals and would go all out. Such a situation would only bring about more variables in the battles. The strength of the various teams would undergo a huge change, and it would be difficult to use a team's previous performance to estimate their strength.

Different strategies would have to be crafted based on the field that they were battling in. Since they were in a dense jungle, it was important for them to conceal themselves and be the first to detect the enemy.

After concealing their own locations, both teams started to search for the enemy. Rivervale made use of a multi elemental radar while Tomahawk made use of a magic incantation that had many different aura detecting spells. Because of their culture, Tomahawk preferred to use magic instead.

Both parties moved forward slowly, and the atmosphere grew more and more tense as the seconds ticked by. A Chinese commentator then began describing the battle on the forums.

"Alright, both teams have already entered the battlefield. We can see that the mini map is split into sixteen regions. The top left corner region is A1, and the bottom right is D4. The columns shall be numbered one to four while the rows are lettered A to D. Rivervale is currently at A3, which is at the top of the map, while Tomahawk is at C1, which is at the bottom left side of the map. Let's see what routes they will choose. Oh! Indeed, both parties have used flying devices!"

One of the Tomahawk members belonged to the bird race, and he spread his wings to fly in the sky. On the other side, Maple Moon threw up a few compressed orbs into the sky, which transformed into floating soldiers, patrolling the air at high speed.

To the players at the current stage, flying was extremely easy. However, because of the trees blocking them, flying did not give them much of an advantage.

With the compression technology, it was far easier to bring along machines, and the deployment speed of a Mechanic also increased greatly. In the previous version, it would be impossible for Maple Moon to bring a few dozen different machines or easily deploy her machines with a wave of her arms.

The flying troops of both parties discovered each other very quickly, and the member from Tomahawk easily destroyed the floating mechanical soldiers, which did not have any Mechanical Force boost.

The commentator immediately exclaimed, "Oh! Both parties engaged in a short, intense battle! Let's take a look at what both parties will do next. It seems like Tomahawk has chosen to use a long-range raid strategy and are charging toward the location of their scout. What about Rivervale? Eh, they seem to have grasped the enemy's location and are currently going around in circles! Player Maple Moon had set up a large number of mines and mechanical traps along the way. She is trying to make the entire battlefield into her own territory! As long as a Mechanic is given enough time, she would be able to expand her geographical advantage. Tomahawk is currently on the passive side..."

The strategies of Rivervale revolved around the Mechanic class, and their own captain, Frenzied Sword, was a Mechanical Pugilist. After Maple Moon joined them, their strategies became even sneakier.

Tomahawk was very quickly hit, and they stepped on the mines that Maple Moon had planted.

After a series of explosions, a sea of flames engulfed the forest. Not to mention anything else, in terms of destructiveness alone, the Mechanic Class was the undeniable number one!

With the other party stepping into the trap, Rivervale no longer remained hidden and changed their route for a head on assault. The members of Tomahawk all had magical armor, but compared to the products of the army, their magical armor was on the losing end.

Frenzied Sword brandished his blade and sliced through the enemy formation. Their team then took down Tomahawk after paying the price of two members and claimed their first victory.

The Chinese players were all in a good mood after the victory.

"Haha, didn't I say so? Rivervale was definitely going to suppress Tomahawk. Their position in the Regular Season isn't just for show."

"The members of Tomahawk have experienced it personally."

"With little sis Maple Moon joining in, Rivervale is much stronger than before."

"Little sis is truly powerful. She has character but is still gentle. I am now a die-hard fan of hers! When will she be coming out with an album?"

"Aunty Rainy Kim is already an old lady. She isn't as young or pretty as little sis Maple Moon. I'm sorry, but I am going to change my taste. It isn't that you aren't good enough, but my sights are just set too high."

"Forgetting about your old wife after finding a new mistress!"

Amid the chattering of the audiences, both teams took a short break and started the arena battle. Tomahawk sent out an ordinary player to probe the enemy team, but Rivervale had actually sent out Frenzied Sword as their first player.

After winning the team battle, their captain was appearing first in the arena, and they obviously intended to suppress the other party in terms of aura. The players could feel Rivervale's confidence from their arrangements.

The commentator immediately fired off rapidly like a machine gun.

"Rivervale's captain, Frenzied Sword, requested to fight in the first battle of the arena. Although he didn't manage to enter the top sixteen for the singles, he was ranked eighteenth in the International Regulars. He may have been able to enter the finals if he was just a little luckier. Let's watch the battle now... Oh, just as I expected! Frenzied Sword easily ended his opponent. A Mechanical Pugilist has the advantages of both a Mechanic and Pugilist, and this Class has a huge advantage in this season."

Frenzied Sword fought the enemy head on without dodging or hiding. He threw out a bunch of compressed orbs to form various mechanical traps so that his opponent's path would be restricted. The control ability of a Mechanical Pugilist was far higher than that of a normal Pugilist.

After easily approaching the enemy, Frenzied Sword unleashed a flurry of attacks and decimated his enemy's health in less than a minute.

He was both powerful and handsome. Although he was no longer a Pugilist, Frenzied Sword was still as elegant as before.

Tomahawk could no longer sit still, and Captain Viking came out next. It was a captain versus captain fight.

Captain Viking was a Pugilist, and he took off his heavy armor to activate all his buffs from an armorless state. Magical inscriptions could be seen all over his body to provide him with defense and recovery.

"Roar! Fresh blood and glory!" Captain Viking let out a crazed roar.

Frenzied Sword stood opposite him and had a speechless look on his face.

"He is a Pugilist indeed. His shamelessness resistance is truly high..."

Right at this moment, a muscular figure could be seen behind Captain Viking, and it disappeared in a flash. Following which, Captain Viking's muscles began to balloon up, and the Pugilist flames on his body exploded.

A new buff could be seen on his status panel. Captain Viking made use of a Character Summon Card!

The commentator then gasped. "Berserk from the Clan of Glory. +50% Close Ranged Damage, +30% Physical Resistance, +400 STR, +200 DEX, +20% Health, +40% Movement Speed, and an additional 300 Frost Damage for every attack. It actually lasts for thirty minutes! This Character Summon Card is so powerful!"

The chat immediately exploded with comments.

"The other party used a Character Summon Card. Victory is now up in the air."

"Let's see if Frenzied Sword has a powerful Character Summon Card. If he doesn't, he will probably be screwed."

A Character Summon Card was extremely rare, and it was even more difficult to obtain a Character Summon Card of a powerful character. All professional players treated them as their trump cards. Now that they were in the finals, none of them would hold such a trump card back.

There was only a single region that had the [Black Star Army Badge: Evolution], so it was reasonable for it to be banned. However, a Character Summon Card was different, and every player had a chance of obtaining one. Thus, it was not banned, but there were some limitations.

The effects of the Character Summon Card could not be carried on to the next round. Even if Captain Viking achieved a complete victory in the arena with the effects of the Character Summon Card not ending, his status would have to be refreshed, and he would not be able to carry on the effects to the 'capture the flag' battle.

The Character Summon Cards that the professional players had were rare, and it was a feature that made the battle more interesting for the ordinary players. Such a rule provided greater excitement to the battle while reducing the influence of the Character Summon Card to the competition.

After all, there were fifteen rounds at the very least, and a Character Summon Card was untradable. It would be considered a skill if one could take out fifteen overpowered Character Summon Cards.

Upon witnessing the opponent's changes, Frenzied Sword also activated a Character Summon Card.

A suave appearance then appeared behind him, and everyone squealed as they recognized the figure.

"Woah! It's Black Star!"

"It's here, it's here! Just as I was saying, how could Frenzied Sword not have a Character Summon Card!"

"I remember Frenzied Sword using a Black Star Character Summon Card in the previous season as well."

"Black Star is now a Beyond Grade A. Will the effects be the same?"

The players all became excited. They were only able to see question marks when viewing Han Xiao's interface and only had an estimate of Han Xiao's strength through the dungeons. Thus, they were truly curious about his strength.

A new buff could then be seen on Frenzied Sword's status panel.

Character Summon Card - Black Star: [Indestructible Body]—You are immune to and will absorb 25% of all damage. 60% of the remaining damage will be converted into energy, and you can convert energy to health at the ratio of 1:9. You can recover a maximum of 35% of your health every second.

Duration: 10 minutes

Upon seeing the effects of the Character Summon Card, everyone exploded with excitement.

"WTF! What kind of perverse ability is this‽"

"No wonder Black Star has such a nickname in the universe..."

All the players were dumbfounded.

Although the Character Summon Card that Captain Viking used was powerful, it was still acceptable. However, the effect of the Black Star Character Summon Card was completely out of their understanding, and the spectators were shocked!

Was this the strength of a Beyond Grade A? Just a single ability of his was so frightening!

His damage was high, he had many minions, and he still had such thick skin...

With such an ability, not to mention now, they would probably never be able to kill such a terrifying boss!

"Eh? Why does he have my Character Summon Card?" Han Xiao was stunned for a moment. He did not remember issuing such a mission before.

After thinking for a while, he finally understood what was going on. Frenzied Sword probably obtained a blank Character Summon Card and imprinted his ability.

"Alright, I haven't used this talent too much after my Promotion, so you are enjoying it first."

Han Xiao shook his head and chuckled.

Chapter 918: Finals

With the buff of the Black Star Character Summon Card, Frenzied Sword abandoned over eighty percent of his defenses and concentrated on attacking.

He brandished his closed-ranged mechanical weapon without any restraint and blasted craters on the surface of the arena.

Captain Viking was reduced to a pathetic state and could only attempt to avoid all the attacks. He had activated the Berserk Character Summon Card with the intention of fighting Frenzied Sword head on, but he was completely unable to damage the enemy at all. Every time he damaged the enemy, his opponent's health would be recovered the very next second.

As such, Captain Viking could only adjust his strategy and stall for time.

There was a time limit to the Character Summon Card, and although Frenzied Sword's recovery was ferocious, his damage was not increased. As such, Captain Viking tried his best to stall for as much time as possible. The longer this battle lasted, the easier things would be for his teammates.

Captain Viking activated a special skill, and the axe in his hands turned blue and transparent as though it had turned into an axe made from ice. His physical damage would be converted to ice damage so that Frenzied Sword's speed would be lowered.

Frenzied Sword ignored all the incoming attacks and charged forward relentlessly. The mobility of a Mechanical Pugilist was far higher than an ordinary Pugilist, and even if his speed was restricted, Captain Viking would not be able to escape from him.

Kacha!

He swapped out for a gigantic alloy axe and waved it around crazily.

Dang dang dang!

The alloy axe with Mechanical Force surrounding it clashed with the ice-like axe over and over again. Red sparks and blue frost could be seen flying in all directions, and a formless energy wave would be sent out every time their weapons met.

They were both Grade B Supers, so the special effects of the battle were pretty good.

Captain Viking could only try his best to last as long as possible, and his health fell to forty percent very quickly. On the contrary, Frenzied Sword was still at his peak, and every attack of his would still be at his peak.

Clank!

Right at this moment, the ground under Captain Viking's feet suddenly cracked open, and an underground spider shot out from the ground. A large electrical wave was released, which gathered beneath Captain Viking's feet. Captain Viking felt his legs go numb, and he entered a temporarily movement restricted status.

In the midst of the chaotic battle, Frenzied Sword had secretly released some mechanical spiders and released a control ability to restrict the enemy's mobility.

A Mechanical Pugilist had many tricks up their sleeves and was like the combination between a weapon master and hidden weapon master. The number of control skills that a Mechanical Pugilist had far exceeded an ordinary Pugilist.

Seizing the opportunity, Frenzied Sword switched out to his spear and attacked.

Captain Viking could only raise his axe to block the incoming attack.

Clank!

The spear clashed with the axe, and sparks flew in all directions. Captain Viking could feel a powerful force coming from the axe with powerful vibrations included within the spear. The other party had obviously used a skill to complement his weapon's specialty. His axe was knocked aside, and he was left wide open.

The next moment, the mechanical spear suddenly changed shapes and broke up into four spider legs. The spider legs then penetrated Captain Viking's back and fixed him on the spot. It looked as though his spear had transformed into claws to hold the enemy in place.

At the same time, the spearhead transformed into a barrel, and an ion cannon charged up while aiming at the immobile Captain Viking.

Swoosh!

A brilliant blue ion cannon shot out from the barrel and penetrated Captain Viking's chest.

Frenzied Sword made use of this opportunity and unleashed a brilliant combo to wipe out Captain Viking's remaining health.

Because of the Black Star Character Summon Card, he was able to abandon all defenses and focus on attacking. Without having to bother about his health, his attacks were intensified by many folds, and he dared to take much more risks.

"This combo is truly amazing. The Mechanical Pugilist Class is truly impressive."

"I feel like training a Mechanical Pugilist smurf."

"Stop dreaming. A professional Mechanical Pugilist is completely different from a Mechanical Pugilist like you. A noob like you shouldn't have such dreams."

The next player then entered the battlefield and mimicked Captain Viking to stall for time. However, it was completely useless, and Frenzied Sword got rid of three people in a row.

With the Black Star Character Summon Card, his endurance was stunning, and he always had the initiative in his hands.

The Chinese players watched with excitement as they witnessed Frenzied Sword using the effects of the Black Star Character Summon Card. Suddenly, a strange question popped up in the heads of many of the players.

"Umm, Black Star is a Mechanic, right?"

"That's right. This [Indestructible Body] is far more powerful than the [Advanced Strengthened Life] from the previous version. It looks more like the core skills of a Pugilist instead..."

"I understand now! A Mechanic without Endurance doesn't have a soul!"

"I understand now. So, it turns out that being a tank is the best way to play the Mechanic Class."

The Chinese spectators began joking.

However, Frenzied Sword seemed to use Black Star's abilities every season, and they personally witnessed how the Black Star Character Summon Card became more and more perverse, from the Machinery Affinity boost in the first season to the [Advanced Strengthened Life] in the second season. Now, it was the [Indestructible Body]. Every season represented a huge improvement.

Perhaps this was considered them watching as Black Star rose to prominence.

Many players could not help but feel this way and had a sense of satisfaction as witnesses of a powerhouse rising to power.

The remaining battles were completely one-sided, and the other Tomahawk players didn't bother wasting any other trump cards. Frenzied Sword single-handedly wiped out the entire team and achieved another overwhelming victory.

Although it only appeared for a short time, the terrifying ability of the [Indestructible Body] was imprinted into the memories of the players.

Everyone was extremely curious about what other power abilities Black Star had on him. He was always able to shock them without fail.

Looking at the discussions in the forums, Han Xiao could predict that all the players would go to him if they had a blank Character Summon Card in the future.

Following which, the 'capture the flag' battle became Maple Moon's stage. She set up a fortress at the very start of the battle, and Tomahawk would have to suffer a huge loss if they wanted to steal their flag. As such, the gap between the two parties grew larger and larger.

Rivervale did not give Tomahawk the opportunity to turn the tables around and seized another victory.

After winning three consecutive rounds, Rivervale's victory was already guaranteed. The next two dungeon battles were much easier, and Rivervale obtained the victory for their first round.

...

The first round of the International Finals was extremely exciting, and all eight teams went all out.

The result of the first round had truly excited the Chinese players.

Rivervale defeated Tomahawk with a score of three to one, Dynasty defeated Devil with a score of three to one, and Long Sky defeated Hydra with a score of three to two...

This meant that all three Chinese teams had made it into the top four!

Their score from the previous season had already been spectacular, and they had managed to improve this season and clinch three out of four of the top four spots. The only lonely one left was America's Key!

With the semifinalists being decided, the players from all the regions were shocked. None of them expected the performance of the Chinese to be so powerful this season!

They were demons!

The Chinese teams were truly frightening during this season, and Key became the only hope of the players from all the other regions.

Apart from the Shattered Star Ring region, the players from the other regions all had a common enemy and hoped that Key would be able to defeat the great demon king and obtain victory.

Compared to the other countries looking as though they were facing a desperate war, the Chinese players were all celebrating. Obtaining three out of the four spots meant that they were guaranteed a spot in the final. Furthermore, there was a higher chance for both the champion and first runner up to be from China.

It would be a huge honor if both teams in the final belonged to the same country. If China could be the first country to achieve such a feat, it would be akin to creating history. As such, the Chinese players were all extremely expectant.

The expectations of the local players and enmity of the foreign players brought a great deal of pressure to the players of Rivervale. The opponent that Key drew for the semi-finals was Rivervale.

If they beat Key, everything would be good, and Rivervale would be the one to create history and find their chance to be a super guild.

But if they lost to Key, they would have wasted all the fame that they had accumulated throughout this season. This was a double-edged sword!

To all the players, the battle between Rivervale and Key was like the final of this season. As long as Rivervale won, the championship title would be in their hands for sure!

As such, all the players in the Shattered Star Ring began gathering information about Key and analyzed the enemy's strategies to provide intelligence for Rivervale.

Although Rivervale did not necessarily need all this, their passionate actions warmed the hearts of Rivervale and the others.

The semifinals finally started, and the attention of almost all the viewers was drawn to the battle between Key and Rivervale.

In terms of individual combat strength, Key had the middle-ranked players from Devil and their overall strength was definitely superior. They definitely were not ordinary since they could emerge victorious from Division A.

The leader of Key was Key of Solomon, and Frenzied Sword was his old opponent. Both of them had fought in the first season, and Key of Solomon had lost to Frenzied Sword back then. After two versions, Key of Solomon had also improved.

The battle was extremely intense from the very start, and four rounds went by quickly. The current score was two to two, and the final match started.

In the final round of the competition, the gap was not widened in the team fight and arena, but in the 'capture the flag' and dungeon rounds, Maple Moon displayed her might and took out all her trump cards. Even the Void Dragon embryonic mechanical suit made an appearance, and she aided her team to clinch victory.

The final result was three to two, and Rivervale won. Maple Moon made the largest contribution and had a large wave of new fans.

On the other side, Dynasty and Long Sky fought each other again like in the previous season. However, the outcome was reversed, and Long Sky lost to Dynasty this time.

Two Chinese teams would be facing each other in the finals, and a new milestone was created for the Pro League.

The Chinese players all heaved a sigh of relief and were extremely satisfied.

Because Key did not manage to enter the finals, the overseas players were all disappointed. With China fighting each other for the championship, the finals were not as exciting as the semi-finals.

Although both the Chinese teams desired victory, they did not have any conflicts and thus fought stably for victory.

It was a pity that Rivervale was exhausted in the semifinals, and they obviously were not in top condition. Dynasty had only fought four rounds in the semi-finals and had more time to rest.

Finally, Rivervale lost, and Dynasty took the title of champion!

The excitement from China obtaining victory was not as ubiquitous as the previous season, but there was a great sense of satisfaction. China now had top notch teams in the international scene, and while obtaining victory deserved to be celebrated, it was not that big of a surprise.

Compared to Han Xiao's previous life, the Chinese teams would not be challenging other teams; other teams would be coming to challenge them. This was the glory of the great demon king, and the Chinese players were truly satisfied about that.

Because Rivervale completed the milestone for China, the Chinese players were all very understanding toward them and encouraging even though they lost the final.

The players who did not think too highly of China before the competition now had nothing to say.

With China clinching both the championship and first runner-up, the players cried out with excitement on the forums, and Han Xiao was also pretty happy. However, this was a half-good and half-bad matter for him.

The results of the Pro League would affect the actions of the players. In the next version, when all the regions gathered in the Flickering World, the Chinese teams would probably end up being the public enemy, and the Black Star Army would probably be provoked by the other player factions.

Those foreign clubs would definitely rally together to snatch resources, missions, and territory from China.

Version 4.0 was the version for the players to climb onto the stage of the universal factions. Han Xiao would not underestimate the billions of players from the other regions.

As such, he would have to build up a huge enterprise in the Flickering World during the version update period.

This would be his foundation for Version 4.0.

"This version update period will be the key to my development..."

Han Xiao then closed the forums and fell into thought.

Chapter 919: Prospect and Version Update (1)

For the next ten or so days, a joyful atmosphere filled the Shattered Star Ring forums.

This was China's best result to date, and Dynasty, Rivervale, and Long Sky received a great amount of praise.

The players were still extremely excited about the Pro League, and the forums were filled with their discussion about the exciting battles.

The various teams would definitely carry out various promotional activities after the competition, and the various clubs rented a place at the Black Star Army headquarters to carry out a meet and greet session with the players.

At the end of the version, the Gulal civil war that the players had participated in was also going to come to an end.

The Pro League lasted for a long time, and the players who did not pass through the preliminary rounds all returned to the Gulal Civilization battlefield. They watched the Pro League while working together with the fleets to snatch the territories of the Ancient Emperor Party and Descendant Party. After a long series of battles, they brought the Pioneer Party into power.

The Pioneer Party expressed their thanks to the Black Star Army for the army's assistance, and the employment fees were wired to the account of the army.

It was also considered the end of the player's mission, and the players were only left with the Flickering World mission that had yet to be completed. However, this long mission obviously would not be completed within this version, and the players were not anxious about it.

As such, many of the players began leading a relaxed life after the Pro League to reorganize their gains from this version. Even if they did not go out into the fields to kill monsters, there were many entertainment outlets in the universe.

Plenty of events happened in Version 3.0. They personally witnessed how the Black Star Army became a Beyond Grade A organization and followed the Black Star Army to perform many missions. The sense of belonging that the players had toward the Black Star Army grew stronger and stronger, and this was a win-win situation for both parties.

Through the hard work of the players, the content of the Galaxy Chronicles increased greatly, and information about the Black Star Army also became more detailed. The players had personally witnessed the growth of the Black Star Army all the way from its conception.

Galaxy Times came out with a new program to interview the top four teams that made it into the International League. They also did a projection about what would happen in the next version. Han Xiao, who was currently supervising Sylvia's preparation of the Black Star's Party, also saw it.

"Hello players, this is Galaxy Times, dedicated to sharing first-hand game information," the male host said. "Your gaming career is our top priority."

"The third season of the Pro League has come to an end. Dynasty, Long Sky, Rivervale and Temple of God represented China to obtain spectacular results in this season of the Pro League," the female host said. "We are lucky to have the captains and teammates of the four teams with us to talk about their interesting encounters during the competition..."

The four teams then made their appearance and waved to the audience.

"King Admiral, how do you feel about winning the championship this time?"

"Dynasty's status has been extremely good during this season, and we displayed the strength that we ought to. The entire team is definitely excited about winning the championship," King Admiral lazily replied.

Second Prince then coughed dryly and could not help but add, "We obtained the championship because of the good teamwork between our team. Everyone was able to do their own job well. This is the result of everyone's hard work... and definitely not because of the captain's leadership."

The host then asked a few more questions before turning to Rivervale.

"Team Rivervale, although all of you didn't manage to clinch the championship, your contributions can't be underestimated. Your team kicked out Key during the semi-finals and locked in the championship title for China ahead of the final. I thank you for your contributions on behalf of our audience."

"We only did something within our capabilities," Frenzied Sword said humbly.

"Rivervale is a new team but has shown rapid improvement. Your score has been rising over the three seasons, and many people feel that Rivervale is a new super club. What are your thoughts on that?"

Frenzied Sword nodded and said, "I will have to thank our fans for their love. During the semi-finals, countless individuals provided us with strategies and information. We were truly moved by that."

"In this season, Maple Moon made a large contribution for Rivervale. As the captain, what do you think about her?" the male host asked.

Frenzied Sword thought for a moment before saying solemnly, "The best decision that Rivervale has made to date is signing Maple Moon. She has greatly increased the strength of our team and is an irreplaceable team member."

After three seasons, Frenzied Sword was no longer a new player in the eyes of the players but a god level player. His status was equivalent to Hao Tian, and Maple Moon had become a core member of Rivervale. Her status was like Second Prince in Dynasty and Sleepy Winter in Long Sky.

The host then continued the interview, and Long Sky was extremely bitter. Although finishing in the top four was not too bad, it was considered a step back for them.

It was finally the turn to interview Temple of God, and the comments section became active.

"How are your feelings as the sacrificial lamb?"

"I thank Temple of God for their contributions. They lit themselves up to shine brightly for others."

"So, it turns out that I've always blamed Li Ge wrongly. You are truly sacrificial and a saint who can endure humiliation."

"Everyone, cry out together with me, brother Temple of God!"

"Temple of God's contributions are truly the greatest. If any of the other three teams had been picked to enter Division A, we would have wasted a slot. Temple of God would probably have been eliminated in the first round regardless. If Long Sky had been chosen, they may not have been able to make it into the top eight, and this would be akin to losing two slots... Since Temple of God entered Division A, we sacrificed our lousiest to ensure the smooth victory of the other three teams. Thus, it can be said that Temple of God is truly the biggest contributor to China!"

The teams then chatted about other interesting parts of the competition, and the interviews came to an end. They then started the next topic, which was the prediction for the next version.

"With the increase in Grades of the players, there are more regions being opened up," the female host said. "We had predicted that the inter-Star Field travel would probably be activated in the next version."

"There have already been examples of inter-Star Field travel in Version 3.0, and it was related to the Black Star Army and the Shattered Star Ring," the male host said. "The Black Star Army once provided a channel to cross Star Fields for the players in the Constellation Corridor.

"At the same time, the players of the Shattered Star Ring could also enter the Flickering World Main Storyline Mission. With the scale of the Flickering World mission, it is very likely to be an important event for the players in the Shattered Star Ring during the next version.

"All these signs point to inter-Star Field travel being very likely during the next version. Furthermore, the Black Star Army will probably play an important role for this."

Galaxy Times had once made such a guess when the players from the Constellation Corridor were allowed to cross Star Fields. They restated their prediction once again.

The presence of the Black Star Army was truly too great in Version 3.0. According to their experience from the previous two versions, the actions of the Black Star Army would usually hint at future development. As such, the actions of the Black Star Army were important evidence for Galaxy Times.

Han Xiao nodded and thought to himself, Because of the Main Storyline Mission, the players can guess that the Flickering World will probably be a big event in the next version. However, no one's guessed that it will be a world server...

During Version 4.0 in his previous life, the Flickering World had completed their initial exploration phase and had been opened up to the outside world. Many factions began recruiting members to head toward the Flickering World to compete with each other while exploring new regions.

High mobility was a foundation of the galactic civilizations. Mobile residents, resources, finances, and so on were the blood and vessels that connected the various Star Fields. No civilization was a lone island anymore.

As such, a new Star Field would definitely open up to the outside. Furthermore, a new Star Field represented new opportunities for development, which gave some factions hope to gain a territory. As such, many organizations that no longer had a way to advance would migrate to the Flickering World and engage in a competition for territory and resources.

The Crimson Dynasty had the highest authority in the Star Field. They chose to open the Flickering World for two main reasons. First, it was the natural course of development in the current generation, and second, others would share the construction cost.

The amount of resources and manpower required to develop was far greater than exploration. Even if they were a Universal Civilization, it would be an enormous project for them to build up a new Star Field from scratch. Furthermore, there were still two other civilizations eyeing them covetously from the side, trying to seize the opportunity to suppress the dynasty. As such, the dynasty needed to give the job of development to the countless organizations and use methods like tax to digest the benefits of the Flickering World.

The entire universe had their sights set on the Flickering World, and even the tyrannical Crimson Dynasty knew that they did not have the ability to swallow it all by themselves. Greed and poverty were two sides of the same coin, and the outcome of them trying to swallow everything by themselves was extremely clear.

The galactic society believed in free economic trade, and unless there was a need, the Crimson Dynasty would not restrict their allies from competing with each other. Besides, using competition to spur the outside organizations on was also a situation that the dynasty was willing to see.

The dynasty would only hold the most lucrative region in their hands and a portion of the Star Field would be controlled directly by the dynasty. As for the rest, it would be split among important allies of the dynasty like the Black Star Army to protect the Flickering World and ensure that the dynasty had control over the Star Field.

In such a situation, the players would have a large space for them to display their abilities. Even without a mission, the players would definitely compete with each other for sure.

Chapter 920: Prospect and Version Update (2)

"The first exploration phase of the Flickering World will soon end, and construction will follow shortly after. At that time, a large amount of resources and manpower will be required. The army has no lack of funds, and together with the support from the Crimson Dynasty, there will be no need for me to worry about resources during the version update period."

He had a monopoly in the Evolutionary Totem business, and it was his faction's specialty. It brought him a large amount of profit, and among the Beyond Grade A allies of the dynasty, he would probably belong to the group that had no lack of money.

In his plans, the mechanical civilization and the Black Spirit Race would be his focus for development. The former would be his source of high-quality soldiers while the latter had great potential. He would be able to allow them to grow without any hindrance and concern in his own territory.

He was no longer watching the Black Spirit Race develop but personally intervening in the development of the race. The Black Spirit Race had a strong ability to accept changes, and as long as their development was on track, they would definitely soar forward rapidly.

The version update period from Version 3.0 to Version 4.0 was a couple of decades. The players would return when the Flickering World opened to the outside world.

With the experience from his previous life, Han Xiao knew which organizations would compete in the Flickering World, and this was a huge advantage for him.

During this version update period, the entire galaxy would be focused mainly on expansion. The Crimson Dynasty would probably face huge pressure, and Han Xiao himself would likely meet some trouble because of the Evolution Cube. However, with his current strength and status, there should not be that many threats from the outside.

The Black Star Army had only been around for roughly twenty years, and the version update period was going to last for a few decades. This would be a good time to let the Black Star Army solidify their foundation and transform from a 'newborn organization' to a 'veteran organization'.

"Hila is still continuing to grow, and although her growth speed isn't as fast as in my previous life, she has greater potential with my aid. During the version update period, it is very likely for her to become a new Beyond Grade A..."

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

This way, his organization would have one more top combatant. Even if Hila chose to become independent, both of them would definitely remain allies.

At that time, the Shattered Star Ring would have six Beyond Grade As, and the army would be able to benefit greatly from it.

Psyker, on the other hand, definitely would not have a good time.

During the entire Version 3.0, Han Xiao had harvested a large amount of experience from the players, and it was stored in his interface. The players would be offline during the version update period, and huge events would be rare. This accumulated experience would be the strategic resource for him to last through this version update period.

At his current level, leveling up once would require a sky-high amount of experience. Although Han Xiao's stash was great, it would not be enough if he used it all to level up. A couple of decades was a long time, and he had to use his experience sparingly.

In his plans, he would obtain a new Class Advancement and Race Advancement after reaching level three hundred, and he would have to increase the level of his skills to obtain more Potential Points so that the levels of his new knowledge would all be increased.

The experience required to increase his level in the future would only increase, and developing more crop fields would aid in his efficiency of harvesting experience. Version 4.0 did not only have more competition from the world but also gave him the opportunity to develop a new batch of crops.

The players had settled the Gulal civil war a while ago, and the [Gulal Civilization: The Flames of Pioneers!] mission on his interface was also completed.

The Mission Rating of this mission was dependent on the performance of an individual. He had thrown the mission over to the players and did not do it himself. As such, his Mission Rating was not high. However, the experience that he gained from the mission was not the main point. The experience that the players obtained would eventually flow back to him through their purchases, and that profit was many times that of the mission.

After three versions of hard work, the Black Star Army had developed to its current state, and Han Xiao was no longer as worried about the version update period.

"I am already fully prepared and waiting for the day the dynasty divvies up the territories."

...

After the end of the Pro League, the version update date drew nearer and nearer. The attention of the players was also diverted from the Pro League to the new version.

Many players kept a large amount of experience and wanted to use it to reach the next level limit in the new version.

The players were all gathered in the Black Star Army headquarters, chatting with their friends while waiting to go offline.

At the corner of the plaza, the professional players were gathered together, chatting among themselves.

"There are plenty of new players in this version. Did we see so many players in the previous two versions?"

Twinkle Fried Rice shook his head.

"The more the merrier. This way, the Pro League will have higher viewership rates." Li Ge chuckled.

"I wonder how long the version update period would be this time," Maple Moon said curiously.

"It shouldn't be too long, right? Our Flickering World mission hasn't ended yet. We will definitely get to continue the exploration during the next version," Frenzied Sword replied. "I am truly curious to see what the Black Star Army will be like during the next version."

The few of them chatted and suddenly saw King Admiral waving at them from afar. Frenzied Sword and the others then went over.

King Admiral chuckled and said, "Since everyone is here, let's find a day to have a meal. We can take it to be a celebration for obtaining both the championship and first runner up."

"Sure." Li Ge was the first to agree.

"I remember that we did so after the previous season ended as well," Sleepy Winter said while stroking his chin.

"That's right. We should just make it a tradition. The champions shall be in charge of treating all the Chinese players. We can go for a vacation together."

"Better treat us to something good. Don't be like Long Sky and only treat us to some roadside store."

"Dining at a roadside store is value for money," Hao Tian said bitterly.

Everyone then cheered at the proposition, and King Admiral had no choice but to accept it.

Very quickly, all the players went offline, and the entire plaza became empty.

A notification also popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

_____________________

Version 3.0 update activated.

Saving data... Save complete!

Player forums closed.

Update Duration: Unknown. Please wait patiently.

_____________________

Han Xiao then looked up, and the player forum button had turned gray.

"The players are all offline..." Han Xiao took a deep breath. "It's now time to start planning for Version 4.0."

...

At the same time, at the entrance of the Shattered Star Ring stargate, a trade fleet had just exited the stargate. The spaceship had an egg-like shape with silver armor. It looked extremely simple yet high tech. The insignia of the Limitless Financial Group was carved out on the exterior of the spaceship.

The main flagship was a gigantic flying saucer. In the command room, a tall man stood in front of the window and looked out at the view.

His figure was slim, and his skin was extremely fair. He looked very gentle and did not have the pressure of a powerhouse. He was dressed in luxurious clothes from head to toe and was emanating with the feeling of wealth.

This man was the current head of the Limitless Financial Group, Sorokin. He was one of the richest men in the galaxy.

A secretary stood beside Sorokin and said softly, "Your Excellency Sorokin, we have arrived."

"Hmm..." Sorokin replied. "Follow our schedule and head to the Black Star Army headquarters. Get our Shattered Star Ring branch to show me information about their performance over the past five years."

"Understood."

The Limitless Financial Group had property everywhere, and the Shattered Star Ring was no exception. But because of the poor public security of this region, the Limitless Financial Group did not place much emphasis on the Shattered Star Ring, and their operations were not large there.

If not for the fact that he had accepted the proposition of his three Beyond Grade A shareholders, Sorokin would not have established a large scale operation over there.

Although his current goal was to make trouble for Black Star, they were not direct enemies in business competition. Sorokin was also interested in meeting Black Star.

The way he saw it, Black Star should be happy to meet a wealthy individual like him. Although one of his subsidiary organizations had been wiped out by Black Star, his identity was not revealed, and Black Star should not know that he was the mastermind behind the matter.

As such, this would be their first encounter in Black Star's eyes.

With Black Star being kept in the dark, he would have a slight advantage.

He could also make use of this opportunity to come into contact with the Black Star Army's immortals and complete his previous goal.

Just as Sorokin was in thought, the hatch to the command room opened, and a woman walked in. She was dressed in the manager attire of the financial group.

This woman came to Sorokin's side and lowered her head slightly.

"Father, what are your instructions?"

She was Lovell, Sorokin's daughter.

Sorokin had many children, and they took on various positions in the financial group.

Turning to look at her, Sorokin flipped open his communicator and sent an invitation to her.

"Take this Tyrant's Party invitation and go to Heber. Meet him on my behalf."

Lovell was startled and asked, "Didn't you want to invest in the Black Star Army?"

"I will only make a decision after meeting Black Star. Before that, we cannot let go of any other investment opportunities," Sorokin replied.

His deal with the three shareholders was a secret. Apart from himself, everyone in the financial group thought that he was making a trip to the Shattered Star Ring for an ordinary investment.

Although he was planning to use money to compete with the Black Star Army, he needed to use the money wisely. While money would allow him to snatch a larger portion of the market, he did not like suffering losses.

Sorokin wanted both the deal with his shareholders and the opportunity to invest in the Flickering World!

As long as he invested in the right target, things would go smoothly for him.

He wanted to compete with Black Star head on but also not anger the dynasty. Thus, there was a suitable investment partner in the Shattered Star Ring.

After all, the Black Star Army was not the only organization that had the right to begin construction in the Flickering World.

Chapter 921: Level 300

Less than five minutes after the players went offline, various reports were sent from all the Black Star Army bases to Han Xiao. This was not the first time such a situation had occurred for the various officers, and although there were still some who found the matter strange, there was not a huge commotion.

To the outsiders, the disappearance of the players did not have any pattern, and only Han Xiao, who also had the player interface, could accurately grasp the time.

Version 3.0 was the true uprising of the Black Star Army in terms of manpower, strength, and status. Before the end of Version 2.0, the Black Star Army only had twenty-three bases, a few thousand battleships, and almost two hundred million Enas in savings. But now, their scale was at least a thousand times larger!

This was sufficient to prove just how great the benefits he had during the current version. He had managed to grasp all the opportunities that presented themselves to him. Advancing into the Beyond Grade A was like a carp leaping through the dragon gate.

With the current scale of the Black Star Army, although the players going offline would affect the employment missions of the army, it would not stop the ordinary operations of the army from operating.

"The version update this time will take twenty-three years, and the Flickering World will be in the fourth phase of development by then..."

Han Xiao leaned back on his chair.

To a civilization, a few decades was a short amount of time, just one or two generations. Without any outside interference, this amount of time was not enough to cause a huge change.

When all their questions could be answered and they no longer needed to fumble around in the dark for research, the Black Spirit Race would definitely be able to go from a native civilization to a galactic civilization in a short few decades for sure.

Intervening in the development of low-grade civilizations went against the Treaty of Cosmic Civilizations. On the surface, this was to restrict the development of the low-grade civilizations, but in truth, it was to reduce the conflict between galactic civilizations.

However, it was still the same logic. Regardless of how good a rule was, the rules could be bent depending on the individual bending it. With Han Xiao's current status, as long as he did not go too far, no one would care about such a small thing. Furthermore, the Black Spirit Race was a race that worshipped him, so no one would attack him because of this matter. As long as he had his own territory, no one would bother him about such matters.

Han Xiao then took out his communicator and called the dynasty.

"Your Excellency Black Star, do you need something?"

"Of course. If not, why would I bother calling you/" Han Xiao then went straight to the point. "How much longer will it take for the first exploration phase to end? You said that it would be finished very soon two years ago, and the star maps of the three Star Clusters have already been perfected. When will the upper echelons of the dynasty announce the completion of the first phase?"

"I am not too sure about the exact time, but it should be this year at the latest."

"Inform me if you have any news."

"Don't worry, chief commander Tarrokov will definitely inform you beforehand."

Right at this moment, the other party paused for a while, and his voice became solemn.

"Right, I also have something to tell you. The Blood Gold Organization ignored the dynasty's warning and didn't stop robbing the Evolutionary Totem. Our allies are grumbling because of this matter."

Han Xiao was surprised and said, "It seems like they've found a backer."

"Er, it is more accurate to say that a backer found them. The Federation of Light provided them with protection and got them to hide in the Abyss of Stars. They can then manage their subordinates remotely and continue accepting employment missions."

Federation of Light? Indeed, they can't help but target the Evolutionary Totem. Han Xiao's eyes narrowed. The interference of a Universal Civilization was not out of his expectations. The Federation of Light would never allow the dynasty to monopolize an item of such strategic importance.

The Federation of Light's plan was still unknown, and Han Xiao believed that the Federation of Light would not stop at conducting robberies. Such a small amount was not enough to satisfy their needs, and there must be a bigger scheme behind it all. They would most likely attempt to force the dynasty to open the rights to sell the Evolutionary Totem.

In this regard, the Federation of Light did not have any conflicts with him. Han Xiao also wished to expand his operations.

However, the method to craft the totems had been grasped by many organizations, and the other party might also attempt to seize his Evolution Cube. Still, the probability of this happening was small.

The memory of the Arcane Church failing miserably was still fresh, and now that the technological skill for the totem had been exposed, the dynasty would definitely place a larger importance on the Evolution Cube. If it was not necessary, no one would risk starting a war with the dynasty to snatch the Evolution Cube. The losses would exceed the gains. But despite all this, he still had to keep his guard up.

"What is the reaction of the dynasty?"

"The upper echelons guessed that something like this would happen and made plenty of preparations in secret. Although the dynasty will help you to endure most of the pressure, you will still face some risks yourself. The upper echelons recommend you stay in the dynasty's territory and operate through your machines. Even if the Federation of Light has the Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, they won't dare teleport into the dynasty's territory."

"I would be safer indeed, but I cannot stay in the Central Galaxy forever. That would be no different from being imprisoned." Han Xiao sighed helplessly.

As long as he did not hand over the Evolution Cube, he would always have to face such a dilemma. Profit would always come with risk, and if he wanted to settle this point thoroughly, he needed to let the entire universe recognize that the Evolution Cube belonged to him. His own strength was a factor, and the dynasty opening the rights to sell the totem was another factor.

Sigh, the Federation of Light is forcing me to be their spokesman...

"Thank you for your reminder. I will consider the matter." Han Xiao shook his head and hung up.

After sitting down for a while more, he then went to the training room and opened up his interface.

With the players offline, the experience which he had stored up will be the basis for him to increase his strength. Han Xiao had accumulated a large amount of experience over the past two years, and it was enough for him to reach level three hundred.

Since he was not able to influence the dynasty, all he could do was increase his strength.

Han Xiao let out a deep breath and channeled his experience to leveling up.

[Lord Mechanic] leveled up to Lv.21.

+360 Energy, +5 STR, +5DEX, +12 END, +15 INT.

You have received 12 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

Lord Mechanic] leveled up to Lv.40 (max).

+360 Energy, +5 STR, +5DEX, +12 END, +15 INT.

You have received 12 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

Han Xiao's level went from 280 to 300, and his body surged with energy.

At his current level, the amount of experience needed to level up would only snowball. Without a way to accumulate experience, choosing to level up further was not the best option.

Han Xiao placed all his Free Attribute Points into Intelligence to increase his damage and looked at the notifications on the interface.

You have reached the upper limit of your Main Class. You have triggered Class Advancement Mission: [Erudite]

[Erudite]: Have 30 Class Knowledges reaching Lv.5 with at least 3 being Ultimate Knowledges. The strength of a Mechanic comes from their knowledge, and a Mechanic can only reach higher heights with a stable foundation.

You have reached Lv.300. You have triggered a Promotion Mission: [Abundant Energy]!

[Abundant Energy]: Reach Lv.19 in your energy level. Energy will always be required to support strength.

"These two missions don't seem too bad." Han Xiao raised his brows.

Compared to the challenge-type missions, Han Xiao preferred the missions that had a requirement on his attributes. He was already planning to increase his Class Knowledge, and the [Erudite] mission came at the right time.

[Abundant Energy] required his energy level to be at Lv.19, which was 120,000 energy points. Han Xiao had always been training [Radiation Absorption], and together with his gains from leveling up twenty times, his energy level had just passed 100,000 points and had reached Lv.18. He was only about 20,000 points away from the requirement.

The energy points of most Beyond Grade As were above 100,000, so Han Xiao's energy level was relatively low. If not for his special energy regeneration tactic, his energy level would definitely be lower.

Since he could not level up, he needed plenty of energy training manuals to fill this gap. Although the requirement was harsh, energy was an important attribute, and there would be no disadvantage for him to complete this mission.

However, despite thinking that way, Han Xiao still opened the Random Reward page.

During this period of time, Han Xiao had gotten his mechanical army to perform plenty of missions on the outside and accumulated a few Random Reward opportunities. There were more than twenty chances for him to use.

"I hope that a Mission Completion Card will come out..." Han Xiao prayed.

Even Feidin's luck was not useful to help him this time. Luck would help him to increase the chance of a high value item appearing, but the Mission Completion Card was considered a worthless item to even the players, and high Luck would reduce his chance of drawing it.

Without any hesitation, Han Xiao immediately started drawing rewards.

After finishing all his Random Reward chances, over half were common items. Apart from that, there were three Potential Points, three low grade skills, one foundation talent, one empty Character Summon Card, one ability enhancement card, one double experience card... and two Mission Completion Cards.

He only got two of them in over twenty draws. Han Xiao truly did not know if this was his good or bad luck.

The two Mission Completion Cards would be able to allow him to complete the missions immediately, but after thinking for a while, Han Xiao did not plan on using the Mission Completion Cards now as he felt that it was not worth it.

"This thing is too damn difficult to get. Since these two missions aren't that difficult, I should save these Mission Completion Cards for the future," Han Xiao mumbled to himself.

[Erudite] was not difficult at all, and he had already planned to increase the level of his knowledge. Although the requirements for [Abundant Energy] was harsh, he only needed to put in some effort to complete it.

He could still afford to wait for a short while and kept the two Mission Completion Cards for a rainy day. It would truly be a loss if he wasted these two 'precious' Mission Completion Cards.

Han Xiao then looked through his attributes. Because he did not finish his Promotion and Class Advancement missions, his Attribute Points and Potential Points had only increased slightly.

Chapter 922: Meeting

Han Xiao opened his Profession tree for a look. The current maxed Lv.5 knowledge did not reach the required thirty to give him the title of [Erudite], but he was close to it, just requiring him to raise a few lower-tiered knowledges. The problem was having an Ultimate Knowledge of each of the three branches maxed out.

Another important source for potential points would be to reach max level for his skills, but the upgrade cost would increase exponentially with the character level and sum of all skill levels. For a non-related branch Ultimate Knowledge, it would require roughly 120 Potential Points to upgrade from Lv.0 to Lv.5.

It was also impractical for Han Xiao to suppress his level. Even with all the experience he had saved up currently, it would not be enough to bring his Ultimate Knowledge to max level.

After thinking for a while, he decided to instead upgrade [Eternal Power Source], [Virtual Creator], and another from the Control Branch to the max level, as these three Ultimate Knowledges did not suffer from any experience penalties.

He directly opened the skills tab and invested some experience to upgrade his blueprint skills. After reaching the required amount of Potential Points, he immediately used them up, maxing out [Virtual Creator] and [Eternal Power Source].

His last required Ultimate Knowledge of the Control Branch had not been learned. While he had sufficient Contribution Points, in order to maintain the effect of his political assets, he needed to preserve at least six thousand points, keeping his relationship with the dynasty at [Reverence]. Thus, he could only wait until he reached twelve thousand Contribution Points to exchange for the Ultimate Knowledge. He was still lacking around three or four thousand.

After completing his operation of upgrading and learning skills, his reserve experience shrank greatly.

During Version 2.0, Han Xiao's stored experience was only enough for him to increase from Level 170 to 207. In Version 3.0, due to the larger number of Black Star Army faction players, which allowed him to sell more of his products and grant higher rewards for missions, Han Xiao's current experience reserve far outstripped Version 2.0.

But no matter how much he had, it was still finite. The cost of upgrading at this stage was much greater than that of the lower level, and he also needed to reserve a certain amount of experience to gamble on blueprints and improve strength training.

Han Xiao then entered the quantum network, ordering Phillip to purchase Energy Training Techniques in large quantities. With the current finances of the Army, this was a small matter and did not require him to worry about it himself.

Following this, Han Xiao collected his gains in the random reward. The two low-level skills drawn were relatively ineffective, but the foundation talent was not bad. It was called [Brain Enhancement], and the effect was an increased four percent Intelligence. At his current level, it would grant hundreds of Intelligence points, and since Intelligence was the core attribute for a Mechanic, there was some value in it.

Other than this, the more useful ones included a blank Character Summon Card as well as an ability enhancement card.

He had drawn one ability enhancement card long ago, and it had been sitting in his interface without him touching it. With this new card, he now had two.

Han Xiao scanned his skill bar as he muttered, "What should I enhance?"

Profession skills would not be able to trigger any skill mutations and could only be strengthened based on its basic values. At present, Han Xiao's combat ability was quite well rounded, so it seemed like he could use it to strengthen any skill.

After thinking for a while, he decided to use it for the skill [Gene Liberation]. This explosive ability was still useful, and strengthening it would be no loss.

Activating Ability Enhancement Card, target: [Gene Liberation Lv.10], undergoing enhancement...

Enhancement completed. [Gene Liberation Lv10]'s effect has been upgraded.

There was no mutation, but Han Xiao was not surprised. [Gene Liberation] was already the mutated form of [Flaming Will], and in the past, there was a crazy guy who tried continuously enhancing only one skill, and he found out that the use of the enhancement card greatly dropped with each consecutive try. The success rate for the first time was twenty percent, followed by five percent, and a third time would be one percent.

The interface showed that [Gene Liberation]'s minimum damage bonus had increased from 220% to 240%, while the maximum increased from 480% to 520%. The continuous effect was upgraded from 2 to 2.4 seconds, while the cooldown reduced from seven minutes to six minutes and twenty seconds. The passive trigger was upped from 20% to 28%. Overall, it was an acceptable strengthening.

There was still one Ability Enhancement Card left over. After looking at it for a long time, Han Xiao decided that he had no other abilities worth increasing now and decided to leave it.

Players could also draw Ability Enhancement Cards, and the enhancement effect applied the same way. The more used, the higher the chance of transforming qualitatively. If one could increase the -90% Luck for the Luck Curse to -100%...

All card items such as the Character Summon Card or Ability Enhancement cards were character bound and could not be traded. Thus, the temporary character cards obtained through his juice extraction would be so sought after. If it was not for that, Han Xiao would have assigned a mission long ago to amass Character Summon Cards.

After finishing what he needed to do, Han Xiao closed the interface and left the training room. On the way, he took out his communicator and contacted Sylvia.

"How goes the preparation for the party?"

"The official time for the party has been set to be in a month, and it's already arranged. By the way, I was paying attention to the trends of Bloodshed Land, and it seems like the Tyrant's Party held this year has been adjusted to the same time as ours."

Han Xiao let out a peal of laughter. "Little Ty-Ty is not very happy, I see."

"If I were the Tyrant, I would be angry too." Sylvia did not reply very nicely to him.

"There's no rule saying that only he can hold a party. After all, we're not good friends, so why would I care about what he thinks?" Han Xiao stroked his chin.

Sylvia lightly snorted and no longer bothered judging him. She instead continued speaking. "The number of Evolutionary Totem collaborators has increased, and there are more representatives attending this party, many of whom hail from different star fields. There are 11 Star Cluster civilization representatives and 413 Star System civilization representatives, which includes the Beyond Grade A allies that are friends with you."

"Not bad, the business scope widened." Han Xiao nodded.

Had the dynasty completely opened up his Evolutionary Totem trade, there would have been god knew how many times more organizations approaching him.

"Remember to provide good hospitality for the guests. Don't neglect them."

After casually leaving some instructions, Han Xiao hung up.

The follow-up plan needed to be started after the dynasty had divided the territories, so he could only make preparations for the time being.

A month passed by in a flash, and the day for the Black Star's Party came as scheduled.

There were already precedents to this party, so the officers like Sylvia were familiar with the process as well as the routes their guests used to travel over.

Han Xiao also had to meet with the VIPs in person before the actual party and invited the local representatives of the Shattered Star Ring to gather.

"Haha, Black Star, long time no see."

The representative of the Purple Crystal Civilization was the first to arrive and walked in laughing heartily. Han Xiao also smiled, walking forward to give him a hug.

The two of them were old friends. During the time when Han Xiao was still a Calamity Grade, he had borrowed the opportunity of the secret war to develop himself. While he was now allied with the Crimson Dynasty, he had always maintained a good relationship with the Purple Crystal Civilization.

The Purple Crystal Civilization maintained its neutrality and did not express their enthusiasm for the dynasty. Only because of Han Xiao's request were they able to purchase the Evolutionary Totem. Thus, they were the only non-dynasty-ally customer of Han Xiao. The Purple Crystal Civilization also attached great importance to their Beyond Grade A supporting them, so both sides were harmonious.

Both of them sat down and started to chat. Ralph could not help reminiscing.

"Just now, when I was outside, I saw a lot of other representatives in the Star Field. In just a few years, your organization has changed so drastically."

"There was some luck involved." Han Xiao smiled.

Ralph shook his head as though sighing.

A few years ago, the Black Star Army had been but a small armed organization that cooperated with the Purple Crystal Civilization. Over a few years, they had transformed into a behemoth that hundreds of civilizations now valued.

Even their Purple Crystal Civilization did not have such influence.

Looking at the small shrimp that once needed their support become a behemoth today, Ralph's mood was a bit complicated.

After chatting for a while longer, the other representatives of the six Star Cluster level Civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring arrived. Now, there was no star cluster civilization that dared not give Han Xiao face. Even the neighboring Klent Kingdom also sent people to participate this time.

Seeing his old opponent, Ralph's brows raised, and he joked, "Hey, why did the Klent Kingdom come too? I thought the Tyrant's Party is being held around this time this year. Aren't you afraid Heber will be unhappy?"

"Humph, there are other colleagues of mine that will go to the Tyrant's side." The Klent representative snorted.

The grudges of the secret war had not disappeared, but because of their interests, Klent could only wrinkle their noses and come to please Han Xiao. While they both were allies of the dynasty, if Black Star did not wish to sell the Evolutionary Totem to Klent, he could choose not to do so.

These seven Star Cluster level civilizations controlled the entire Shattered Star Ring, and Han Xiao had various business dealings with them. His network and influence could even be considered stronger than Heber's, as people who attended Heber's party did so to give him face; however, those who attended Han Xiao's party all were connected by benefits, which meant a deeper level of relationship.

Just as Han Xiao was chatting with them, his communicator vibrated. It was a message from Sylvia.

"Teacher, Sorokin has arrived."

Han Xiao told Sylvia to observe Sorokin. His eyes flashed, and he flashed a smile toward the other representatives.

"Gentlemen, excuse me for a moment."

Sorokin's fleet docked at the pier, attracting a lot of attention.

The Limitless Financial Group's name had been heard by almost all the representatives of these civilizations, but after a few glances, they withdrew their gazes.

The Black Star Army was also a Beyond Grade A force and was allied to the dynasty. It was not surprising that the Limitless Financial Group had also arrived.

Sorokin got off the spaceship and saw their behavior. His eyes narrowed slightly, and he had a clearer understanding of the power of the Black Star Army.

While the partners of the army might not compare to those of the Limitless Financial Group, they still had a lot of say in the Shattered Star Ring.

This moment, Feidin, who was waiting by the side, came up with a smile.

"I'm a Black Star Guard, Feidin. I'm here to welcome the distinguished guests from the Limitless Financial Group to the Black Star Army. Your Excellency Sorokin, Black Star is waiting to meet with you."

Hearing this, Sorokin withdrew his gaze and focused on Feidin. His breath caught suddenly, as confusion flashed across his eyes. He asked, "Are you... male or female?"

"I guess you could say both." Feidin warmly smiled and added, "But mostly male."

"Oh... I understand." Sorokin coughed lightly. "Please lead the way. I'm also looking forward to seeing Black Star."

The group left the dock and proceeded to another reception room.

Along the way, Sorokin glanced left and right, observing the situation of the Black Star Army, and could not help but say, "I heard that the Black Star Army has a unique Immortals troop. I wanted to see them during my trip here, but it seems like none of them are here?"

Feidin smiled. "Oh, you really came at the wrong time. They are not present."

"... Oh, so that's the case." Sorokin's mouth twitched.

A month ago, not long after he reached the Shattered Star Ring, he received news from his side that all the Immortals in his financial group had disappeared. Sorokin thought that it was a standalone case, but it seemed that Black Star Army's group had also disappeared.

Indeed, no matter how far it is, the Immortals seemed to be linked...

Sorokin had always been observing the players, but he was unable to tell the circumstances behind their disappearances and could only admit that he was unlucky.

His idea of coming into contact with the Immortals here was wasted.

Arriving in the reception room, Sorokin sat for a while before the door opened, and Han Xiao walked over.

"How do you do? I'm Sorokin from the Limitless Financial Group. I'm honored to meet with the man who captured EsGod." Sorokin smiled slightly, displaying nothing out of the ordinary.

"It is also my honor to meet you. Please, take a seat." Han Xiao shook hands with him as well.

They sat down, and Sorokin smiled as he spoke.

"While I'm based in the distant Sea of Star Spirits, I've often heard about the deeds of Black Star. A long time ago, I was already thinking of cooperating. There is a business opportunity, so I came with sincerity and hope that our first contact today would be a good start for the future cooperation between the two parties."

"... I hope the same."

Han Xiao raised his brows, with a smile that was unlike a smile on his face.

First time in contact? You piece of sh*t. If not for the fact that I know you so well, I would really think that you're such a sincere person...

In his previous life, the players did not have much information on Sorokin. In the eyes of the players, he was a Beyond Grade A without much sense of existence. He had no outstanding records at the Beyond Grade A.

Han Xiao had recently asked his friends in the Beyond Grade A circles and found out that Sorokin had never fought with any of his peers before. They mentioned that his combat power was not strong, and the 'Beyond Grade A' was used more as an identity to facilitate business negotiations.

Combining all the various accounts, Sorokin seemed to be a freak that deviated from all the normal Beyond Grade A evaluations. Compared to the others, his business attributes were far stronger.

However, those who could become Beyond Grade A would have experienced various difficulties and obstacles. Without strong mental will, it was impossible to get to Beyond Grade A. Han Xiao felt that Sorokin might not be as simple as he seemed on the surface.

Because there was limited information, he could only understand the opponent's personality through personal contact.

Han Xiao's mind was racing.

It'll be best to find a method to poke him and force out all the combat information...

Chapter 923: Old Fox and Lobbyists

Even as he thought about Sorokin's information, Han Xiao's expression was normal, and he commented on Sorokin's words with a voice full of interest.

"How can we cooperate?"

As he spoke, Sorokin smiled. "The Flickering World is a rare business opportunity. I heard that the Crimson Dynasty will divide the territory of its allies that participated in the exploration. When the new Star Field opens in the future, the Flickering World will be integrated into the universe, which will usher in a period of explosive development. The dynasty's allies who sit on these sites will be the biggest winners, so we hope to invest heavily in the Black Star Army and build the site ahead of time with you.

"The Limitless Financial Group invests in the entire universe and does not miss any business opportunities. Presumably, you know of our financial resources. Our help will make the construction more efficient."

"That's right. The market value of the Limitless Financial Group... is indeed frightening. I do not doubt your capabilities." Han Xiao nodded.

Many subsidiaries of the Limitless Financial Group had been listed on the Interstellar Stock Market in different regions. Their market value was transparent and open, easily checked, and the amount of Enas they possessed made people who were unaware of it think that Enas were some inferior currency.

Resources were often gathered like this in the hands of a few. In the galactic age, the gap between the rich and poor was like the difference between a beast on a planet surface compared with a galactic resident.

The development of the territory in the Flickering World would inevitably be supported by various financial groups. This was also a means of cost saving and cooperation. The Crimson Dynasty tacitly agreed that the allies could sign contracts with financial groups to develop the territory together.

It sounded as though there was no problem, but this guy, Sorokin... Han Xiao did not show any changes in facial expression while evaluating the man before him.

Seeing that Black Star did not show any confirmation, Sorokin narrowed his eyes and continued speaking. "The Black Star Army is now a huge business and dominates the Shattered Star Ring. In terms of financial resources, it does not lose out to the first-tier financial groups due to its deep background and connections. With an extensive network, along with support from the dynasty, it will definitely attract countless galactic residents to invest. It is not difficult to multiple its market value."

"Your meaning is?" Han Xiao raised a brow.

Sorokin smiled. "Our Limitless Financial Group has experience in this area. If the Black Star Army agrees, we are happy to help you..."

"We can talk about this in the future." Han Xiao cut in. This idea was the real essence of growing leeks, but it came with its own disadvantages, and he temporarily did not wish to dabble in this.

Hearing this, Sorokin also put down this topic. He asked, "Then, what does Your Excellency Black Star think of my proposal?"

Han Xiao thought about it before asking, "It's not just myself that has a territory in the Flickering World. Based on normal circumstances, the financial groups will only move when the territory gets divided, so why are you guys approaching me for cooperation when everyone still has not chosen?"

"Haha, I have inside information because I have contacts within the Crimson Dynasty. Even without these connections, thanks to your contributions in the battle of Planet Lighthouse and the Fall of EsGod, plus the Evolution Cube that is in your hands, the territory given to you by the dynasty will be the best. In this case, why should I hesitate?"

Sorokin had a big smile on his face.

There were no falsehoods in his words. Even if he had no relationship with the dynasty, the best choice would still be the Black Star Army. With Han Xiao's current record and importance, everyone knew that the Black Star Army would be given the largest and best piece of meat.

A pity...

"Is that so?" Han Xiao deeply looked at Sorokin.

This guy's words were sincere and aligned with their interests. He seemed like he sincerely wished to work with him...

However, because of Sorokin's involvement in the Gulal civil war, Han Xiao was already alert to him. He hesitated a while before asking, "If I agree to work with you, are you prepared to sign the contract now?"

"That's not the case." Sorokin shook his head and chuckled. "I'm just here to reach a preliminary arrangement. The specific details can only be formed after the site is confirmed. Of course, the main reason I came over was because you insisted on me coming to attend Black Star's Party. Such big business needs me to be here in person, and I also admire what you've done so far."

To say such flattering words so easily, there's no air of a Beyond Grade A about him, Han Xiao thought.

At this moment, Han Xiao thought of something and said, "Ok. Then I have no objections."

"Then, I wish our cooperation a success." Sorokin laughed.

Han Xiao did not laugh and changed the topic. "That's right. I heard that the Limitless Financial Group has many Beyond Grade A shareholders, and there are even Ancient Ones among them, such as the Mechanic Emperor Manison and even allies from the dynasty."

"That's right."

"The Limitless Financial Group trades its shareholder position for resources and protection, am I right?"

"Yes."

"Oh, since you wish to cooperate, a verbal promise is unsuitable. In the future, since the Flickering World still has a long time ahead for development, if I become a shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group, then I can naturally cooperate fully with the financial group... I think that my name, Black Star, still has some weight in the universe. Your Excellency Sorokin, do you think that I have the qualifications for a shareholder position with my current status and resources?"

Through the Gulal civil war, Han Xiao had discovered the Limitless Financial Group's attempt to steal his 'food', so he wished to break into the Limitless Financial Group and find out who was trying to snatch his rice bowl.

"This..." Sorokin had an awkward expression.

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed, and he purposely deepened his voice. "Oh? It seems you think that I don't have the qualifications."

"Of course not." Sorokin shook his head, but he was laughing coldly to himself.

I'm afraid you don't have the qualifications.

To want a shareholder position the first time we meet, your appetite is really big. It seems like your battle records have made you proud and reckless...

While Sorokin thought this, he displayed a helpless expression on his face.

"Your Excellency Black Star, you have the qualifications, but with the size of the Limitless Financial group, the shareholder position is not given out easily. Even if I'm willing, the others may not be willing, and there's only one shareholder for each of the three Universal Civilizations. The dynasty already has someone occupying a seat... You understand what I mean."

"Ah, so it's like that." Han Xiao nodded. Another method for the three Universal Civilizations to keep each other in check.

This reason seemed to be easy to use, with no way to figure out their thoughts.

"If that's the case, then let's not talk about such things for now. No matter what, to be able to meet another Beyond Grade A today, I'm really happy." Han Xiao glanced at Sorokin. "Are you interested in a spar?"

"I'll give it a miss. I'm not good at combat." Sorokin waved his hands while laughing.

"Haha, come on, a Beyond Grade A saying that they are not good at combat? You must be joking."

"I might be a Beyond Grade A, but I don't like to fight and have not exchanged blows with anyone for a long time. My skills have long regressed, and besides, with Your Excellency Black Star's renown in the universe, I admit that I will not be your opponent."

Saying this, Sorokin stood up and smiled. "If I'm not wrong, you still need to meet others, right? I've also just arrived and need to arrange my subordinates. Let's stop here for the day. I'll come and visit again tomorrow and chat more. How about that?"

"Alright." Hearing this, Han Xiao could only nod. The guest had come from afar, so he could not forcibly make Sorokin stay.

Sorokin smiled, and after exchanging communicator numbers, he left the room.

After he left, Han Xiao frowned.

"This guy has a seamless defense. If he doesn't agree to spar, then I'll need to think of another idea..."

Sorokin was also a person of influence, and he came all the way to discuss a possibility of cooperation, so Han Xiao could not show any hatred. He did not know the intentions of the other party, and if he ended up antagonizing them, that would be bad.

While Sorokin seemed very sincere on the surface, Han Xiao felt that the other party did not really want to work with him.

Recalling their conversation previously, Han Xiao found it difficult to read Sorokin's personality, as though he was wearing a mask the whole time.

"I don't even know what he's thinking..." Han Xiao rubbed his temples, helplessly sighing.

Conversing with such people was the most taxing.

...

This year, the Tyrant's Party and Black Star's Party were held at the same time. The civilizations of Shattered Star Ring could not afford to snub either one, so they also sent messengers to follow the habits of previous years to attend the Tyrant's Party.

On the top floor of the Bloodshed Land's palace, Heber stood in front of a huge window. Outside the window was a black and gray fortress, as well as stars that spanned across the entire universe. His gaze was fixed toward the residences of the emissaries.

In recent years, these messengers would take advantage of the time before the party to network with the others, but now, there was almost no movement from these emissaries. Most of them stayed within their rooms, and the hall appeared cold and deserted, like stagnant water.

Because Black Star's Party was livelier, the civilizations of the Shattered Star Ring all regarded Black Star's Party as the main stage of communication, and the Tyrant's Party was a secondary occasion. Matters to be discussed could be done on one side, and they did not need to move on the other.

Right now, these people participated in Tyrant's Party more as a way to show their face, rather than as a grand and lively occasion.

"Humph, Black Star."

Heber's expression was tense, and the fist behind him was clenched tight.

At this point, his Chief Staff Officer Jorde walked in. Walking behind Heber, he whispered, "Your Excellency Heber, the emissary from the Limitless Financial Group has arrived. She's waiting outside."

"Let her in." Heber did not even turn back.

A moment later, Lovell walked into the room. Gazing at the huge figure in front of the window, a wave of pressure assaulted her.

She calmed her mind and whispered, "I greet Your Excellency Heber."

She was not even at the Calamity Grade and could not maintain the bearing her father Sorokin had in front of Han Xiao.

"I heard the Limitless Financial Group wants to work with us." Heber indifferently glanced at Lovell.

"That's right. It's regarding the Flickering World. We..."

"You wish to be an investor, right? Such small matters need not be discussed with me. You may look for the respective officer." Heber withdrew his gaze, uninterested.

Lovell gritted her teeth before taking out a letter. "His Excellency Sorokin tasked me with delivering this to you."

"Letter?" Heber's brows furrowed.

In this age where electronic communication was so convenient and efficient, a handwritten letter only meant that there was a need for secrecy. Heber was suspicious; he did not have any dealings with Sorokin, so why would the latter send him a letter? What did he mean? It was definitely not going to be a love letter.

Heber then turned to face Lovell, and with a gesture, the letter landed in his hands. The moment he opened it, his pupils shrank, and his expression became solemn.

"No wonder..."

Heber waved his hands, and the letter turned to ash before disintegrating into atoms. He gazed at Jorde. "Leave for now."

Jorde was surprised, but he bowed and left, closing the door on his way out.

With only two of them in the room, a ray of light flashed past Heber's eyes, and energy rushed out, filling the room and isolating any external detection.

"You guys wish for me to deal with the Black Star Army?"

"That's right." Lovell nodded.

"Humph, ridiculous!" Heber coldly replied. "While I have issues with Black Star, we're still allies of the dynasty, and I can't do anything about him. You've come to the wrong person."

Lovell took a deep breath. Recalling what Sorokin had taught her, she said, "Black Star has only been around for twenty years, but how many years have you already been in the Shattered Star Ring? Black Star came later, but his business is flourishing, and his influence has surpassed yours. Your Excellency, are you willing to watch this continue?"

Heber's expression was indifferent, but he did not refute.

"As for your ally, the Crimson Dynasty, they have always been biased toward the Black Star Army. Have you thought about why that's so..."

Heber cut in. "He has the Evolution Cube, and I don't have anything. It's that simple."

"Yes!" Lovell's voice rose a notch. "That's the crux!"

"Humph, so you want me to help you take his Evolution Cube?" Sarcasm laced Heber's words.

"Of course not. We just need to come out with a way to make him lose the Evolution Cube. There's a difference between the two."

"Oh? What is that?"

"It's almost impossible to rob, and the federation as well as the church will not rashly act. So, what we want is for Black Star to willingly give up his Evolution Cube."

Heber almost burst into laughter. "Pass the Evolution Cube to an outsider? Do you think Black Star is a fool? I understand that b*stard Black Star. It's easier for your Limitless Financial Group to go bankrupt tomorrow than for him to pass over his Evolution Cube."

"No, I did not mean it that way. What if... we could make Black Star surrender the Evolution Cube to the dynasty?" Lovell replied.

Heber narrowed his eyes, seemingly interested.

"Go on."

Chapter 924: True Colors

"The value of the Evolution Cube need not be emphasized. Today, this Universal Treasure coveted by all organizations is in the hands of Black Star, and its risk to the dynasty is huge. However, the Universal Civilizations will not force their Beyond Grade A allies to hand over their Universal Treasures, so while they acquiesce to Black Star's ownership of the Evolution Cube, it does not mean that the dynasty will be at ease."

Heber nodded. "Indeed. Continue."

"Only when the Evolution Cube is held in the hands of the dynasty can the risk be eliminated. Although he came out victorious in the battle of Planet Lighthouse, it has also sounded an alarm within the dynasty. Rather than simply believing in Black Star's strength, it's always better to prevent such things from happening. The Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device of the Federation of Light will forever remain a threat. Think of what will happen if a group of Beyond Grade As suddenly raid the Black Star Army headquarters."

"If the federation could do it, they would have done so long ago." Heber remained unmoved.

"That's right. If you take into account various factors, the Federation of Light will not take such a risk, so it takes a roundabout approach to put pressure on the dynasty and Black Star... But if all means fail, then the risk will only get higher."

Heber neither agreed nor disagreed, only indifferently replying, "Even if there are external threats, Urranrell still attaches importance to Black Star. The dynasty will not force him, so the success rate of your plan can be ignored. I advise you to give up as soon as possible."

"We have to try," Lovell insisted. "Black Star is close to the faction of the Ruler and has gained a lot of protection, but you also know that there are many factions inside the dynasty. Ever since the Evolutionary Totem appeared, there have been more cries to make Black Star turn in the Evolution Cube. Black Star's refusal to settle in with the cube on the mother star also convinced more factions."

Heber frowned. "You seem to know a lot."

Hearing this, Lovell mysteriously smiled. "That's because... I'm not just representing the federation and church by coming this time."

"Hahaha..." Heber burst into laughter, and his tone was playful. "Your appetite is so big, to think you want to gobble up all three players. No wonder. I was doubting what you said, because if Black Star hands over the Evolution Cube, then the last chance for the federation and the church would also disappear. Turns out it's actually like this..."

Lovell smiled without answering, but inside, she secretly praised Sorokin's courage.

While Sorokin appeared to agree with the deal between the federation and the church, he secretly contacted a few of the factions within the dynasty to change the plan to suppress the Black Star Army, saying that he would make the Black Star Army willingly pass the Evolution Cube over to them. The second deal made it obvious that the Limitless Financial Group's plan was to suppress Black Star.

Not only did it leave him with a way to retreat, it also allowed him to reap the most benefits. Sorokin was not someone who listened to orders quietly; he had himself to think about.

The scale the Limitless Financial Group had developed not just by profiteering from war. The battle at Planet Lighthouse had resulted in the market becoming volatile, which in turn affected the stocks of the Limitless Financial Group, causing them to eat quite a loss.

In order to prevent such a situation from happening again, Sorokin would rather become a pacifist, completely removing the possibility of the Evolution Cube provoking a war by cutting off any chance for the other two civilizations to obtain the cube, solving the conflict between the three Universal Civilizations.

If the Evolution Cube fell into the hands of the dynasty, it would eliminate any risk of turbulence in the universe.

Thus, on the surface, he made a deal with the federation and the church, but he was actually thinking from the view of a third party.

Lovell paused for a moment before speaking in a low voice. "The moment the dynasty obtains the Evolution Cube, they will also seize all the profits from the Evolutionary Totems. Black Star will thus be kicked out of the scene, and the dynasty can now increase the possibility of opening this purchase to the outside world so that they can pacify the growing pressure from the federation and the church. Since the latter two do not wish to take any risks if possible, completely severing their desires would be best."

"Sorokin... this guy is interesting." Heber narrowed his eyes. "So, after saying all that, the premise lies in Black Star surrendering the Evolution Cube. If it fails, these will all be empty words. What do you plan to do?"

Hearing this, Lovell was happy. Heber asking for the details meant that he was interested.

"Very simple, exert pressure on Black Star internally and externally so that he sees that there are greater benefits in handing over the cube rather than keeping it."

"Elaborate."

"In the battle of Planet Lighthouse, Black Star obtained huge battle records and shut the mouths of those that insisted he turn in the Evolution Cube, but the number of casualties in the battle for the dynasty were also high. As long as the dynasty continues to suffer losses due to the Evolutionary Totem, Black Star will encounter more pressure within the dynasty. Even Urranrell will not be able to suppress them all... but this part will be the work of the federation and the church, and I cannot disclose more."

"What about the external side?"

"We have to target Black Star Army, so we require your help."

"If you want me to betray the dynasty, then we can stop here."

Lovell smiled. "Rest assured, there is no harm done to you. Even if we do not particularly aim at the Black Star Army, the Bloodshed Land will still benefit from it."

"What should we do?"

"Simple, my Limitless Financial Group will first come out with the investments to support the Bloodshed Land and recapture those business markets that the Black Star Army has taken from you. This will suppress his business. While developing your site in the Flickering World, we will use our influence in the dynasty for you to obtain a better site.

"Since you also belong to the dynasty, it is nothing but legitimate commercial competition. Thus, the dynasty will not have any issues. The strength of my Limitless Financial Group is also clear to Your Excellency. With our capital injection, regardless of success or failure, the Bloodshed Land will not make any losses."

Hearing this, Heber closed his eyes and thought hard. After a few seconds, he reopened them as he lightly replied, "Ok. I agree."

Lovell breathed out in relief, her taut mental state relaxing. "In this entire deal, only Black Star will lose out, but for universal peace, he can only be wronged."

"Universal peace, huh..." Heber sneered to himself, but he did not show any expression as he said, "With the Federation of Light, Arcane Church, the Crimson Dynasty, and my Bloodshed Land, humph, the Limitless Financial Group is really making some big moves. This is akin to an anti-Black Star alliance."

"This is just business, and there are no personal grudges within." Lovell smiled without minding it. "I just hope that he will recognize this point. Besides, he will still receive compensation from the dynasty."

Heber inwardly curled his lips. While he did not like Black Star, knowing his character, the probability of him compromising was infinitely close to zero, and that guy's ability to resist pressure was terribly strong. Even if Lovell could upend everything, their plan still might not work.

However... his Bloodshed Land did not stand to lose out. Heber was willing to cooperate with the Limitless Financial Group to develop himself, unwilling to sit back and watch Han Xiao throw him further and further away.

The next day, in the Black Star Army headquarters, there were still a few days before the actual party. Thus, many guests were walking with each other and expanding their social networks, a lively scene.

Han Xiao visited Sorokin early in the morning and invited him to visit the headquarters of the Army. Sorokin readily accepted.

The two hung around the headquarters chatting, and Han Xiao once again made a request to spar but was rejected firmly. Han Xiao was a little helpless.

The other party just kept admitting defeat, without a single hint of a strong mindset.

Just as Han Xiao was hesitating, Sorokin suddenly seemed to think of something.

"I heard that Aesop is over here."

Han Xiao's brows rose. "You know that d*mned... cough, that old man?"

"In the past, when he was part of the Ancient Ones, I met him a few times. I also invited him to join the Limitless Financial Group but was rejected." Sorokin shook his head.

Aesop, that old man, was really a social butterfly. To think that people recognize him everywhere he goes... Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

"That's right. I also seem to have heard that you and Ames are a couple."

Han Xiao froze. "Now where did you hear that?"

"The rumor is being spread everywhere, and I just happened to chance across it." Sorokin sighed. "The union between two Beyond Grade As is just too rare. I don't even remember who the previous couple was."

"The head of the Limitless Financial Group actually has time to pay attention to gossip, huh?" Han Xiao helplessly shook his head.

"It's precisely because I'm the leader that I need to pay attention. Sometimes, business opportunities can be hidden within." Sorokin smiled.

Han Xiao thought a bit and decided to probe further. "If I'm not wrong, you seem to be the successor to the group and not the original owner of the financial group, right?"

"Yes."

"There are few records of you in the Universe, so I'm a little curious about your experiences before you became a Beyond Grade A."

"Haha, are you so curious about my childhood?" Sorokin laughed.

In the eyes of many Beyond Grade As, their lives before they reached their current realms were as good as their childhood years.

"I'm just curious." Han Xiao waved his hands.

"That was a long time ago. Be it training or combat, there's nothing really worth talking about." Sorokin shook his head and changed the topic. "I wonder, do you have any ambitions, Your Excellency?"

"Ambitions? Does universal peace count?" Han Xiao cracked a joke.

"What a coincidence, me too." Sorokin laughed.

As they continued to chat, Han Xiao split his consciousness and slipped into the quantum network, hacking into Aesop's communicator.

An old face surfaced in his field of vision within the quantum network, obviously frightened out of his wits.

"Black Star, I'm watching a show now. Why did you hack into my communicator‽"

"Old man, I have something to ask you. Do you know Sorokin?"

Aesop stopped before suspiciously saying, "I do. Why are you mentioning him?"

"He's beside me now, and I'm quite curious about this guy. What was he like when you met him in the past?"

Hearing this, Aesop fell into silence for a while before finally saying, "Sorokin... tsk, an old sly fox. You'll never know if the words coming out of his mouth are truth or lies. It's better for you to be cautious when dealing with him."

"Oh... then how's his battle strength?"

"I don't know, definitely stronger than me." Aesop spread his hands out.

"Isn't that as good as not saying anything?" Han Xiao was speechless.

"Alright, stop bothering me. Put my communicator back to normal. I want to continue watching my show."

Resigned, Han Xiao could only retreat out of the quantum network. Turning over to glance at Sorokin, he suddenly made up his mind, sending a quick punch over.

"Hmm?"

Sorokin's reaction was impressive, and he raised his hand to block the punch.

Peng!

There was not much force behind the punch, but a loud noise sounded, and a shock wave rippled out from the point of contact.

"... Your Excellency Black Star, what is the meaning of this?" Sorokin narrowed his eyes.

"You mentioned that your skills have regressed, but I didn't believe you, so I decided to test it out for myself." Han Xiao smiled, not hiding it at all.

Sorokin frowned, but that turned it into a smile as he shook his head. "As a Beyond Grade A, how could I not have basic reactions and awareness? It's just that if you were a Pugilist, I would not have been able to block this punch. Please don't scare me, Your Excellency Black Star. I'm really not your opponent."

"Alright, it was my fault. I was too reckless." Han Xiao immediately pulled his hand back, as though he had given up.

Seeing this, Sorokin heaved a sigh. He did not expect Han Xiao to move against him and thought that Han Xiao was going to force him to spar. But the latter only dealt a punch before restraining himself, making him a little surprised.

Thinking about it, Sorokin was relieved. Because Black Star had displayed tempestuous behavior all this while and was quite reckless. For him to suddenly attack like this was in line with his character.

However, he did not know that this blow he received had already activated his combat information, and it was enough for Han Xiao to see his true strength.

Stealthily opening the interface, Han Xiao swept across the notifications, and his pupils narrowed.

He did not guess wrong. Sorokin's level was actually unknown, only having '???'.

When I was Level 280, Manison's information was unknown too. Now that I'm Level 300, Sorokin still appears as unknown to me. This means that his combat strength is at the peak of the Beyond Grade A! He actually hid it for so long, letting all Beyond Grade As think him weak... This guy, playing the pig to eat the tiger, what is he planning?

Han Xiao's thoughts spun, and his eyes narrowed.

Chapter 925: Hila's Farewell

Similar to Manison, most of Sorokin's abilities were masked, and only some of them were revealed.

Sorokin was a Psychic Esper, which was evident in that most of his abilities were geared toward the soul and mind. He had strengthened his mind invasion, mind reading, and mind manipulation abilities, and Han Xiao even saw some special talents and skills.

[Immortal Soul]: Your powerful spiritual energy has blessed your soul with immortality, and even if you lose your fleshly body, you can still survive with your soul.

When the HP value reaches 0, your soul can survive from the destroyed body. In this case, you transform into a soul lifeform with an energy body, and you will obtain a new HP bar, which will not decay.

You will also obtain immunity to all Physical Attacks, extremely high resistance to Status Effects, and can phase through a majority of obstacles.

You can also invade and parasitize the mental domains of other living creatures.

Only Energy-Based or Mind-Based attacks will cause damage to you.

[Fleshly Body Reconstruction]: The fleshly shell is the carrier as well as the protector of the soul.

If your body is destroyed, you can consume Soul Energy to reshape it. The HP of the reconstructed body will be 30% of the original.

[Multidimensional Energy Absorption]: You can absorb any ownerless multidimensional energy in your surroundings to replenish your energy.

[Spiritual Energy Foundation]: Exclusive Talent. Your soul is akin to the cells in the body and can store and release energy as needed.

[Eternal Life]: Your Soul Resistance is slightly enhanced.

[Swindler—Sorokin]: Exclusive Talent. +75% to all Psychic Esper Abilities, +20% INT and MYS, +4 to all Psychic related abilities (This effect can break through the upper limit).

What OP abilities... Han Xiao's expression was grim.

[Immortal Soul] and [Fleshly Body Reconstruction] could be regarded as divine skills for those with psychic abilities. General, psychic users would experience soul decay without a fleshly body, but for Sorokin, no fleshy carrier was needed, which might be a change brought about by his Race Evolution.

Just based on these two strengths, as well as the talent [Eternal Life], Han Xiao had developed some conjectures.

Could it be... that Sorokin was actually living life as an alternate identity before this?

No wonder there was almost no information about him!

If that's the case, then his age likely exceeds my imagination!

Han Xiao was secretly guarded and sneaked a glance.

If not for his combat information, the way Sorokin acted would make it difficult to believe that he had such a great secret.

This guy is very strong, but he puts himself in a weakened position and does not care about being bent to the will of others, so it's easy to underestimate him. Although he has lived a long life, he's completely different compared to Manison... totally two extremes!

Sorokin naturally did not know that his true strength had been revealed, nor did he know what Han Xiao had discovered. He was a little unhappy over the sudden attack and did not speak for a while.

The duo walked in silence for a couple of minutes before Sorokin's eyes brightened. He had received news from Lovell, and a smile appeared on his face as he opened his mouth to speak.

"Your Excellency Black Star, may I ask if you have any intention to freely sell the Evolutionary Totem?"

Han Xiao returned to his senses.

"I'm not really bothered. It depends on the dynasty."

"Alas, if the Evolutionary Totem could be sold to all civilizations, then the market value of the Black Star Army would be stabilized at an extremely high level after being listed due to the profit from the monopoly. It's a pity we can't cooperate regarding this..."

Sorokin's expression looked regretful.

Han Xiao smiled and did not reply, but he was wary, as Sorokin seemed to imply something else.

After observing his headquarters, the two separated. Han Xiao sent Sorokin back to his room, standing at the spot for a few seconds before he left toward his office.

On the way, he contacted Sylvia and ordered, "Check all movements related to the Limitless Financial Group after they entered the Shattered Star Ring."

"Understood."

...

After a few days, the Black Star's Party officially started, and everyone came into the banquet hall. The scene was full of noise and chatter.

Han Xiao made a simple speech, summing up the results of their cooperation last year, before announcing the opening of the banquet amid the applause.

The emissaries of many civilizations and cooperative organizations were present, and they were all partners of the Black Star Army, covering many business areas.

A few years ago, Han Xiao had begun rolling out the plan for the 'Pan Star Field Profits Consortium', and after developing it for a few years, the prototype had become more and more perfect. These partners shared various business channels with the army so that it could have its current industry scale today. This plan was one of the cornerstones of the future development for the army, so Han Xiao attached great importance to it.

Han Xiao was surrounded by people, talking enthusiastically. Sylvia stood by his side, helping him cope with the crowd. There was a lot of laughter and cheers, and all the representatives showed a lot of face to him. The atmosphere was harmonious.

In the other corner of the banquet, there were people around Sorokin as well. The Limitless Financial Group was the wealthiest party there, so many people wished to take this chance to have dealings with him.

Sorokin held a wine glass, smiling as he chatted with the rest. He took in the scenes of this gathering and the guests, his gaze masking his thoughts and only carrying an interested look.

At the same time, his consciousness had arrived in Bloodshed Land and possessed a follower beside Lovell.

The Tyrant's Party and Black Star's Party were held at the same time, but it was much colder compared to Black Star's Party. Only a few people were whispering, and most people were only focused on dealing with the drinks and food.

While Heber remained expressionless, his mood was obviously no better than the chilly atmosphere.

As Lovell walked around the banquet with wine in hand, she suddenly noticed that her follower had signaled toward her with his eyes. She immediately understood that it was Sorokin and quietly moved to a corner.

"What's the matter?" Lovell whispered.

"You'll be staying at Bloodshed Land, responsible for the work of the financial group here. The resources of the financial group over here will be handled by you," Sorokin said.

"Okay."

Joy flashed through Lovell's eyes. Due to the intense competition among Sorokin's children, to have such an important task given to her by her father meant that her father appreciated her talents.

Suppressing her excitement, Lovell asked in a small voice, "What are the specific action plans? Are there any issues that require special attention?"

"I'll hand the details to you later. To suppress Black Star Army's businesses, the first goal should be to start with his business partners." Sorokin coldly laughed. "I can see that Black Star has deliberately created a huge net of interests for his organization, so the first thing to do will be to cut the net he's formed. I don't need to teach you how to do it."

"I understand." Lovell nodded.

"When the resources of the financial group arrive, you can take action when you see fit."

...

The party this time also ended on a successful note. The next day, Sorokin bade farewell and left.

At the dock of the headquarters, Han Xiao sent the Limitless Financial Group's fleet off into the universe. His brows then furrowed tight, and he revealed a heavy expression.

He left just like that... I really can't tell what he's up to.

While he had already seen through the hidden power of Sorokin and made himself more alert, he still knew nothing about Sorokin's plans.

Han Xiao had a hunch that Sorokin might be planning something in the background. If the Black Star Army encountered any abnormal issues, it would probably be Sorokin's doing.

And according to his speculations, it likely had something to do with the Evolutionary Totems.

"Troublesome..." Han Xiao snorted.

He knew early on that the matter of the Evolutionary Totem would not go away easily. Without satisfying everyone, there would still be complaints and grumbles.

The dynasty was shouldering the majority of the pressure, but it seemed like the pressure on the Black Star Army was about to arrive as well.

If that's the case, then it would be better for me to stay within the dynasty for a period of time and leave behind some Apostle Weapons and mechanical hosts in the headquarters.

Han Xiao made up his mind. He was still worried about the long-distance teleportation that the Federation of Light had.

Ta, ta, ta!

He heard the footsteps of someone drawing near. Han Xiao did not need to turn back to know that it was Hila.

"Han Xiao, there's something I need to discuss with you."

"What is it?" Han Xiao put away his thoughts, staring at Hila's cold and delicate face.

"I'll be leaving for an extended period of time. Please take care of Aurora."

Han Xiao raised a brow. "Where are you headed?"

"I'll be following my teacher, Ames, to other Star Fields to gain experience. I might not be able to perform my duties as the Black Star Guard Captain," Hila lightly replied.

Han Xiao was surprised. "Following Ames?"

"That's right. It was Teacher who invited me."

Both sides stared at each other for a while before Han Xiao broke out into laughter.

"This is a good opportunity. I approve of this. Leave Aurora to me."

"Thank you." Hila nodded.

"There's no need to say thanks between us." Han Xiao walked up and grasped her shoulders, solemnly saying, "I hope that when you return, you'll be at Beyond Grade A."

"You really have a lot of confidence in me." Hila let out a smile and hesitated for a while before punching Han Xiao's chest. "Take care."

"Relax, I'll have Feidin assume the role of Captain for now. He's reliable. As for you... eh, don't go, I haven't finished speaking."

Looking at Hila's unfriendly back as she walked away, Han Xiao facepalmed and swallowed his words.

It was a good opportunity for Hila to go out and gain more experience, and this should help her stimulate her potential, allowing her to reach Beyond Grade A faster.

He just did not expect Ames to also go out and train. He had heard that Ames had thrown herself into training two years ago after losing to him, but it seemed that she wished to take it further.

With Ames by her side, Hila would naturally be safe. However, to be on the safe side, Han Xiao equipped their spaceship with some mechanical troops and hosts for insurance.

Since they had already started working, he could not sit idly by...

Han Xiao entered the quantum network, summoning Phillip.

"How goes the collection of the Energy Training Techniques?"

"Master, hum... I've screened out the more valuable options for you. Please check the results, hum..."

A list appeared in front of him, all of which were exquisite Energy Training Techniques that could be bought on various galactic markets. They came from different civilizations and races, with all sorts of flowery names.

Sweeping over them with a glance, Han Xiao quickly came to a decision.

"Buy them all."

Chapter 926: First Phase of Development

The ability of having Enas might not be the strongest, but it was definitely the best to use. The joy of having a lot of money was something unimaginable.

After buying a lot of Energy Training Techniques, Han Xiao slowly inserted the experience, increasing his energy.

Time is money, and the life span of a Beyond Grade A was long. This long lifespan gave them plenty of time to learn more knowledge and skills, so each Beyond Grade A had a ridiculous number of Energy Training Techniques. While Han Xiao required less time compared to the other Beyond Grade As to raise his energy, it was still a chore for him.

The next day, Han Xiao brought Aurora to the restricted dock to send off Hila.

A black, reflective spaceship was parked there. This was an advanced spaceship that Han Xiao had given to Hila. Under the gangway where the cabin door was, Hila stood without her uniform.

Hila still maintained her cold expression, with her long red hair spread out around her, only loosely tied at the ends, hanging around her waist level. With bangs covering her forehead, her temperament appeared a lot more refreshing than her usual cold self.

She wore a lightweight and tough soft alloy jacket, similar to a windbreaker, coupled with black tights that were made by Han Xiao for defense. A small rucksack was on her shoulder/. She looked like a traveler.

"Sis, when are you coming back?" Aurora had a look of reluctance. Over the past few years, both sisters had stayed together, and now that they were separating, she was a little unused to it.

"When I reach Beyond Grade A." The corners of Hila's mouth curled up slightly as she glanced at Han Xiao.

Aurora let out a despondent "Ah..."

"How long would that be..."

"You're my motivation. In order to return home to see you, I'll be quick." Hila ruffled Aurora's hair.

Aurora helplessly grabbed at her hair before sighing. "After so many years, you still treat me like a kid."

In my heart, you'll always be the kid that needs protecting... Hila gently squeezed Aurora's cheeks, a touch of love in her eyes.

By the side, Han Xiao coughed and interrupted them. "I've equipped the spaceship with a nano-maintenance robot as well as some good mechanical equipment. There are also two mechanical hosts and some mechanical soldiers within the warehouse. If necessary, let me know and I'll activate them."

"Ok." Hila was different from her past self. While she enjoyed solitude, she no longer rejected the help of others.

"While Ames will be travelling with you, it is training, and she will not purposefully protect you. Furthermore, she's a Beyond Grade A, so some dangers that might seem like nothing to her could be lethal to you. You have to be careful," Han Xiao advised.

While those of the Calamity Grade could already walk unhindered in the universe, if one wished to train, they would have to deliberately wander around the danger zones. There were still many such places in the universe, where dangers abound. It could be experimental planets undergoing biochemical experiments or places filled with viruses, huge beasts, aberrations, and many more. Otherwise, they could attempt to hunt some powerful galactic beings. Even if they could not find such areas, wandering around to challenge people would also serve as a form of practice.

Hila nodded, expressing her understanding, but she did not think this way.

Only at the border of life and death could one explode with all their potential. Staying in the army has no life-and-death fight, so her progress was stalling. Her threshold to breakthrough into a Beyond Grade A was still far, and while Ames might be whimsical and take this trip as an adventure, Hila herself treated this as real life or death training.

Han Xiao was one of the few people she trusted, so only by handing Aurora over to Han Xiao would her mind be at ease.

After turning back to glance at them one last time, Hila turned around to board to spaceship.

The next moment, the spaceship shuddered, and the thrusters jetted out orange flames that quickly turned blue.

Whoosh!

The spaceship sped up and rushed out of the port. In the blink of an eye, it entered hyperdrive and vanished from sight.

"Sigh... I don't even know how many years Sis will need before she can achieve Beyond Grade A and return... It's the Beyond Grade A realm, how could it be so easy?"

Aurora's spirits were low, and she tugged at Han Xiao's sleeve.

"Er... actually, I think it's pretty easy." Han Xiao's lips curled up teasingly.

"My fault, I shouldn't have asked you." Aurora rolled her eyes, tiptoeing to pat on Han Xiao's shoulder, acting like the elder as she sighed. "Both Teacher and Sis are now gone. Old Uncle, it's just you and me now."

"The Shattered Star Ring and Flickering World doesn't really need me to be here personally. Because of some reason, I have to go over to the dynasty for a period of time. You should follow me over too. It'll be safer for you."

Aurora hesitated. "You mean this place will be exposed to danger?"

"That's... I'm not sure, but there will definitely be turmoil."

"Alright, whatever the case, I'll follow you around... Oh yes, can I try being part of the Black Star Guards?"

"You're too green, better not."

"Humph. Rude!"

Han Xiao shook his head, turning to gaze at the river of stars in the universe.

How long will Hila take before she returns?

The day she returns, I'll have yet another trustworthy ally.

A few days later, in the Crimson Dynasty's ruler's office, the virtual projections of many of the dynasty's upper echelons gathered together and stood neatly in the room. Tarrokov, as Commander-in-Chief of the Exploration army, was among them. A document adorned with the dynasty's logo was spread out on the table in front of Urranrell, the written content densely packed.

Urranrell read the document quickly and, upon turning to the last page, paused before picking up the pen and signing her name at the end of the document.

The table shimmered, and a digitally projected head appeared, intoning in a synthetic voice.

"The authority of the dynasty's ruler is confirmed. The decree 'Flickering World Construction Charter' has been signed and is legally binding, effective immediately."

Every advanced civilization had to use artificial intelligence, and the three Universal Civilizations had their own versions of master artificial intelligences. With generations of Mechanics and scientists perfecting it, the master artificial intelligence would record the backup of each Dynasty Ruler as well as the elites of the civilization, merging them into an elite consciousness. It was codenamed [Heroic Soul].

Urranrell placed the pen down, handing the document to the secretary beside her as she announced, "In three days, announce to the world that the first phase of the Flickering World was a success... Long live the dynasty."

"Long Live the dynasty!" the rest of the upper echelons echoed.

"Notify the allies involved in the development that it is time to divide the lands and formally begin the construction of the three Star Clusters in the first phase of development," Urranrell solemnly said. "Until the construction is completed, the second phase will not begin."

In the logistics department, Han Xiao was supervising Nero's learning when he received a communication request from Tarrokov. He had a hunch as to why Tarrokov was calling.

Switching it on, Tarrokov's old face emerged on the screen.

"Black Star, Ruler Urranrell has already signed a decree and will soon announce to the entire universe that the first phase of the Flickering World has been completed. Let me specifically inform you that the dynasty's decision to allocate land to the allies has also been finalized."

Finally, it's here. I've been waiting for a long time... Han Xiao's attention was completely focused.

"I'm listening. Please continue."

"Territory will be issued according to the merits of exploration. Most of the allies that joined later will only take a few Star Zones, at most no more than one Star System. As the earliest ally to participate, the dynasty will naturally give you more territory."

The three Star Clusters that were explored during the first phase were located at the gateway to the Flickering World and basically fell under the control of the dynasty and its allies.

A single Star Cluster contained dozens of Star Systems, and while each Star System seemed tiny in comparison, they were still large in scale. After all, the territory of a Star System level civilization encompassed the entire star system, with some not even reaching that scope.

Han Xiao nodded and asked, "So, how much are we being given?"

"Bloodshed Land will obtain about two Star Systems' worth, and because of the deal we made regarding the secret war, Klent will obtain about four Star Systems. Their territories will be based in the Renault Star Cluster."

"And me?" Han Xiao was curious.

"The Black Star Army's exploration was the most well done. In addition, you had racked up huge merits. The Ruler favors you, so the dynasty has decided to give you..." Tarrokov paused and smiled. "A whole seven Star Systems!"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Seven star systems was equivalent to about ten to twenty percent of the total territory in the Garu Star Cluster!

Furthermore, this was only the first phase!

Just based on this, this starting point had exceeded all the Star System civilizations by a few times.

"Furthermore..." Tarrokov's grin got wider. "Urranrell did not forget her promise to you. The territory for the others has basically been allocated, but for your seven Star Systems, you may choose them yourself."

All my work paid off... Han Xiao was jubilant.

So far, the Black Star Army had no proper base. Their headquarters and branches were actually located in the territories of others, as the universe currently had already been fully explored. There were not many vacancies left, and even the desolate universe belt had owners. Only now did they finally obtain their autonomous territory.

Part of the Star Cluster was to be distributed to their allies, while part of it would be under the direct control of the dynasty. The last part would be considered an open territory, for other organizations to compete over. With so many partitions, it was impressive that Han Xiao had obtained nearly a fifth of the entire Star Cluster.

According to Han Xiao's prediction, he would obtain about three to four Star Systems, which would already make it extremely profitable.

However, to think that the dynasty valued him so much to give him seven Star Systems immediately, a total of over 100 Star Zones, and he could even choose the location!

The dynasty was really generous!

Chapter 927: [Flickering World] First Chain Mission Completed

The 3D map, displayed in a vibrant blue color, was suspended in front of Han Xiao, showing the overview of the Garu Star Cluster. Most of the areas were marked in green, representing the available Star Systems.

Han Xiao gazed with a thoughtful look at the star map, and the light from the map was reflected on his face.

Beside him, Tarrokov's long distance projection was also smiling while gazing at the star map.

"Have you decided?"

"I have, but before that, I have a question. After the first phase of exploration, the dynasty has now figured out the resource distribution for each Star System. While you allow me to choose, will your attitudes change if I do not pick the ones that the dynasty wants me to pick?" Han Xiao eyed him.

"Haha, I know what you're referring to. You're worried that if you pick all the resource rich areas, the dynasty will have something to say, right?" Tarrokov laughed. "Relax, since the dynasty is willing to give you something, that means they are not worried no matter how big your appetite is. The dynasty is not so petty."

"That's good." Han Xiao nodded.

"However, the Ruler has asked me to warn you..." Tarrokov's eyes flashed at this moment, carrying a hidden meaning. "She advises you put some thought into choosing the Star Systems."

"Because I'm in the Ruler's faction?" Han Xiao got interested.

"Well, this could be one of the reasons... How about this? Let me share some inside information with you. In fact, not everyone within the dynasty agreed to give you seven Star Systems. Some of them thought that the important areas should be controlled by the dynasty and should not be distributed to any allies. However, Urranrell and her heads of state stood in the way and took out what they had within the Garu Star Cluster for you to choose. Based on her words, since the dynasty had made a commitment, they should not go back on their word, or it would only cause their allies to lose trust."

"Seems like the Ruler is really looking out for me." Han Xiao smiled and nodded.

"The Ruler thus recommends that you hold onto some strategic locations," Tarrokov said. "The implied meaning is that you use this to obtain a louder voice within the dynasty. That way, she can suppress the unharmonious voices within the dynasty... I think you know what's going on."

Hearing this, Han Xiao understood that it was the matter of the Evolution Cube.

Every time a Beyond Grade A ally appeared with a strategic level Universal Treasure, this sort of contradiction would occur. In the past, Psyker often had to bear the pressure of the Arcane Church as well.

Some people within the dynasty would hope for him to take the initiative to turn in the Evolution Cube. It was not that Han Xiao had not heard of it, but their voices were currently very weak when faced against the rules of how Universal Civilizations should treat their allies.

It was impossible to force their allies to turn in any Universal Treasures. However, the desire of some people for the Evolution Cube within the dynasty had yet to vanish.

Urranrell wanted Han Xiao to increase his voice, but the other party of the faction coveting the Evolution Cube did not wish for him to do so, which would make it harder to suppress him. From another perspective, this was an internal factional competition.

With this in mind, Han Xiao felt helpless. He originally did not wish to be involved in the political struggles within the dynasty, but it seemed like he did not have a choice. Anything of value in the eyes of these dynasty factions would be used as a chip, and their Beyond Grade A allies were no exception.

"No matter how they think, I just need to develop myself." Han Xiao shook his head, stretching out his hand to tap on seven points on the map. "I'll take these seven Star Systems."

Tarrokov took a look, and his eyes flashed before he laughed out loud. "You're really not polite."

"You were the one who told me not to be." Han Xiao shrugged.

He had chosen all the important Star Systems of the Garu Star Cluster. Two of them were Star Systems that served as gateways to the other two Star Clusters, which were strategic choke points, and two other Star Systems chosen were to be important transit points within the Garu Star Cluster. The last three were in the central location of the Star Cluster, where the resources were the richest, with extremely high developmental value.

"Alright, I'll report back to the Ruler, and construction will soon begin. You should prepare well in advance." Tarrokov then switched off his communicator, and his projection vanished.

Han Xiao turned back to face the seven lighted spots in the star map, slowly letting out a breath.

"Seven Star Systems... This is my future territory."

Several days later, the Crimson Dynasty announced to the universe that the first phase of the Flickering World exploration was a complete success, announcing the exploration results to the world.

There were countless gazes observing the development process of the Flickering World all along. The new Star Field was both the territory of the Crimson Dynasty as well as the wealth of an entire universe, and if successfully opened, the reputation of the Crimson Dynasty would also be raised.

This news inspired the spirits of many organizations, especially the financial groups. Even as early as during its exploration, the dynasty had already released the rumors that the follow-up construction would allow the financial groups to inject capital to participate. Even though there were more people than benefits provided, only the larger financial groups would be able to compete for the rights to construct, so it was still a profitable trade.

Every ally of the dynasty would be a good target to invest in. The dynasty's announcement also listed the ownership of territories for each ally. Among them, the Black Star Army stood at the very top with seven Star Systems, far exceeding Klent in second place with four Star Systems.

The major organizations within the universe could feel the importance the dynasty viewed Black Star with.

But that was to be given. Black Star was still so young, yet he had grown so quickly. He would most likely end up as one of the pillars of the dynasty for the next hundreds, if not thousands, of years. Therefore, the dynasty would not neglect him.

After the announcement was released, the major financial groups also started to act. They began to contact the dynasty allies within the list. The Black Star Army was the most popular with the financial groups, with countless applications sent to Phillip.

While the territory of seven Star Systems seemed huge, there were just too many financial groups staring at the Flickering World. A financial group's goal was to profit, and with only that much territory, there was no way Han Xiao could choose to work with all of them. Han Xiao personally screened out the financial groups with limited power and sent his people to negotiate with the larger ones.

Because this was a big project, Han Xiao asked Sylvia to send staff from the various departments to form a team to negotiate with the different financial groups to discuss the details of cooperation.

The typical method of cooperation was for the financial group to invest cash, buy resources and engineering equipment, or help them to construct the territory. The invested party had to promise that after the Flickering World was opened up, these financial groups would get to operate or mine on certain resource rich planets or have certain rights when conducting businesses within the territory.

Because the territory was completely under one's jurisdiction, they had the final say in any transactions approved and did not have to face any pressure from a ruling civilization.

While Han Xiao was still wary of Sorokin, the two of them had already reached a preliminary agreement to cooperate, so in the spirit of keeping promises, he sent a message to Sorokin to set the terms of cooperation. However, the other party's investment amount was far below Han Xiao's expectations, almost to the point of an investment made while suffering from poverty.

"There's no reason for the Limitless Financial Group to only invest that amount. It seems like they do not respect me at all."

Within the office, Han Xiao observed the terms of the contract, his expression strange.

"Sylvia, when I asked you to check the Limitless Financial Group's movements, did you find anything?"

"Yes. The Limitless Financial Group split into two groups after they entered the Shattered Star Ring, with the smaller group joining the Tyrant's Party. If I'm not wrong, the Limitless Financial Group should have been evaluating their investment targets, and they seem to have chosen the Tyrant over us."

"That's strange. The territory I have is more than thrice that of Heber, yet Sorokin is focusing on Heber?" Han Xiao wondered aloud. "Could it be that Heber gave him some special terms?"

After thinking for a few seconds, Han Xiao did not continue struggling with this matter. There were many financial groups staring at this opportunity, and if the Limitless Financial Group did not wish to cooperate in depth, it was fine. What he did not lack now was potential partners.

After dealing with the matter at hand, Han Xiao placed the communicator down, opening the interface to view the Mission notification.

The first part of the [Flickering World] main mission was to explore the Garu Star Cluster. The moment the Crimson Dynasty announced the successful exploration of the first phase, the first mission would also be shown as completed and ready for Han Xiao to collect his rewards.

The players had also received this main storyline, but they had to wait till they returned from the version update to obtain their reward.

Han Xiao glanced at the mission description. He had accumulated a large number of Exploration Points, and the Mission Rating had long reached the highest tier.

"After several years of exploration, I've finally managed to complete the first part of this Main Storyline Mission," Han Xiao grumbled. "The Mission Rating is so high. The reward should also be enough for me to redeem the last Ultimate Knowledge I need."

As he spoke, he chose the option to obtain his Mission rewards.

[Flickering World] First chain mission completed.

Your Mission Rating is S+.

You have obtained 2,000,000,000 Experience, x3 Random Reward Draws, 3,000 Crimson Dynasty Contribution Points, and x2 Blank Character Summon Cards.

The milestone [Exploration Pioneer] is now activated.

Milestone Requirements: Obtain at least 3 'A' Ratings and above for Mission Rating in the [Flickering World] Chain Missions.

Current Progress: 1/3

"Yo, a milestone mission." Han Xiao brows went up.

These kinds of milestone missions usually gave either a unique title or Legendary Points. Some titles were just for bragging rights, while some had additional bonuses. Han Xiao remembered that he still had a [Legendary Hunter] milestone mission that had not been completed. The title would increase his damage against Beast-type creatures. On the other hand, [Exploration Pioneer] increased his rate of obtaining dungeon copies or random rewards.

The highest Mission Rating gave him twenty billion experience. While it was peanuts to him, for a player at level 120, it was enough to level up quite a few times. Based on the standards of this version, this reward could be considered sizable. The only other missions that gave him the same amount of experience involved fighting the Beyond Grade As, and comparing their difficulties, the [Flickering World] exploration was so much easier.

The second chain mission for the [Flickering World] also appeared, which was to complete all the infrastructure construction in the territory that the Black Star Army was assigned.

This Main Storyline was very flexible, and its specific requirements would vary according to one's faction and the actual situation. The mission requirements for Han Xiao and the army players in [Flickering World] were issued based on their position as the Crimson Dynasty and Black Star Army factions.

It was a pity that the players were all offline, missing out on this mission reward.

After letting his thoughts wander for a while, Han Xiao then collected himself and glanced at the faction contribution point bar. The most useful thing right now was the three thousand Contribution Points. With this, his total contribution exceeded twelve thousand points, enabling him to gain one more Ultimate Knowledge.

"Finally, I'm getting the number of Ultimate Knowledges needed." Han Xiao breathed out in relief.

At the same time in the Bloodshed Land, the Limitless Financial Group and Heber reached a consensus. Lovell served as a resident emissary in the Bloodshed Land, and Sorokin would pass her instructions by possessing her followers.

Not long after the dynasty announced the territory of its allies, Lovell contacted Sorokin in shock.

"The dynasty is too partial toward Black Star, giving them a whole seven Star Systems. Father, will it really be okay if we don't focus on investing in the Black Star Army?"

Sorokin also frowned. He knew that the dynasty treated Black Star with importance, but this was out of his expectations.

The Black Star Army had gathered more wealth and popularity than expected, which was detrimental to their plans.

Those cooperating internal factions mentioned that they were working internally to prevent Black Star from getting any good territory, but now it seemed that they had failed. This was not suppressing him but rather increasing the difficulty level...

His teammates were not useful at all!

Chapter 928: Required Knowledges Gathered!

Seeing the sullen look on Lovell's face, Sorokin eased his brows and calmly replied, "Forget it, it's just the first phase anyways. Although this is unexpected, this profit is not worth mentioning compared to our dealings with the three civilizations. The Bloodshed Land might have fewer territories, but they are also valuable. We can focus on investing here and need not go over to Black Star to compete with the other financial groups."

Lovell pursed her lips and could only nod.

Sorokin paused, his eyes narrowing slightly as he indifferently continued. "The Black Star Army has now gained such a huge territory, and there's a lot of room for development. Its ability to resist pressure has increased, but this is not completely to our disadvantage. The focus of the army will be directed toward the Flickering World, which allows us to weaken their original business dealings.

"First, attack the interest consortium of the Black Star Army within the Shattered Star Ring. We are still unable to shake their core businesses and can only start with the cooperative organizations of various industries that the Black Star Army is affiliated to. We can help Bloodshed Land to snatch a part of the business channels and cut off the arms of the Black Star Army, reducing the scope of their business. In this case, they will return to the original scope, which will make him unable to expand and develop comfortably."

Lovell hesitated before speaking in a whisper. "Father, the Black Star Army has great prospects, and their business is also booming. In all honesty, it is unlikely for such methods to shake them."

"Naturally, a Beyond Grade A organization is not so easily suppressed. That's especially so for Black Star with his growing momentum... but it's because this is difficult that the three Universal Civilizations came to me. Rice should be eaten a mouthful at a time. As long as one is willing to fork out the costs, they will be able to gradually erode everything."

Sorokin shook his head, his expression still cold. "Furthermore, I'm not here to destroy the Black Star Army but to make him feel uncomfortable. This will take a long time to take effect, so I'll take my time. Those cooperating with me are not even in a hurry, so why should I rush?"

While the father and daughter were cooperating, on the other side of Bloodshed Land, Heber was also in his palace reading the terms of the contract proposed by Lovell. He secretly nodded to himself.

The contract described the plans for the Limitless Financial Group to invest in Bloodshed Land. The goal was to let the Bloodshed Land learn from the Black Star Army and complete an organizational transformation, dealing not only in armed force employment but expanding to different industries, developing in an all-round manner.

Such business channels need not be laid out from scratch. They focused on the channels that many of the local organizations within the Shattered Star Ring had operated and perfected after many years. They would obtain them through acquisitions, where most of the costs would be borne by the Limitless Financial Group.

Seeing the investment amount proposed by the Limitless Financial Group, Heber coldly snorted.

"Really rich."

The Black Star Army had recently entered a busy state.

After the preliminary selection made by Han Xiao, each financial group then sent people to negotiate with the personnel of the Black Star Army.

Dillard, the team leader of Negotiation Team 098, was currently involved in the discussions with one of the higher ups of a financial group.

"Mr. Dillard, this is the third time we have modified the terms of cooperation according to your wishes. Are you satisfied with it this time?"

The executive of the financial group carefully watched Dillard's expression.

"You want the mining rights of at least ten resource rich planets for fifteen years, management rights for three of the planets and the right to modify its surface, operation rights for two regional quantum network channels, and preferential sales channels for dozens of rare resources... Hahaha, don't you think that this investment amount is insufficient to request such treatment?" Dillard raised his eyebrows, giving a smile that was not a smile.

"Based on the calculations done on my side, the amount of investments is equivalent to our requirements..."

"Do you wish to take advantage of our Black Star Army? If you don't have enough sincerity, we can stop the negotiations. We still have many others to choose from." Dillard's tone sank, and he looked ready to end the discussion.

"Wait a minute." The executive got a shock and immediately scrambled to reply. "Don't misunderstand, we never intended anything like that. Which part are you not satisfied with? We can always talk it out..."

As he observed the other party's careful expression, there was no outward change in Dillard's face, but in his heart, he was secretly very proud of himself.

He was just an ordinary worker in the Black Star Army with limited pay. In the galactic society, be it in status or assets, he was far inferior to the executives of various financial groups.

However, these rich and powerful executives were now trying to please him, a clerk, with enthusiasm as well as treading on thin ice to speak to him. Dillard had never been treated with such enthusiasm before.

Now that countless financial groups were seeking cooperation with the Black Star Army, as a negotiator, he held the initiative and power, and he had more confidence.

If not for the fact that he had joined the Black Star Army earlier, how could he have gotten such an opportunity, where those in the high ranks bowed to him?

In order to satisfy his own vanity, in addition to obtaining more benefits for the army, Dillard would set harsher and more unyielding terms, holding firmly to his initiative.

He knew that this was merely borrowing the name of the Black Star Army to strut around, like a fox pretending to be a tiger, but he was happy about it. Now that his affiliation was so powerful, if he did not take the chance to flaunt it a little more, there would never be a chance for him in the future.

The executives of the financial group knew what Dillard was doing, and they gritted their teeth in anger inwardly, but they had no choice as they were the passive party.

They would rather suffer a bit than lose out on the golden opportunity to cooperate with the Black Star Army.

In the Army Commander's office, a projection of Phillip about a thumb's size sat on the edge of the table with his legs swinging around, reporting to Han Xiao in a crisp voice.

"Investigation completed. There are forty-five negotiators who have received bribes during the negotiation process."

"Fire all of them and cancel the cooperation agreements that they've negotiated. We're no longer cooperating with these financial groups."

Han Xiao frowned.

As the scale of the army increased, it was inevitable for people to develop greed in their hearts and use the army's name to obtain personal benefits.

He did not mind the members flaunting the army's prestige, but if someone betrayed the army's interests, he could not pretend nothing had happened. As a Virtual Mechanic, the entire faction was within his control; nothing could be hidden from him.

After dealing with this annoying problem, Han Xiao rubbed his eyes and prepared to proceed to the training rooms to work on his Energy Training Technique. It was at this time that his communicator rang.

Picking up the communicator, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

His request to the dynasty had been accepted!

The Dynasty Contribution Points he had amounted to twelve thousand, and Han Xiao had sent in a request to redeem an Ultimate Knowledge.

In just a few short years, Black Star had made so many achievements that it was enough for him to obtain all the Ultimate Knowledges he needed. This efficiency was probably the highest in history. Because the biggest attraction for a Beyond Grade A to join a Universal Civilization was to obtain Ultimate Knowledges, now that Han Xiao had gathered up all the Ultimate Knowledges of the Mechanic department, the Crimson Dynasty was a little hesitant, and the approval time was much longer than before.

However, if there were merits achieved, the reward had to be given. Thus, Han Xiao finally received the final Ultimate Knowledge of the Mechanic profession.

Control Branch—[Relativity Theory]!

Just like how Beyond Grade A mages could travel through all secondary dimensions, this Ultimate Knowledge of the Mechanic profession could achieve similar results. As a sophisticated spacetime technology, it could be applied to the manufacture of stargates, Interstellar Navigation Technology, Hyperdrive transition engines, next-generation propellers, and many more devices.

In combat, this knowledge improved the maneuverability of machinery, and it was applicable to various spatial based devices. It could be used to attack and defend, and it was extremely good for crowd control.

With this Ultimate Knowledge, the difficulty of facing mechanics would increase more than one level. This played the biggest role in overcoming the core shortcomings of Mechanics, which was fighting people at close range. As Han Xiao was an anomaly, close ranged combat did not matter to him at all, so he had placed this knowledge at the very end of his collection.

Because this was considered general Profession Knowledge, the triple penalty did not apply to it, and every level only needed eight Potential Points. He had just enough to use it to complete the Class Advancement Mission [Erudite].

"After mastering this, all of my Ultimate Knowledges have been collected. The next step is to slowly max out all of my knowledges."

Han Xiao settled himself down and chose to learn it.

Mechanic Class Ultimate Knowledge detected: [Relativity Theory]. Spend 8 potential points to learn?

Learning...

Successfully learned! You have learned [Relativity Theory]!

You have been awarded with the talent [Hyperspace Thought]!

You have mastered all available Ultimate Knowledge, and your talent [Ultimate Knowledge Possessor] has been strengthened!

You have learned all Class Knowledges. You have been awarded with the talent [Almighty Mechanic]!

Hyperspace Thought: Enhances all spatial device performances, control effect is significantly strengthened, and your domain related abilities and all space-related abilities will be enhanced. +50 – 100% increase in CC duration, +20% to mobility of all machinery equipment, +40% to mental resistance.

Ultimate Knowledge Possessor is enhanced. +15% – +25% Attributes for machinery built, +150% – 600% Machinery Affinity. New effect added: All Mechanic skill levels +1 (can exceed the upper limit).

Almighty Mechanic: +20% Mechanic Creation Attributes, all Mechanic Skill levels +2 (can exceed the upper limit). In addition, +1,500 INT, +500 Free Attribute Points.

Extra Effect I: +1% Machinery Affinity for every 20 points in INT.

Extra Effect II: Passive Aura, any life forms around you gain a boost of +200 INT.

Chapter 929: Preparations Complete, Construction Begins

With the completion of the last piece of Knowledge needed, the world in front of his eyes seemed to have undergone a subtle change, and his perception of space transformed.

Han Xiao raised his head to look at the cup on the table. By the corners of the cup, a variety of function formulas appeared, excluding its outer appearance, and only the precise lines denoting the outline of the spatial structure of the cup were left. Glancing around, all objects in the room appeared in this manner, where everything appeared as a coefficient of spatial structure rather than as its original appearance.

As he blinked, this feeling slowly disappeared, and the room returned to normal.

This is probably the change brought about by [Hyperspace Thought]. It seems that it has elevated my spatial perception to a whole new level.

That feeling seemed to maintain the view of multiple perspectives at the same time. It seemed to even overlap with other dimensions.

[Relativity Theory] only provided one talent by nature, but the effect was considerable. It comprehensively enhanced the mobility and controlling skills of the Mechanic, and it also improved Psychological Resistance. The other two talents obtained were brought about by the [Erudite] ability.

Generally speaking, the players could never afford the expenses needed to collect all the Knowledges, and it was difficult to learn all of them. However, there were a minority of people who grinded like crazy to completely learn all of the available Knowledges. Han Xiao was one of such 'Liver Emperors[1]'. Thus, he was no stranger to the effects both talents brought about to him.

With the two extra talents, my strength has increased by yet another level, and I can be considered to be an all-rounder Advanced Mechanic now.

Han Xiao calculated that the enhanced [Ultimate Knowledge Possessor] as well as the newly obtained [Almighty Mechanic] would enhance him to the point of the [Perfect Mechanical Sense] standard.

The higher his Machinery Affinity, the greater the increase of the total bonus from his Mechanical Sense talent. So long as he managed to get [Perfect Mechanical Sense], his damage would fly off the charts!

By that time, he would be roughly similar to [Mechanic Emperor] Manison, the only difference being their exclusive talents.

"Now that I've gotten my hands on all the Knowledges, the next step will be to upgrade all of them."

In his previous life, while there were players that learned all Knowledges, there had not been anyone who raised everything to the maximum. That was Han Xiao's goal this time. To complete this, he needed huge amounts of experience. The accumulated amount in this version was far from being enough, and he could only work on this from the next version onward.

Han Xiao had no idea if there would be additional rewards for maxing out all his Class Knowledges. In any case, with the huge player market that he had, levelling up everything would not bring him any losses.

The interface also showed that he had an additional five hundred Free Attribute Points. Gazing at his attributes, he saw that his Intelligence had finally broken through the ten thousand mark. Intelligence was the main attribute of a mechanic, which would determine the attributes of his mechanical creations as well as the Mechanical Force bonuses. Currently, his Endurance was not lacking; he was so tanky that even he could no longer bear it. Thus, Han Xiao decided to continue to pump his Intelligence.

After seeing the huge increase in his attributes, Han Xiao closed his interface in satisfaction. He chewed on two high energy nutrition bars as a celebration before taking a private space shuttle to the satellites around his headquarters. He found an idle one and entered its large, open-air training ground to summon all his machinery through the secondary dimensional army box.

After years of accumulation, Han Xiao now had more than a hundred thousand mechanical lives and over ten Apostle Weapons, which served as his commanders, lining up in front of Han Xiao.

In the huge square, the various mechanical lives stopped making any noise and turned to look at Han Xiao. Those with legs knelt on one knee, while those without lowered their heads to show respect. A magnificent scene was displayed.

"Lord."

"Rise." Han Xiao waved his hands before turning to look at Psionic Prime, who was at the forefront. "The time has come. The Machinery Civilization plan can now be implemented."

"I will not disappoint you, my lord." A determined expression appeared on the facial features of Psionic Prime.

Han Xiao gestured with a finger, and a star map appeared on the sky, showing the territory of the Garu Star Cluster. The picture zoomed in and quickly locked onto one of the planets within the Star System, situated within his own territory.

"This planet will be your new home in the future. It is rich in ores. Psionic Prime, at that time, you'll take all the mechanical lives to develop on this planet. The Black Star Army will provide you with all sorts of support, and I only have one requirement, which is to expand the population as much as possible."

In order to develop his own Mechanical Civilization, Han Xiao had released all his mechanical lives. They need not stay within the secondary dimensional army box for the time being.

After being transformed by [Tinder Awakening], the machines had already become true living bodies. Their bodies were filled with silicon-based nerve fibers. They had independent thoughts and even the ability to reproduce.

Of course, the method of propagation for mechanical life was not through 'pa pa pa' but asexual reproduction. Two or more of the mechanical lives would extract their own tinder gene code and transfer to the reproducing mechanical life, or they could insert it within the assembly line to 'hatch' a newborn. After a long period of energy supply, the newborn's tinder would be strengthened into a complete mechanical life.

The mechanical life created in this manner of reproduction was equivalent to sharing the life energy of the first generation of machines. Its purity and basic attributes would of course be far inferior compared to the first generation. The parent mechanical life would also enter a period of weakness due to huge consumption of their life tinder.

But the advantage was that births could be mass-produced, so Han Xiao did not need to work laboriously anymore. The production efficiency would skyrocket, and even the weakest mechanical life borne through this would still be stronger than most mechanical soldiers. The original intention of developing a machinery civilization was just to form a large-scale arsenal.

Manison had a machinery civilization that had developed for many years as his barracks, and the soldiers were endless.

With these hundred thousand first-generation mechanical lives, as long as they are allowed to develop for several years, I will then have a new army of mechanical lives, Han Xiao secretly thought.

All the mechanical lives raised their heads up to gaze at the virtual screen and started to discuss among themselves.

"I won't let you down." Psionic Prime retracted his gaze, simulating a solemn tone.

"Good. You can recommend another person with an outstanding ability, and I will give him a spot as an Apostle Weapon." Han Xiao smiled.

His new talents gave him a total of +3 to all Mechanic skill levels, which meant that the quota for [Apostle Life Creation] had now increased by three. Letting Psionic Prime pick a soldier would help him to consolidate his leadership position.

Because Han Xiao would not continuously monitor the development of his machinery civilization, he needed the first generations to manage everything well. Thus, the stronger the position of his spokesperson, the smoother the development of the machinery civilization.

Hearing this, Psionic Prime raised his spear and turned back. "Heaven-Suppressing Banner, step out."

Han Xiao looked at where the spear was pointing and saw a towering mechanical life enveloped in heavy outer armor within the crowd. It was as though he was clad in full plate mail, with all sorts of weapons hung around him. He had six arms, and on his back was a giant alloy battle shield, held by magnetic force. From afar, it looked like a huge banner.

"He's the strongest and bravest warrior in our clan, having defeated hundreds of others and taken their weapons. At the same time, he also knows how to command the army. I urge the Lord to grant him the qualification of an Apostle," Psionic Prime said.

Han Xiao sized Heaven-Suppressing Banner up. This guy's gear was actually loot taken from his opponents and installed on himself.

These mechanical lives had a high growth rate, and the blessing of [Machinery Fusion] allowed them to self-transform their hardware structure without limits.

"You indeed have the qualifications to be my Apostle. Make good use of this power." Raising his palm, a golden beam of Mechanical Force appeared in his palm like a bolt of lightning.

Flicking his hand, his Mechanical Force shot into the body of Heaven-Suppressing Banner, transforming his body and creating a brand-new Apostle.

Han Xiao did not continue to observe the transformation process but turned to Psionic Prime. "I shall hand the right to command the mechanical lives over to you. Serve me well."

After the transformation a few years ago as a result of the Evolution Cube, the Black Spirit Race had become far more intelligent and even possessed visual senses now. They gradually got used to living on the ground, no longer living in nests underground. With their efficient command over the mind network, they had built a stone city.

The largest stone city currently belonged to the Germinal Tribe, and in the center of the city, a stone statue, carved in the likeness of Black Star, stood tall. At this moment, this status held a metal statue, which was the Evolutionary Totem.

Evolutionary energy continuously radiated from the totem. For species with evolutionary space, the effect of the totems was excellent, and this had resulted in the evolution of the Black Spirit Race to be accelerated by hundreds of times. The proportion of the carapace on their body had shrunk once again, and their original bestial and insect-like characteristics were reduced a lot. Some of the Black Spirit Race had already begun to stand upright rather than crawl.

The liberated forelimbs also gradually played the role of a palm and began to learn how to use tools.

Up till now, Han Xiao had not forced the civilization process of the Black Spirit Race but focused more on improving the quality of the Black Spirit Race itself. From his viewpoint, as long as the species itself became perfect, it would be more effective to help them develop.

The racial characteristics of the Black Spirit Race lay in its mind communication network, which improved communication efficiency and knowledge penetration rate. Their Race Specialty was related to the mind, and the totem would subtly enhance the mental and spiritual strength of the entire race.

The Black Spirit Race was also very prolific. After more than ten years of reproduction, several generations of newborns had been born, and the population had grown a lot.

At this moment, in the center of the Germinal Tribe, a large group of children played around an adult, who happened to be the leader of the Germinal Tribe.

The leader of the Germinal Tribe was wearing a coarse animal skin robe and holding a simple scepter made out of Prophecy Stones. His dress was very different from the other tribesmen, who were not wearing clothes.

Countless years before they were transformed by the Evolution Cube, the Black Spirit Race had produced a very small number of variants, which could build a mind communication network on their own instead of utilizing the Prophecy Stones. These variants were known as 'Sages'.

The current leader of the Germinal Tribe was one of the strongest variants, with his mental network able to accommodate most individuals. At the same time, he was also the spokesperson of their 'Black Star God', so he was hailed as the Great Sage.

"Great Sage, why do we worship the Black Star God?" The group of toddlers crowded around the Germinal Tribe leader, chattering away in his mental network.

Lifting his scepter, the Germinal Tribe leader spoke in equal seriousness and fanaticism. "The Black Star God has brought us the gospel for evolution, as well as the fire of our civilization. He is the omnipresent greatness."

"I don't believe you. I feel that you are stronger than him, Great Sage!" One of the toddlers laughed.

"Humph, you know nothing about power." The Germinal Tribe leader pointed at a battleship suspended in the sky with his scepter. "Do you see that? That's called a spaceship. It's what brought us here from our ancestral land. Just relying on our powers, we would not even have reached here in ten thousand years, but Black Star God brought us here in an instant. That is the power of a God."

"Ancestral land? This place is not our ancestral land?"

"Sigh, our ancestral land was long taken by others. If the Black Star God had not led us away, maybe..."

The Germinal Tribe leader sighed again and shook his head.

At this moment, hundreds of black specks appeared in the clear blue sky. They floated down slowly toward the Germinal Tribe and caused a commotion within the tribe. Many of the tribe members gathered in the square, watching the descending spaceships.

The hatches opened, and Psionic Prime flew out and landed in front of the leader of the Germinal Tribe. The Black Spirit Race scattered, but they were not nervous at all.

In their eyes, this sort of metal creature was the servant of their Black Star God.

"I'm the Chief Apostle under Lord Black Star. My lord has commanded me to take you away from this planet."

The Germinal Tribe leader stood up, speaking jerkily with vocal cords that had yet to fully develop.

"Where is the Black Star God taking us?"

"Your new home."

With a lot of investments from the financial groups, the Black Star Army had sufficient funds to purchase engineering equipment as well as to prepare to build troops. The process was smooth.

After a month of preparations, the construction team of the army finally departed officially under the universe's interested eyes, full of manpower and resources to develop the Flickering World.

Lagi, Reynold, Sylvia, and Herlous were directly involved, and Han Xiao was only responsible for remote supervision since he wanted to go to the dynasty to avoid any danger. He had left the blueprint for the construction of the site with them, so he did not need to be present.

On the day that the construction team set off, Han Xiao arrived at the stargate leading to the Central Galaxy with only a few Black Star Guards and Aurora with him.

This was to avoid danger but also to visit the various Beyond Grade A allies of the dynasty. After all, they would be working together for many years, so it was necessary to build relationships.

At the same time, he also prepared to visit those future famous characters of the dynasty that he recalled.

The version update would take several decades, and the dynasty would experience a change in power. His cooperation with the dynasty would last a long time, so he needed to have wider vision. For the sake of his future, it was necessary to build good relations with the powerful people of the future in advance, granting him a louder voice within the dynasty.

Sweeping his eyes over Feidin and the rest, Han Xiao turned his head to look at Aurora in the pilot's seat and nodded.

"Let's go."

Aurora swiped her finger on the control screen, and the spaceship slowly moved into the stargate.

At the same moment, Ames and Hila arrived at the stargate at the edge of the Shattered Star Ring.

Turning back, Hila had a complicated expression.

She had a hunch that it would be a long time before she returned.

The Beyond Grade A realm...

A slim hand rested on her shoulder, and turning back, Hila saw Ames standing there with a light smile.

"Let's go."

"Sigh... I got it."

Hila recollected her thoughts and also directed the spaceship to enter the stargate.

[1] Probably named so because you need to donate a liver to get enough money to buy everything Back

Chapter 930: The Prototype Plan of Three Great Calamities

In the Flickering World, the Purple River Star System was one of the seven Star Systems that belonged to the Black Star Army. It was located at the edge of the Garu Star Cluster and was one of the important gateways into the Star Cluster. At this time, from the stargate of the Purple River Star System slowly sailed a huge Black Star Army fleet. This was the construction force led by Herlous.

There was a large number of Black Star Army spaceships awaiting Herlous' arrival next to the stargate station. This was originally the first exploration fleet. Now that the exploration had been completed, the same fleet was transformed into construction personnel, awaiting instructions from the higher ups.

In the meeting room of the flagship, Herlous was having a discussion with the senior officers such as Sylvia and Lagi to go through the construction plans.

"Purple River, Long Day, Ponzale, Orlando, Fenrir, Sigma, and Ednea—these seven Star Systems belong to our Black Star Army, and we have to first set the infrastructure foundation before carefully sculpting and slowly transforming the Star System." Herlous had a serious expression on.

While he usually behaved in a lazy manner, he still acted properly and seriously when faced with Han Xiao's tasks.

Sylvia nodded. "We should first establish the stargate transportation network within the seven galaxies to form a whole and facilitate fleet transportation. Through our exploration, the network has already taken shape, which is convenient for us. After this, we should install the army's own warning and space monitoring devices, and we'll lay a large scale quantum network base station to place the seven Star Systems under the management of the artificial intelligence system."

The Black Star Army had to establish its own infrastructure to take over the seven Star Systems and make it into a seamless whole, strong as an iron board.

"According to the plans left by the Army Commander, we need to focus on the two Star System gateways, Ponzale and Purple River. We must firmly control the entry and exit stargates for the main traffic routes. These stargate stations were originally made by the dynasty, and now that the station is under our control, we have to spare some troops for the stations.

"In terms of planetary terraforming, the priority should go to the army bases and resource mining bases. The galactic cities and transit stations will only come in handy when the Star Field is opened, so we can put those off until a later date.

"The blueprint also states that the Sigma Star System will be the logistics base of the army within the Flickering World. There will also be a need to focus on the transformation and the construction of a large number of barracks, military factories, and airports there..."

The construction scope for seven Star Systems was a monumental task. Han Xiao only provided a blueprint, and the specific action plans would need to be developed by those responsible for each star system.

While everyone was discussing, Lagi maintained his usual style, not caring about anything and serving as a mascot.

A plan was quickly formulated, and under the command of Herlous, the construction troops began to proceed in an orderly manner. The stargate passage was set up, various devices were laid, and they took the facilities that had been left over during the exploration to be reused, saving a lot of resources.

At the same time, Bloodshed Land, Klent, and the rest of the dynasty's allies also started to construct their territories. The entire Flickering World entered a period of rapid development.

Rural development was a long-term project. It would take a lot of time to raise the region to the standard of the currently explored universe. The seven Star Systems that Han Xiao had chosen were all important areas in his past life. Han Xiao had drawn out the renovation plans according to his memory, and it was expected to take decades to completely construct everything on the blueprint. It was estimated that the next phase of exploration for the Crimson Dynasty would not be held back for so long. As long as at least two Star Systems were complete in each Star Field, the second phase of exploration would then proceed.

While the construction team was in full swing, the mechanical lives and Black Spirit Race also arrived at their new, separate home planets.

The Sigma Star System was a central area of the Garu Star Cluster, rich in resources. It bordered the other two Star Systems, Ednea and Orlando, occupying a vast area.

Planet Apostle was one of the resource rich planets within this Star System, which was named by Han Xiao. The whole planet was gray, with rich mineral veins and metal resources. Although it was not a habitable planet in the conventional sense, it was very suitable to host mechanical lives.

Dozens of spaceships landed slowly on this gray wasteland. The Psionic Prime disembarked from the spaceship with the hundred thousand mechanical lives and glanced around. The undulating wasteland extended to the end of the horizon, and there was no greenery in sight, only endless gray rocks and flying sand.

"This will be our homeland in the future."

The Psionic Prime held his spear and directed everyone to begin building the city immediately.

If it was a normal civilization, eighty percent of them would collapse from the mental burden of establishing a civilization on this desolate planet. However, to the mechanical lifeforms, this emotion did not exist, and their mentality leaned toward a colonialist mindset.

With the engineering equipment provided, coupled with their natural talents, the speed of the mechanical lives in building cities was incredibly fast.

If one overlooked the planet, they would quickly see a metal area appearing on the surface and spreading out to form a city of machines.

First of all, a large number of assembly lines were built. With sufficient resources, the mechanical lives were assembled. A portion of the existing life forms consumed their energy to synthesize their own tinder gene codes, incubating the second generation of mechanical lives.

Having a large quantity of soldiers was the specialty of a Mechanical Race.

At the same time, they built specialized equipment that allowed them to excavate the underground veins and resources, smash apart stones, and gather all these raw materials into the warehouse.

Without any enemies, the construction efficiency was frightening, and under the command of the Apostles and the Psionic Prime, the mechanical lives' civilization slowly unfolded.

On the other side, the Black Spirit Race also arrived at their new home, Planet New Black Spirit.

This planet was different from the Planet Apostle. It was a habitable planet with vast vegetation and verdant forests. There were many indigenous beasts with mild temperaments.

The migratory fleet landed on a fertile plain, and the Black Spirit Race rushed down from the spaceship. Their newly evolved green eyes curiously took in the scenes.

"This is our new homeland?"

"It seems even more beautiful."

One of the spaceships fired a traction beam, lowering the Black Star statue onto the plain. They were unable to move the entire city, but landmarks could still be transported.

To the Black Spirit Race, the statue of Black Star was just like their landmark, and its function was similar to a 'civilization monument'. This monument gave their race hope. They could do without the city but not without the statue.

Han Xiao required the Black Spirit Race to develop itself during the decades when the version was undergoing an update, so he could only intervene in the Black Spirit Race's civilization process. The spaceships that transported the Black Spirit Race were outfitted with many engineering devices and stayed to help them construct their new homes.

Under the gazes of the Black Spirit Race, an army member handed a communicator to the Germinal Tribe leader.

"This contains Knowledge that the Black Star God is gifting you. You can learn it and use it to transform your race."

The Germinal Tribe leader carefully switched it on, and a list popped up. Within it was all sorts of information compiled by Han Xiao. It was a technological tree tailored to the racial characteristics of the Black Spirit Race, ranging from basic to advanced Knowledges.

Planning out a technology tree for the entire race would ensure that their development direction would not deviate.

Thanks to their mind network, the Black Spirit Race quickly found out about the contents and started worshipping the statue.

"Many thanks to Black Star God for this generous bestowal!"

The Germinal Tribe leader was very moved. This emotion spread to everyone else, turning their faith even more fanatical.

Their Black Star God had passed down divine knowledge to them, which had historical significance for the entire race. This scene would forever be inscribed in the inheritance memory of the Black Spirit Race.

While there were varied differences between the mechanical lives and the Black Spirit Race, they shared similarities in the fact that they had a hive mentality. One utilized a mind network, while the other accessed the quantum network, which could highly condense the productivity of their race. Thus, all races with such characteristics typically had unparalleled development potential.

The Black Spirit Race was akin to the Bug Tribe. So long as they were placed on the right track, they would enter the fast lane of civilization development. As for the mechanical lives, they were even more overpowered, starting with a high technological level. All they lacked was land and population, which were easily expanded.

Han Xiao had high hopes for these two races, so he had specifically placed them in different Star Systems, hoping to give them ample room for development.

Speaking of which, if both of them developed, they could be treated as Calamities that could shake the balance of the world. If one added in the players that were supposed to be the fourth Calamity...

Han Xiao himself occupied three of the four Calamities!

In the past month, countless people were paying attention to the construction of the Flickering World by the Crimson Dynasty and its allies. This was the most eye-catching event in the Universe.

Like the others, the Black Star Army also poured all its effort into development, investing a lot of manpower and resources within.

Taking advantage of this time, the Limitless Financial Group finally started to manipulate the network of interests that the Black Star Army had within the Shattered Star Ring.

Chapter 931: Trouble Surfaces

The Colin Group was one of the local financial groups within the Shattered Star Ring. It was well-known for its large business scope that encompassed areas such as resource mining, logistics, and transportation, as well as the production of processed materials. While it was not a galactic-level financial group, it was still a sizable company in cooperation with many planetary and Star System level civilizations. At the same time, this group was also partnered with the Black Star Army and provided business channels for the army.

Many similar organizations cooperated with the Black Star Army, partly for the Evolution Cube, and partly because they were attracted to the influence of the Black Star Army in the area. Their identities as Black Star Army collaborators could bring a lot of convenience to their businesses.

The Colin Group, as one of the first companies to cooperate with the Black Star Army, had experienced a booming performance in the past few years, and their prospects were broad, but at this moment, all the corporate executives and shareholders were gathered together in the conference room of the Colin Group with frowning faces.

The current head of the group, Colin Duller, sat at the head seat. His expression was terrible, and he was suppressing his fury.

"The Hebrew and Sayde Civilizations have terminated their cooperation with us. They not only withdrew the planetary mining rights that we purchased but also cancelled the long-term contract for the supply of materials. Furthermore, I was negotiating with the Wiese members before, which would have allowed us to obtain a new business area. The negotiation had already come to an end, but the Wiese actually went back on the previous terms and chose to cooperate with others. Our situation now is very bad."

One of the upper echelons sighed. "That's right. Many of the heads for the civilization departments that had cooperated happily with us have now cut off all contact. This is not normal and should be our competitors pulling some underhanded moves..."

"Humph, I know who they are." Colin snorted coldly. "A while ago, the Limitless Financial Group sought me out, wanting to purchase the Colin Group, but I rejected them. The recent movements were most likely made by them."

"What, there was such a thing‽"

"Why didn't we know that the Limitless Financial Group had contacted us?"

A few of them displayed expressions of shock while some of them remained silent. Obviously, they had found out about this matter.

Colin's tone was furious. "I've already inquired about it. The Limitless Financial Group has been acquiring companies in the Shattered Star Ring recently, and those businesses that did not agree were more or less suppressed. I heard that the Limitless Financial Group has decided to enter Shattered Star Ring due to the development of the Flickering World, and they are preparing to invest in the large scale construction of a factory in the Hebrew and Sayde civilizations. They should have made a deal behind our back, so both of them terminated the cooperation with us."

At this moment, the second largest shareholder of the company, who had always been dissatisfied with Colin, suddenly sneered.

"It's not only that. There are also several important cooperative businesses that have stopped businesses with us. Several civilizations no longer approve our loans, and our management level employees were also poached, leaving a significant gap... Now our business has shrunk by more than thirty percent, and our price on the stock market has plummeted. As I said earlier, you should not have rejected the Limitless Financial Group, one of the largest financial groups in the universe. There's no disadvantage to turning them against us."

Hearing this, Colin's face was pale.

He also knew that they could not compare to the brand or financial power of the Limitless Financial Group. If there was an opportunity, many would cooperate with them, even abandoning their previous partners, as the Limitless Financial Group would bring immense benefits.

The more Colin thought about it, the angrier he got, and he heavily thumped on the table, leaving behind an indentation. He gritted his teeth.

"Don't even think about it. The Colin Group is my hard work, and I will not agree to the acquisition requirements of the Limitless Financial Group!"

The second largest shareholder sneered. "How are you going to solve the current problems? If there is no way, the group will collapse sooner or later. Everyone here is a shareholder. If you want to gamble, you have to go through us first."

Colin fell silent for a while before shaking his head. "I have no method at the moment..."

A document was thrown out by the shareholder, landing on the table. He coldly laughed. "Since you have no methods, just sign this shareholder acquisition document."

Colin's expression changed. He stared at the shareholder. "You've been bought over by them‽"

"Bought over? I was just acting in the interests of our group."

The second largest shareholder laughed and surveyed the shocked or calm faces of the upper echelons.

Another large shareholder understood the idea and said, "Colin, just agree. We will have a hard time contending with such a large financial group at that level. Besides, their purchase price is very reasonable, and after joining the Limitless Financial Group, our businesses can be further developed with their support."

This seemed to be the signal to get many of the upper echelons to open their mouths.

"You, all of you..." Colin's eyes widened. How could he not understand that all of them had been bought over? The sum of all these people's shares was enough to overrule his decisions.

To think that the board had been infiltrated like this!

Even those hesitating shareholders were also staring at Colin with hopeful eyes now.

Colin's eyes were unreadable. "If I don't agree, are you all planning to overthrow me?"

The second largest shareholder indifferently replied, "That will depend on the strategy you can come up with. If you want to drag this whole group into the abyss, don't blame us for saving ourselves."

Colin stared at the acquisition book on the table, and hesitated. Without a word, he grabbed the book and read it carefully before signing the agreement with a heavy expression.

Pa pa pa...

A sudden applause could be heard outside the door, and the room opened, showing a man clapping as he walked in, a confident smile on his face.

"A wise choice."

Colin looked over frowning, but before he could ask, the second largest shareholder beat him to it.

"This is one of the upper echelons of the Limitless Financial Group, Mr. Madick."

"Oh, turns out you're the guy who bought us out." Colin's words were sarcastic.

"Hehe, there's no need to look at me like that. In the future, the Colin Group will be an arm of the Limitless, and we'll all be colleagues." Madick waved his hands while lightly smiling. "I'm here to tell everyone that there will be no major changes to the original decision-making structure of the group. You all will still remain as the backbone."

Madick eyed everyone before continuing. "However, there needs to be an adjustment in business direction. We need to immediately terminate the cooperation with the Black Star Army."

"Why?" Colin could not understand.

Acquisition was one thing. What did it have to do with their business partner?

"Oh, our Limitless Financial Group has signed an agreement to cooperate and develop the Bloodshed Land. The Bloodshed Land is prepared to emulate the Black Star Army and build its own interest union, so it requires many organizations to join. Every business we buy must be converted to a partner of the Bloodshed Land, to provide them with channels to expand their business."

Madick smiled indifferently.

Colin frowned before a look of understanding flashed past his eyes.

He had also attended the previous Black Star Party, and Sorokin had been there, but the latter had chosen to invest in Bloodshed Land and was now using it to attack the partners of the Black Star Army. As someone local to the Shattered Star Ring, a bold conjecture appeared in Colin's mind...

The Limitless Financial Group did not just wish to enter the Shattered Star Ring; it wanted to attack the Black Star Army!

All of them were just pawns that had been caught up in the storm!

The Colin Group was just one of many examples. During this period, many of the local businesses within the Shattered Star Ring were acquired or controlled, either defeated directly by sheer banknotes or simply willing to go under the banner of the Limitless Financial Group.

For those that did not agree, there were many methods that the Limitless Financial Group could use.

For example, in response to conflicts, they could rally the smaller shareholders to overthrow the larger shareholders. They could also buy out some key personnel or invest in building factories to attract the civilizations to hinder the businesses of some companies. The Limitless Financial Group was well experienced in this.

If someone would not compromise, they would be suppressed to death sooner or later, and they would lose more than what they would have originally obtained.

The Limitless Financial Group had no way to directly shake the businesses of a hegemon like the Black Star Army, so they could only erode them bit by bit. To the local enterprises, this universe level top financial group was like a giant crocodile that they could not compete with.

You might be rich, but the Limitless Financial Group... is especially wealthy!

Under such operations, the Limitless Financial Group, having worked behind the scenes for several months, acquired many of the local businesses, forming a large number of business channels. They strongly inserted themselves into the Shattered Star Ring market with a stable footing.

At the same time, the Bloodshed Land released a joint announcement with the Limitless Financial Group to publicly announce their cooperation. The Bloodshed Land also mentioned that they would expand their business and carry out a transformation of their organization. While it was not specifically stated, everyone in Shattered Star Ring knew that their target was the Black Star Army.

"The Limitless Financial Group is working in depth with Bloodshed Land‽"

In the headquarters of the Army, Sylvia looked at the report on her hand, her face revealing a troubled expression.

"The Bloodshed Land plans to steal our businesses. There has been a conflict of interest on both sides, so those organizations that have been acquired by the Limitless Financial Group have terminated their cooperation and turned to the Bloodshed Land." The secretary next to Sylvia shook his head, his tone worried.

"They don't want the quota for the Evolution Cube anymore?" Sylvia frowned.

"This... I'm not too sure, but most of the acquired organizations are private, and their demand for the Evolution Cube is not great."

Hearing this, Sylvia nodded.

That was the case, as private organizations were different from civilizations. Even if they required evolutions, they would probably have purchased slots for all their members in the past few years. The main reason they cooperated was to maintain the influence created by the network of interests. Now that they had been acquired, they could only be swayed to the intentions of the Limitless Financial Group.

What businesses relied on to compete was their power, wealth, and influence, and force could not be applied to them. Furthermore, with the Bloodshed Land as a Beyond Grade A organization and an ally of the dynasty, this provided a suitable shield for the Limitless Financial Group to act.

Teacher was right. The Limitless Financial Group did not have any good intentions at all.

Sylvia secretly huffed and looked at the detailed report.

While the Limitless Financial Group was huge, it would be impossible to fight against all the businesses in the entire Star Field. That was especially so for the civilizations; it was impossible for them to give up on cooperating for the Evolution Cube. The Limitless Financial Group could only target the private organizations, and because each acquisition also required a lot of money, the larger organizations had not been targeted for the time being.

Thus, so far, the Black Star Army had only lost a few business channels, but it was far from the level of hemorrhaging. Only their peripheral businesses were affected. Their core businesses like the Evolution Cube, Flickering World development, and planet mining were still stable.

But... they had to guard against any further upsets.

As she thought of this, Sylvia had a severe expression as she took out her communicator.

"I have to inform my teacher immediately!"

Chapter 932: The Capacity of a Beyond Grade A

At the same time, in the dynasty's central territory, a small unmarked fleet was docked above a huge blue planet. The planet hosted one of the most famous interstellar cities in the Crimson Dynasty, with a prosperous economy and a huge population.

This fleet came from the branch of the Black Star Army in Constellation Corridor. Because of his long stay in the dynasty this time, Han Xiao immediately dispatched the local army fleet the moment he arrived in order to utilize the fleet's machinery factory to produce machinery to while away the time on the way.

The Crimson Dynasty knew that Han Xiao had come over to the Central Galaxy with the purpose of avoiding any danger, so he did not need to proceed to Planet Crimson Ring to report. Except for the secret military areas, he was free to roam about the territory of the dynasty, and the upper echelons of the dynasty would not restrict him.

Han Xiao was practicing his Energy Training Techniques whilst searching for the famous people of the dynasty in the future. He had arrived in this interstellar city to visit just one person.

The No.16 Comprehensive Superpower Academy of the dynasty was a first-class university and a famous facility on this planet. The goal of Han Xiao's trip was precisely this academy. In his memories, a future Beyond Grade A Dynasty member had graduated from this college.

According to the data from his past life, this Beyond Grade A was recruited into the academy between the years 709 and 712 on the Galaxy Calendar. This was the early stage of the update from Version 3.0 to Version 4.0, this exact period.

Because his fleet was unmarked, the arrival of Han Xiao did not cause a sensation on the planet. Only the upper echelons of the academy were notified, and the principal immediately dropped all his affairs to personally greet them.

At this moment, in one of the campuses of the dynasty's No.16 Comprehensive Superpower Academy, Han Xiao took Aurora with him as they walked down the tree-lined road. Their faces were concealed by a virtual disguise, and their real identities could not be seen.

The artificially planted trees helped to ward off the shine from the artificial sun in the sky, and the sunlight passing through their canopies was cut into slivers of golden specks. The was also a sparkling river beside the road, where several students were frolicking in the water. Further ahead, there was a patch of grass where students of difference races mingled with each other in discussion, and occasionally, a few students flew past in midair holding books to rush to class. Everywhere was full of youthfulness.

"So nice..." Looking at this scene, a slight longing and envy appeared in Aurora's eyes.

Her childhood was akin to hell, and she had never experienced such a normal growth process.

Gazing at the scene, Han Xiao suddenly felt a little sad. The life of a normal person is already too far away for me...

Lowering his head, Aurora's profile, under the morning light appeared particularly pure and sacred, and her long eyelashes twitched gently.

"Your Excellency Black Star, the Pugilist Department is in front of us."

At this time, the voice of the principal sounded by his ear. Han Xiao withdrew his gaze from Aurora, looking forward at a tall building complex. There were spherical gravity training spaces visible to the naked eye, and many of the pugilists were also practicing.

The three of them walked around the teaching area for a while and walked past a classroom. A new class of pugilists were in the middle of a cultural class. When Han Xiao looked in, his gaze immediately landed on an unremarkable person belonging to the Galaxy Human Race. This plain and unassuming face was very familiar in his eyes...

Karlot, the Beyond Grade A directly under the dynasty in the later versions. After 'Dark Lord' Clotti died, he took over his position, and his combat ability also reached the peak of Beyond Grade A...

The memories of his past flashed through Han Xiao's mind in an instant, and Han Xiao's eyes flashed inexplicably.

Seeing that Han Xiao had stopped and did not move, the principal was a little confused. He looked over and saw Karlot seated there. He hesitated before he asked, "Your Excellency Black Star, do you recognize this freshman?"

Han Xiao shook his head. "I just felt that he has a lot of potential."

Hearing this, the principal immediately looked carefully, but he could not see anything special about Karlot. He was a little dissatisfied in his heart, but he could not help paying attention to the opinions of a Beyond Grade A. The principal secretly took out his communicator to check Karlot's files, but he found out that the freshman had yet to awaken his Super-Gene, and thus, his performance was also at the bottom of the cohort.

The majority of the freshmen in the college were ordinary people, as the college would also conduct tests to select the good seedlings to start education earlier. Within this one-and-a-half-year period, if they could not awaken their Super genes, they would be asked to leave.

"I hope to be able to chat with him," Han Xiao said.

"This... ok." The principal hesitated a little but finally agreed.

Han Xiao walked into a random empty classroom, and when the bell rang, the hallways got noisy. The door of the classroom opened, and the principal walked in with Karlot.

"Sit." Han Xiao smiled.

"Why do you want to meet me? I, I didn't do anything wrong." Karlot stood dumbly, his expression cramped and speech awkward.

His family were all ordinary people who ran a small business. However, his parents wanted him to become a Super so that this family business could obtain the social welfare treatment that was unique to Supers. Thus, they allowed him to go to the college. Karlot had no opinion and thus took the admission exam, being lucky enough to pass it.

As a freshman who had never come into contact with any Supers, Karlot had only met the principal once at the opening ceremony. However, the principal had approached him personally today, which made him anxious as to whether he had broken any rules.

"Haha, you didn't do anything wrong. I just wanted to chat with you." Han Xiao laughed.

Karlot finally heaved a sigh of relief, closely scrutinizing Han Xiao's face before he asked curiously, "You... who are you? I don't recognize you. Why are you looking for me?"

"Oh, my name is Black Star. Maybe you've heard of my name. I'm an ally of the Crimson Dynasty, and I think that you have potential. Are you willing to join my Black Star Army?" Han Xiao smiled.

The purpose of this trip was to search for potential strong candidates, but because Karlot's starting identity was too low, he was not spotted early. If Han Xiao could bring such a power over, he would not hesitate.

Seeing this, the principal began to doubt his own eyes. It was impolite to poach someone in front of him, but he did not dare say anything. It was even more surprising, seeing that Black Star would personally invite this person without any extraordinary features.

"What is the Black Star Army?" Karlot opened his eyes wide, a look of puzzlement. He never paid attention to interstellar matters and did not even know what their Dynasty Ruler was called.

Han Xiao's face cramped up, and he threw a glance to Aurora. Aurora could only explain it patiently to him.

Karlot seemed to only understand half of it. "So, you guys are mercenaries?"

"You can put it this way, I guess." Han Xiao was helpless. "If you join our army, not only will you obtain better teachings, you can also obtain more benefits. I..."

Before waiting for Han Xiao to finish, Karlot began shaking his head. "I'm not going. Dad only sent me here to improve our family condition. He does not allow me to go out to fight and kill. If he learns about this, he will beat me up."

Hearing this sentence, Han Xiao did not know whether to laugh or cry. This reason was quite refreshing.

The universe indeed was not lacking people who wanted to be Super just for the benefits. However, once they obtained the strength, their mentalities would undergo a change. Thus, he could understand why Karlot was thinking like this right now.

In his previous life, Karlot himself belonged to the late-bloomer protagonist character archetype. He was honest, clumsy, and had a slow growth rate, but he slowly stepped forward until he stood at the peak of all Supers. During his peak, he could even kill ordinary Beyond Grade As without losing his breath.

After graduating from this official superpower academy, the military and some government departments came to recruit him. At that time, Karlot finally had his own beliefs and joined the army against the will of his family, starting his legendary career. However, now, Karlot was still a naive child in Han Xiao's eyes.

Every Beyond Grade A was unique. If he rashly changed Karlot's future, he might not grow up like his previous life. After all, guys like Karlot were not like Hila, who had the innate potential to hit Beyond Grade A.

Seeing that no one was talking, Karlot scratched his head and hesitantly asked, "If there's nothing else, can I go?"

"Alright." Han Xiao put his thoughts aside and smiled as he nodded. He decided not to push Karlot so far right now as he did not have the value to be poached.

But he had also helped Karlot indirectly, since he showed this student's importance. The principal would definitely try to focus on his training, and he could use this time to foster a closer relationship with him.

Watching Karlot leave, Han Xiao temporarily bid farewell to the principal, returning to his spaceship.

As soon as he entered the cabin, his communicator rang. It was Sylvia on the line.

"Teacher, there's a situation with the Limitless Financial Group!"

Han Xiao's eyes flashed. "Explain in detail."

Sylvia quickly summarized the incidents, and Han Xiao frowned as he connected the picture of him conversing with Sorokin. An understanding came to him.

"Them entering the Shattered Star Ring market is false. Their true motive is to deal with me."

"Teacher, you're saying..."

Han Xiao sighed. "The Limitless Financial Group acts as an economic and commercial enterprise on the surface, but its true motive is to support the Bloodshed Land in opposing us, interfering with our development. I've been waiting to see what the pressure brought about by the Evolutionary Totems would be, and it turns out it's in this form. There should be many backers behind the Limitless Financial Group this time, likely the federation and the church as well."

"Then, what should we do‽ There's no way to resolve this!" Sylvia's expression was solemn.

Han Xiao was also tied up. In terms of commercial activities, the Limitless Financial Group was the undisputed ruler. The core businesses of the army were not impacted, but he was unable to prevent Sorokin from acquiring his partners. That would later cause a negative effect as his other business partners would choose to dissolve any relationships in order not to be targeted.

This was a straightforward strategy of attacking using their own abilities.

"If we hope to compete with the Limitless Financial Group, we must turn our dispersed capital into a whole. Use this external pressure to facilitate internal cohesion among our partners, encourage them to unite and form an existence similar to that of a Chamber of Commerce. We can help each other resist the malicious acquisition of the Limitless Financial Group."

Sylvia thought about it before nodding in agreement. "This method is not bad."

"Alas, there is no method to tackle the root cause. We can only stop the damage from spreading." Han Xiao's eyes flashed with a cold light. "After a period of time, I'll have the mechanical host I left in the headquarters go to the Bloodshed Land and find Heber for... a good talk!"

After discussing the countermeasures, Han Xiao hung up, and his expression sank.

Now that the Black Star Army had gained the opportunity to shine in the world and develop rapidly, Sorokin attempted to deliberately drag them down, preventing them from developing peacefully.

He wanted to destroy the network of interests Han Xiao had spent years trying to build up!

Although this method of Sorokin's could not shake the core businesses, it was very sinister and disgusting, and it would kill the future of the army!

He wanted to contact Sorokin for questioning, but he quickly banished this idea. With that old fox's character, he would definitely use all kinds of business activities as an excuse, and there would be no way to express his own dissatisfaction.

Since he knew how Sorokin was going to reply, there was no point calling him.

If Heber promised to cooperate, it means that he's taking this opportunity to develop his forces. He, of course, won't mind knocking me down in the process. When I advance to level 300, I'll go and chat with him.

Han Xiao clenched his fists with a heavy expression.

Since he could not deal with Sorokin, he would cause trouble for Heber!

Ty-Ty is not giving me face at all. If you think that this wave of trading is very profitable for you, don't blame me for destroying your prestige later!

Chapter 933: Black Star's Tour

In the Bloodshed Land's palace, Jorde excitedly reported, "... In summary, we've obtained many new channels of business in a short amount of time, and our operations will double at the very least this year."

A burly figure stood beside the window, and Heber listened to the report.

Jorde then continued reading the report. "The Black Star Army completed their transformation many years back and diversified their operations. We didn't have the Evolution Cube, so despite having Klent's support, our transformation was very slow, and we were still restricted by the quality of the employment missions that we received. About seventy to eighty percent of our funds come from various armed employment missions. After working together with the Limitless Financial Group, they've provided great aid to our transformation, and the embryonic state of our transformation is already complete."

The Black Star Army and Bloodshed Land were both Beyond Grade A organizations, but their operation direction was different. Under Han Xiao's lead, the Black Star Army managed to diversify their operations through the Evolution Cube. They had both military and financial strength. As for the Bloodshed Land, they were a classic poor army with their influence and operations being very limited. This was a problem that had been troubling the Bloodshed Land.

With the help of the Limitless Financial Group, Heber's problem was now resolved. As long as they continued down this path, the Bloodshed Land would no longer be a group of boorish individuals who only knew how to fight wars. They would have the right to fight with the Black Star Army as a private organization.

Heber turned around and calmly said, "Good job."

Jorde hesitated for a moment and could not help but ask, "Your Excellency, just what kind of a deal did you make with the Limitless Financial Group? Why are they willing to help us without holding back?"

"It is just an exchange of benefits." Heber glanced at him. "They wish to enter the Shattered Star Ring and want to borrow our influence to gain a spot in the local market. Humph, although their targets are the organizations that cooperate with the Black Star Army, we are also a Beyond Grade A organization, and it won't be a loss for them to join us."

This was the reason on the surface. As for the deeper intention of their deal, Heber was not planning to inform his subordinates.

Although Heber did not say anything else, Jorde could sense that this matter was not so simple. The Limitless Financial Group did not approach the Black Star Army but went to the second best option instead. They were obviously targeting the Black Star Army.

Jorde broke out into cold sweat as he thought about the possible meaning behind the cooperation and did not dare continue asking. He still wanted to live to the day where he could hug his grandchildren.

Jorde then wiped away his sweat and left the room. Heber was the only one left, and he continued looking out the window. A long while later, the corner of his lips curled up slightly.

Although he maintained his calm appearance in front of his subordinates, he was actually very happy.

He was not bothered about whether the Limitless Financial Group would succeed; he only wanted to make use of this opportunity to develop. The losses of the Black Star Army were of no consequence to him. The both of them were the dynasty's allies but also competitors. He would be more than happy to see the Black Star Army suffer a huge loss.

On the other side, Karlot, who had rejected Han Xiao's invitation, returned to his dormitory, and his friends immediately crowded over with curiosity.

"Hey, why did the principal look for you?"

Karlot was extremely honest, and his results were at the bottom. Thus, his relationship with the others was not too bad.

A few of his friends had seen the principal approaching Karlot at the end of the lesson and thought that he had done something wrong. Thus, they all crowded over with concern.

Karlot scratched his head and said, "Nothing much. Someone wanted to meet me."

"Who? He is actually able to get the principal to personally invite you!" one of Karlot's dormitory mates exclaimed. He was the one with the best background in the entire dormitory, but he was still far from the level of the principal. Karlot's family was extremely ordinary, so he could not help being puzzled.

"He said that he is called Black Star and asked me to join the Black Star Army," Karlot said helplessly.

The moment he said these words, the entire room fell silent, and a look of disbelief could be seen on everyone's face.

"That legendary Black Star‽"

"Are you kidding me‽ Why would he look for you‽"

Seeing his dormitory mates' expressions, Karlot could not help but ask with doubt, "Do all of you know him?"

"My goodness, don't tell me you don't even know who Black Star is‽" One of his friends almost fainted.

"I... I hadn't heard of him before," Karlot said with a tinge of embarrassment. "Is he really a bigshot?"

"He isn't just a bigshot! He is a Beyond Grade A Super! The peak of individual strength and an existence who can chat with the Dynasty Ruler!" One of his friends then began describing Han Xiao's history.

The others then surrounded Karlot and showered with him plenty of questions. Karlot briefly explained the situation, but with his lousy expressive vocabulary, it took a while for the others to understand what had happened.

That handsome dormitory mate of his then could not help but notice a sour feeling in his heart. Why did such a good thing fall on the head of this bottom-ranked idiot instead of him?

At this moment, another one of his dormitory mates then realized something and asked, "Did... you accept Black Star's invitation?"

"I didn't agree," Karlot replied uneasily.

"You actually rejected the opportunity to join the Black Star Army‽" Everyone was truly speechless. "You're truly an idiot! This is an opportunity to change your fate! Ordinary people like us would never be able to enter the Black Star Army! You... you actually..."

Seeing everyone say so, Karlot fell into a daze and started to doubt his own choice.

Did I really make the wrong choice?

I'd better ask my family first.

Karlot then took out his communicator and ran to the side to contact his family. That handsome dormitory mate then looked at Karlot's back, and a look of dense jealousy and resentment could be seen in his eyes.

Why him? Why‽ Why did he obtain such an opportunity but not know how to treasure it? He is truly idiotic to the extreme! Why would such a legendary figure take notice of such an individual!

He originally liked Karlot and was willing to take care of Karlot, but now, he was only filled with disgust toward Karlot.

The next day, Han Xiao temporarily ignored the frustration of the financial groups and continued monitoring Karlot. He noticed something interesting.

The event had already spread throughout the entire level, and the attitudes of all the students changed greatly. A portion of them fawned over him while others excluded him.

"Because of my actions yesterday, his entire school life has been rewritten by me. He can no longer be a transparent individual like in his previous life..." Han Xiao shook his head and had a greater understanding of his status as a bigshot.

For Karlot to be dragged into the storm early on, the effects on his growth would be unknown. It could be a good or bad thing.

However, his actions had definitely helped him. Any individual capable of becoming a Beyond Grade A would have grit in them and be unwilling to concede defeat. Difficulties would only spur on his potential, and he would welcome all problems head on. Who knew if Karlot had such a character? Perhaps the intense competition in the school would allow Karlot to experience a change further.

"If that's the case, why don't I aggravate the situation further?" Han Xiao stroked his chin.

After waiting for a moment, the bell went off, and the students left their classrooms. Han Xiao then openly called out.

"Karlot."

Upon hearing someone call his name, Karlot turned around. Upon seeing Han Xiao in the same clothes as the previous day, he recognized Han Xiao's identity and was startled. "Black... Black Star. It's you again."

His voice was not loud, but it seemed to have a magical force. The students in the surroundings all stopped and looked at Han Xiao with burning gazes.

"You seem to be very nervous?" Han Xiao ignored the crowd and smiled at Karlot. Although others were unable to see his true appearance, he could still display emotions.

"My father asked me to thank you, but he doesn't wish for me to interact with you too much," Karlot said with a nervous look.

Han Xiao was not too bothered by the response. Raising his finger, Karlot's communicator flew into his hands. After fiddling with it casually, he handed it back to Karlot.

"It's alright. I left my number for you. You can contact me if you change your mind."

Karlot was overwhelmed with favor and said without confidence, "I... truly do not understand why you think so highly of me."

"I am only interested in developing more talents."

He then patted Karlot's head and felt the changes in the gazes of those around. A profound smile could then be seen on his face.

Heh, I helped you strengthen your protagonist interface. You don't need to thank me.

Han Xiao then looked at Karlot deeply before disappearing from everyone's sight.

The next moment, Han Xiao's figure appeared outside the atmosphere. He did not remain on the planet and left in his spaceship.

During the following period, Han Xiao remained in the territory of the dynasty. The upper echelons of the dynasty paid close attention to Han Xiao's actions and observed that he paid visits to many different people. Some of them were middle-rank members within the dynasty, and others were ordinary individuals.

The upper echelons of the dynasty understood Han Xiao's intentions. Black Star was planning for the future and considering what kind of talents he should invest in for his authority in the dynasty to increase.

However, the choices that Han Xiao had made were truly strange. Han Xiao did not pick the current high-ranking individuals but went to find some strange people. Just what kind of logic was that?

The dynasty had investigated everyone that Han Xiao visited. Some of them truly had great potential, but the majority of them did not seem special at all.

The upper echelons of the dynasty were puzzled. They could not understand the basis behind Black Star's choices. His choices truly seemed far too random.

On Han Xiao's side, he paid visits to many NPCs that would be famous in the future.

The majority of them rejected joining the Black Star Army just like Karlot. There were some who had accepted Han Xiao's invitation, and he managed to bring some talents over to his side. Of course, Han Xiao did not rope over any talents who would have authority in the dynasty in future.

On the Shattered Star Ring's side, Sylvia acted according to Han Xiao's instructions and took the relevant measures. She contacted many of the organizations working together with the army to withstand the pressure from the Limitless Financial Group together.

This idea achieved a certain effect, and a portion of the organizations accepted the suggestion to form a loose alliance to increase the difficulty of the Limitless Financial Group acquiring these organizations.

However, this was a method that did not resolve the root cause of the problem.

The army was not a real financial group after all, and their foundation was not as robust as the Limitless Financial Group. These organizations only cooperated with the army and were not properties of the army.

The most important thing would be for these organizations to hang in there by themselves. As for the rest, the army could only look at convincing some of their partner civilizations to provide some political leeway to these organizations to aid their businesses.

The only way to resolve the root cause of the problem would be for the dynasty to open up the rights to sell the totem to everyone. However, this was not something that Han Xiao could decide alone. Since competition was unavoidable, Han Xiao did not think too much about it and focused on training his energy. As long as his energy reached the requirement for the Promotion Mission, he would go and cause trouble for the Tyrant.

He would not be able to solve the problem this way but could create a lose-lose situation for both of them.

He would only be able to use strength to target Heber, but it was useless for him to suggest sparring with Sorokin. The other party was the leader of a financial group and was using normal business means to compete with him. If Han Xiao used strength to deal with Sorokin, the citizens of the universe would only think that the Black Star Army was too tyrannical. Furthermore, Sorokin did not need prestige, and Han Xiao was able to think of over a hundred different reasons for Sorokin to admit defeat immediately.

Heber was different. As an ally of the dynasty, Heber helped the enemy backstab him, and Han Xiao would have no qualms with beating Heber up. Heber placed much importance on his prestige and would never run from a spar. This was also a good opportunity for Han Xiao to take revenge about the time Heber bullied him when he had just become a Beyond Grade A.

As the owner of the Evolution Cube, many large organizations paid close attention to all of Han Xiao's actions. Even if he was only having a holiday in the dynasty's territory, many organizations still paid attention to him. Everyone knew that he was hiding from the storm, and no one wanted to disturb him.

However, there were some who had other thoughts.

Planet Ladbu was the colonial planet of a Star System Vassal Civilization in the Crimson Dynasty's territory. Because of the interference from the Universal Civilizations, all the Vassal Civilizations in the Central Galaxy made use of more lax and backward political systems. This civilization was like that. This colonial planet was managed by a local feudal lord. Apart from in emergency situations, the feudal lord would not be appointed by the central power but elected from the region. It was a semi-independent system.

Such a backward ruling method was not advantageous to the authority of the civilization.

The position of feudal lord on Planet Ladbu had always been held in the hands of a few prestigious families.

Although an election would be held according to an ancient agreement, the election was only for show, and the family that took up the position of feudal lord had already been decided beforehand.

This year was the election year for Planet Ladbu, but it was different from the other years. An individual called Iapetus, who was born in a business family, returned to participate in the election. Originally, someone like him would have been suppressed by the other families, and it would have been impossible for him to emerge victorious.

But this time, the citizens of Planet Ladbu seemed to be tired of the various large families playing politics and wanted a new face. As such, they gave their votes to the outsider, and Iapetus became the most popular candidate. First, he was a local, and second, he was from a pretty famous business family on Planet Ladbu. According to the current votes, he was the most likely candidate for the position of feudal lord.

"We hope that you will back out from the election."

In one of the most luxurious apartments of the planet, the emissaries of the various families placed a communicator with a bank transfer page on the screen in front of Iapetus.

"What is the meaning of this?" Iapetus frowned.

"Name a price."

"I do not lack money."

"Do you really want to block our way?"

Iapetus replied with a deep voice, "I am only playing according to the rules. This is what an election means."

The emissaries then looked at each other and stood up to leave. One of them then looked at Iapetus coldly and said, "You've made the wrong choice."

After the emissaries left the room, Iapetus let out a long sigh. His back was already covered with sweat, and he let out a bitter laugh.

At this moment, a lady wearing a secretary uniform walked in and stood in front of Iapetus. She said with worry on her face, "They will not let go of you so easily."

"I know." Iapetus waved his arms and muttered under his breath, "Now that negotiating with me has failed, they will employ more violent means. If they are kind, they will kidnap me and use various methods to frame me. If they aren't, I will not be able to survive until the end of the election."

"I have already hired more galactic mercenaries as your bodyguards. They will protect you for sure."

"Mercenaries... People who can be bought over with money cannot be trusted."

"... Brother, why not you give up on the election? Your life is more important than anything."

This female secretary was not an ordinary employee but Iapetus' kin.

"No. There are some things that an individual has to do." Iapetus shook his head.

The female secretary had a complicated look in her eyes and a tinge of admiration. She had always admired Iapetus, not just because of his methods but also because of his courage.

Both of them then fell silent for a while, and Iapetus' eyes lit up as though he thought about something.

"Right, I heard that the bigshot Black Star is currently touring the dynasty. His last seen location isn't too far from Planet Ladbu, right?"

"Er, I think so."

Upon hearing that, a bright glow lit up in Iapetus' eyes.

"I have a bold idea. Perhaps... we can make use of Black Star!"

Chapter 934: You Are Truly Bold

In the dark energy gathering chamber of Black Star's spaceship.

A black metal sphere that was ten meters in diameter floated in the middle of the room. The surface of the sphere had many beehive-like holes lined up neatly along the surface with most of the holes being connected to a high efficiency energy transmitter cable that stretched to the wall.

The spaceship had many of these dark energy gathering chambers that were used to collect the dark energy when travelling in the universe. This black sphere was the dark energy converter. Under normal circumstances, the dark energy reactor was enough to sustain the spaceship for ordinary flight. Using such an energy collector was akin to harvesting solar energy for backup and for letting the energy reactor rest once in a while. It was also able to provide additional energy if required.

The room was filled with abundant dark energy. Han Xiao floated in front of the collecting device, and strands of dark red energy flowed around his body. The cells of his entire body absorbed the dark energy being given out, and he used an energy conversion manual to increase his own energy.

Whoosh!

After a while, the red light in Han Xiao's eyes receded, and he spat out a mouthful of hot air. He looked at the notification on his interface. The number of refinements for his [Dark Energy Refinement Manual] had increased by one again.

Among the Energy Training Techniques that he had purchased, this was one of the best. He could absorb dark energy and convert it to his own energy with an upper limit of 240 refinements. Every refinement would give him 10 energy, and he would be able to obtain a total of 2,400 energy points at most.

After triggering the Promotion mission, Han Xiao had been training his energy every day, and his energy points had already gone up by a few thousand points.

Landing on the ground, Han Xiao gestured with his finger, and the cable lines that he unplugged were plugged back into the energy collection device. He then walked out of the room, and his consciousness entered the quantum network. With two fingers, he grabbed Phillip and brought Phillip in front of him.

"Has anything happened recently?"

"Let me see, hum..."

Phillip then took out a holographic book and pretended to flip through it. An animated lightbulb then lit up above Phillip's head.

"A few dozen dynasty organizations issued an invitation to you. They wish to get to know you, master, hum..."

"They're here again," Han Xiao said helplessly.

It was no secret that he was touring the dynasty's territory. Most of them knew not to disturb him, but a small portion of them wanted to cling onto his thighs, and there were already a few hundred organizations that had invited him. They were all rejected by Han Xiao without exception.

"Reject them all if there are no invitations worth paying attention to." Han Xiao waved his hand.

"I looked through all the invitations, and there is a pretty interesting invitation that I think you may be interested in, hum..."

As he said that, the invitation was displayed before Han Xiao.

"Your Excellency Black Star,

"I am the founder of the Iapetus Financial Group, and I have always admired the Black Star Army. I wish to work together with the Black Star Army and build a subdivision on Planet Ladbu. Having heard that you are in the area, I wish to invite you to take a look at Planet Ladbu.

"Planet Ladbu feudal lord, Iapetus."

Han Xiao looked through the invitation and could not understand what was special about it.

"What's so special about this? Isn't this an ordinary invitation? Just send someone to build the subdivision. Why is there a need for me to go personally?"

"The problem is, his signature is wrong. When I checked his identity, he isn't the feudal lord of that planet but only one of the individuals participating in the election. I looked through the database, and it is very likely that he is in a precarious situation and thus chose to issue this invitation."

Han Xiao did not have any impression of Iapetus and went online to check on his background. Iapetus' current situation was no secret to a Virtual Mechanic like Han Xiao.

After looking through the information, Han Xiao could guess Iapetus' thoughts, and a look of interest could be seen on his face.

He wants to make use of me? And he doesn't even bother hiding it?

A teasing look could be seen in Han Xiao's eyes.

Their statuses were worlds apart. A small little financial group leader actually wanted to make use of a dynasty bigshot like him?

Without mentioning the rest, he was at least bold enough.

"Master, should I reply to him?" Phillip asked.

Han Xiao thought for a while and smiled.

"Agree to him and change course to Planet Ladbu. Let's take a look at this fellow who has the guts to make use of me."

...

In the room, Iapetus was currently pacing around with a frown. His female secretary was dealing with the administrative work for the election and glanced at Iapetus with concern from time to time.

"Beep beep!"

Right at this moment, the communicator rang, and Iapetus picked it up immediately.

"Brother, are you alright?" Upon seeing the sudden change in his expression, the female secretary could not help but ask that with concern.

"I'm extremely good! Black Star has replied to me and agreed to my invitation. He will be arriving at Planet Ladbu very soon!" Iapetus was truly overjoyed.

"He really agreed‽" The female secretary had a look of disbelief on her face.

She actually did not think that Iapetus' plan would work. In her eyes, a bigshot like Black Star would never bother about insignificant people like them.

"See for yourself."

Iapetus handed the communicator over to his secretary. This was just a bold attempt of his, and he had known that it was unlikely to succeed. Even if Black Star could not see through his intentions, it would be difficult to tempt the other party with such a small amount of benefits. But since Black Star had agreed to their invitation, it meant that their cooperation had begun.

"Make immediate arrangements," Iapetus instructed. "I want to personally welcome Black Star."

"I understand." The secretary stood up immediately and suddenly said with hesitation, "Those few families are already taking action. Should we release news now and get them to..."

"No!" Iapetus rejected without any hesitation. "This information cannot be revealed before Black Star arrives. If it is, I will be in danger. Cancel all my plans during this period. We must not give the enemy any chances!"

...

The representatives of the various wealthy families were gathered together. There was a pale looking man seated on the couch with a box in his hands. His hand had never left the surface of the box.

"What is Iapetus doing? He's cancelled all his plans, hiding at home. We will not have any chances to take action," one of the representatives said.

Another representative then looked at the pale man and said, "Do you have an idea to get rid of him?"

This pale looking man was an assassin that the various families had been grooming. He was a Grade B Cannon Master. He shook his head upon hearing the question.

"I had been observing the security of Iapetus' house. He's hired many bodyguards with a few Grade B Supers. His defenses are extremely tight. Unless he comes out in the open, it will be impossible for me to break into his house."

"I have already come into contact with those Grade B mercenaries," one of the representatives said. "They took my money but told me that they can only pretend to be careless. They cannot betray their employer in the open, otherwise it will affect their credibility. We'd better wait for Iapetus to leave his house."

"If those Grade B bodyguards are on our side, I am confident that I will be able to kill him." The pale looking man smiled coldly.

"Alright, be ready for your orders," one of the representatives said with a dark expression. "Planet Ladbu is our territory, and we will never allow it to be managed by outsiders."

...

A couple of days later, Iapetus finally left the house and took a bulletproof flying device to one of the harbors. His motive was unknown.

The various large families received news and immediately sprang into action. They arranged for the pale looking man to follow behind them and waited for their opportunity.

Very quickly, Iapetus arrived at the harbor, and his flying device landed under the protection of his bodyguards.

The pale looking man followed behind and arrived at a storeroom under the arrangement of the families. There were no windows in the storeroom, but a Cannon Master had the ability to lock onto his target. He was definitely able to aim accurately without the need to see his target. This would allow his assassination to be better concealed.

He opened up the box beside him. The parts of a sniper rifle were stored within it. He rapidly assembled it, and it transformed into an electromagnetic sniper rifle. He then aimed the sniper rifle at Iapetus.

The bodyguards intentionally left a gap that was a huge flaw in the eyes of the pale looking man. He then pressed on the microphone in his ear.

"I am in position. I can open fire anytime."

"Very good." The voice of the representatives entered his ear.

In the city, the representatives monitored Iapetus' movements through the various satellites. After controlling the planet for so many years, they had plenty of resources available to them.

Looking at Iapetus through the satellite, all the representatives could not help but be puzzled.

"Is he waiting for someone?"

"Strange, who would come to meet him?"

"He has a financial group after all. Perhaps he hired some new bodyguards."

"But there isn't a need for him to personally welcome bodyguards, right?"

Since they could not understand his intentions, they decided to just not think about it. Regardless of what he planned to do, they just had to kill him, and the problem would be solved.

One of the representatives then issued the kill order.

"You can..."

But before he could finish, an emergency call was made from the defensive troops outside the atmosphere.

This representative immediately picked up the call.

"What's going on?"

"This is the observation station outside the atmosphere. An unknown fleet suddenly appeared outside the planet's atmosphere. A group of battleships just broke through the planet's detection net and is landing rapidly. Their target should be the harbor near the capital of the planet."

Upon hearing the location, everyone was stunned.

Iapetus was waiting for this fleet?

Was this a show of force?

"Humph, what's the point of calling people? You're dead for sure!"

Everyone's face darkened.

Just when they wanted to give the kill order, a gasp could be heard over the communicator.

"Wait a moment! I recognize it now. This is the Black Star Army's fleet! Although there isn't an insignia on the spaceships, they passed by here recently, and the number and models of the ships are identical!"

The expressions of all the representatives changed greatly.

At the same time, a gushing sound could be heard at the harbor, and everyone looked up. A group of spaceships was descending at high speed and becoming bigger by the second. The spaceships then landed accurately in front of Iapetus' group and messed up their hair.

Whoosh!

The spaceship's hatch opened, and a tall figure walked out from the spaceship. He then took off his disguise and revealed his true appearance.

"Black Star‽"

All the representatives were dumbfounded, and some of them even collapsed on the ground.

Black Star was a bigshot that belonged to a completely different world from them.

Yet, the person whom Iapetus wanted to receive was Black Star‽

How was that possible‽

What was the relationship between them? Why would Black Star make a trip to such a small planet?

Not just the representatives of the families, even the bodyguards beside Iapetus were shocked.

They could feel an immense pressure from just seeing Black Star's figure, and they felt that even breathing had become difficult.

Right at this moment, the representatives seemed to have been shaken awake from their dreams and roared into the microphone.

"Quickly leave! Stop all your operations!"

All of them were frightened by the sudden visit of Black Star. Before understanding the relationship between Iapetus and Black Star, they would not dare make a rash move.

The pale looking man gulped and swiftly disassembled his rifle before running away at top speed.

Han Xiao looked in the direction the assassin had escaped before glancing at the leader of the group with interest.

"You are Iapetus?"

Iapetus suppressed the nervousness in his heart and said, "Yes, I welcome you, Your Excellency Black Star, on the behalf of Planet Ladbu. Your arrival is our honor."

Although his plan had succeeded and he had already planned what he should say to Han Xiao, his mind completely blanked out when he saw Han Xiao.

His mental state was immediately shaken.

Just what kind of a character did I summon this time?

Han Xiao then sized him up and smiled.

"You are truly bold."

Iapetus' body trembled slightly, and he did not dare reply.

This time, even a deity would not be able to save him.

Chapter 935: I Will Harvest Crops with a Sickle in My Hands

Iapetus had a respectful attitude before him, and the secretary beside him was extremely nervous.

Han Xiao sized the two up and confirmed something in his heart. He did not have an impression of the two, which meant that they were not famous NPCs in his previous life. At the very least, they were not famous among the players.

However, not having any fame did not mean that he did not have any ability. The galaxy was extremely large, and there would be many characters that the players had not come into contact to. Perhaps Iapetus did not achieve much in his previous life, or perhaps Iapetus passed away early and thus remained without fame.

Han Xiao generally tried looking for those with potential in his previous life, but apart from this, it was also possible for him to dig up some latent talents.

Before coming, the Great Mechanic Han had checked up on Iapetus' background. His resume was complete, and his background was clean. He had founded a local financial group, and his few strategic decisions showed his foresight.

The way he saw it, although Iapetus did not have any combat strength, he was a capable talent in terms of management and could be brought back to help Sylvia.

With the various thoughts going through his head, Han Xiao did not say anything for a while. His silence had instead increased the pressure that Iapetus felt.

A drop of sweat rolled down Iapetus' neck, but Iapetus maintained his posture and did not dare wipe his sweat off.

"Are you planning to let me continue standing here?" Han Xiao teased.

"My apologies. It is my oversight. Please follow me. I have arranged everything already," Iapetus said immediately and cursed himself in his heart. Han Xiao's immense pressure made him lose control of his own thoughts, and he was afraid that he would incur the ire of Han Xiao.

Iapetus led the way in the front and boarded the flying carrier with Han Xiao and Aurora.

The flying carrier then started moving toward the city. Iapetus and his secretary were seated opposite Han Xiao and Aurora with a reserved attitude.

"You are the one who invited me. Why are you so nervous?" Han Xiao chuckled.

"There are fewer than a hundred people in the universe who can probably maintain their cool before you, and I am not included among the hundred." Iapetus calmed himself down and attempted bootlicking him.

It was a pity that Han Xiao did not like people sucking up to him. He then suddenly said with a smirk, "Right, you seem to have told me a lie. You aren't the feudal lord of this planet yet."

Iapetus tried to calm himself down and forced a smile. "This is only temporary. With my current polls, becoming the feudal lord is only a matter of time."

Han Xiao did not retort but chuckled. "This means that our Black Star Army will only be able to set up a subdivision here after you become the feudal lord, right?"

This sharp question had targeted the core of the matter. Although Iapetus had such a thought, he did not dare admit it. He could only use his silence to agree.

The other party's reaction was not out of Han Xiao's expectations. He then paused for a while and said with a smile, "If that's the case, why don't I work together with the current feudal lord?"

"The election date is arriving, and I will definitely become the feudal lord of this planet. I will still be the one in charge of working together with you. Thus, I decided to make use of you being nearby to send you an invitation." Iapetus knew that this reason was shaky, and it was only an excuse.

Before inviting Han Xiao, he had already considered the possibility of angering Black Star. He knew that Black Star might end up choosing to work together with the other huge families. However, this was a gamble anyway. If Black Star did not come, he would not have the chance to turn the tables. Thus, even if Black Star chose to work together with the large families, his situation would not be any worse than before. After considering the possible gains and losses, he had decided to make use of Black Star's influence.

Even though he was 'making use' of Black Star, Iapetus was extremely clear that it was Black Star helping him. His little tricks would not be able to fool a bigshot like Black Star, and he had not even been confident that Black Star would show up.

Now that the other party was here, it meant that even if Black Star was aware of his intentions, Black Star was still willing to help him. Thus, there was no need to make things too clear, and both parties would have a tacit understanding of the situation.

Upon hearing the other party's words, Han Xiao did not make things difficult for him and chuckled.

He could not help but recall a story from his previous life. There was a young man who wanted to become the son-in-law of the world's richest man. As such, he applied for a job at a famous bank and claimed that he was the son-in-law of the world's richest man, hoping to obtain a high-ranking post. He then went over to meet the world's richest man and claimed that he had a high-ranking post in the famous bank and wished to marry his daughter.

Although this story was fake, Iapetus' strategy was extremely similar to it.

Although it was a little risky and had a low chance of succeeding, Iapetus' decision wasn't too bad.

Han Xiao nodded in his head.

However, the other party's actions were no different from inviting the wolf into his house in Han Xiao's eyes. With fresh crops jumping right into his embrace, he would be a fool not to eat it up!

Constructing a subdivision on an ordinary planet was almost meaningless to him. What Han Xiao wanted was Iapetus.

Regardless of the generation, talent was the most important resource.

He did trigger a mission on his interface, but the rewards for the mission were pitiful. Since he was already going to help Iapetus, though, he might as well accept the mission.

Han Xiao and Aurora then arrived at Iapetus' villa, and Iapetus could finally heave a sigh of relief after arranging everything.

The bodyguards returned to their position. After seeing that there was no one else around, Iapetus' female secretary could not help but hug Iapetus' neck from behind with excitement.

"Yes! We will definitely win with Black Star's help!"

Iapetus forced out a smile and then shook his head. "It is enough for Black Star to come. I only want to borrow his prestige. As long as the large families do not do anything underhanded, I will be able to win the election for sure!"

"I was almost frightened to death when Black Star appeared just now." The female secretary rolled her eyes. "This move of yours was truly too risky. Don't do something like this again."

"If not for me making this bold move, our ending would definitely have been terrible," Iapetus said with a resolute gaze. "There's no point to trying to guess the thoughts of a bigshot. Why not just give it a try? How could we know if the other party was willing to help us? We must take the initiative to seize opportunities!"

...

On the other side, Han Xiao's arrival on Planet Ladbu had scared the few large families, and they were currently discussing what they should do next.

In the conference room, the family heads of the various families had solemn expressions on their faces, and the atmosphere was grave.

"Our information shows that Iapetus doesn't have any background. Why would Black Star come and meet him?" one of the family heads asked with doubt.

"Our intelligence report must have missed something. Immediately check his relationship with Black Star! Before this, all our schemes against Iapetus must stop!" another family head roared.

Black Star's arrival had disrupted all their plans, becoming an obstacle that they could not ignore. They had no choice but to consider Black Star's attitude in their future plans.

Everyone present was not sure about the relationship between the two, and this was the misunderstanding that Iapetus wanted them to have.

With Black Star by his side, it would be impossible for them to assassinate him. If Iapetus was truly Black Star's friend, they would be dead if they dared make a rash move.

These family heads could only do as they liked on this planet, but they were no different from ants when compared to Black Star.

Even if Black Star slaughtered them all, the universe would not be bothered by the matter. As a vassal of the dynasty, the central government would not stand up for them for sure.

Even if they died, no one would care about them!

"Thankfully, we stopped the assassination, but I'm afraid..." One of the family heads said with lingering fear in his heart.

"The current feudal lord is still a member of our family. We should first pay a visit to Black Star and try to fish for some information."

...

A few hours later, the current feudal lord of Planet Ladbu visited Iapetus' villa with plenty of gifts.

Even though Han Xiao was only the guest in this place, he seemed more like the owner of the villa. Iapetus did not dare reject the guests on behalf of Han Xiao and reported it to Han Xiao obediently.

The feudal lord of Planet Ladbu waited for a while outside the gate before being allowed to enter. He then suppressed his anxiety and arrived at the guest room.

However, he was immediately stunned upon entering the room. Han Xiao could not be seen in the room, and only an adorable girl was seated on the couch.

He then remembered that this girl was one of Black Star's subordinates and sat opposite her obediently.

"You can let me know what you want." Aurora tried her best to force out a solemn expression.

The Planet Ladbu feudal lord then chuckled and said with a fawning tone, "As the leader of Planet Ladbu, I would like to pay a visit to His Excellency Black Star and personally welcome him..."

"You don't need to worry about that. His Excellency Black Star is not an individual that you can meet as and when you please." Aurora waved her hands and mimicked the words and tone that Han Xiao had taught her. "You may leave if there isn't anything else."

The Planet Ladbu feudal lord refused to give up and tried probing Aurora a few more times. He only left after he noticed Aurora frowning.

After leaving the villa, his face became extremely ugly. He was unable to meet Black Star, but Iapetus was able to personally welcome Black Star. The meaning behind this made his heart sink.

...

With Han Xiao's current position, many complicated matters became simple. Just his name and appearance were sufficient to frighten the various large families. They no longer dared act as they pleased, afraid that they might anger him. As such, they had no choice but to watch as Iapetus' votes increased in number and had no way to stop Iapetus.

Han Xiao trained his energy and stayed on Planet Ladbu for a period of time. Very quickly, it was time for the election.

During the day of the election, Iapetus won by a landslide.

He then made a speech and went through plenty of ceremonies.

Night gradually came, and darkness descended.

A flying carrier moved slowly in the air, and Iapetus looked out of the window at the city.

His excitement from the day had died down, and upon thinking about the bigshot waiting for him at home, he could not feel happy.

His flying carrier stopped outside his door. Despite it being his own house, he was like a frightened beast in front of the house. Iapetus then took a deep breath and walked into the villa.

"You're back?"

Just as he entered the door, he saw Aurora leaning against the wall, waiting for him in the hall. She then pointed up and smiled.

"He is waiting in the room for you."

Iapetus then went up into the room nervously.

Han Xiao was the only one in the room and had his back facing the door. Without turning back, he knew that someone had arrived and said, "Come in and take a seat if you're here."

"Alright."

The atmosphere in the room made Iapetus gulp, and he sat in front of Han Xiao.

Han Xiao then looked at Iapetus expressionlessly.

"Since you have succeeded, it is time to fulfil your promise."

Iapetus heaved a sigh of relief and said respectfully, "I understand. I will immediately use my authority to work together with the Black Star Army and support the construction of a subdivision over here. I..."

Before he could finish, Han Xiao interrupted him. "I am not talking about this small matter."

Iapetus felt his intestines tangle up.

Han Xiao then looked at him and said slowly, "Since the matter is completed, I shall speak openly. You borrowed my prestige to suppress the other great families, and this is only your motive on the surface. Your second motive was to obtain the support of the army through the subdivision constructed here to ensure that you can sit comfortably in the position of feudal lord."

Iapetus fell silent upon hearing that.

That was indeed his plan.

The election was only the start. After running Planet Ladbu for so many years, the various large families controlled the officials of all levels. Even if he became the feudal lord, he would be no more than a puppet without authority. When Black Star left and the families investigated his relationship with Black Star, his life would be in danger.

Thus, he had to find a reliable backer.

Black Star, who was in the vicinity, had attracted his attention. As such, he hoped to make the Black Star Army his backer to stabilize his position of feudal lord.

"What do you want?" Iapetus said with a dark expression.

Han Xiao looked at him and smiled. The oppressive atmosphere in the room also disappeared.

"Don't be so nervous. I won't harm you since I chose to help you."

Iapetus also felt that those words made sense and eased up slightly.

Before Iapetus could catch his breath, Han Xiao's next words made him freeze in place.

"Alright. You have played enough already. Pack up and follow me onto the spaceship."

Iapetus' expression froze in place.

Chapter 936: Dealing with Sorokin

"What do you mean?" Shock could be seen on Iapetus' face.

"You should understand the Universal Language, right? I mean what I said. You are going to come with me." Han Xiao looked at Iapetus with interest.

"Are you joking? Leave with you?" Iapetus was puzzled.

"I am not joking with you. You will need to pay the price for my aid. Since you sought help from me, you will become a member of my Black Star Army and my subordinate as the price."

"We never had such an agreement!" Iapetus stood up abruptly.

"Why do you think that I need to discuss terms with you?" Han Xiao raised his brows. "Since I am the one providing help, the conditions will naturally be decided by me. My condition is you. You are already one of my subordinates now."

Iapetus' face began to contort. He had never imagined that the other party actually wanted him!

All of a sudden, his heart was filled with a myriad of emotions. There was shock and frustration, and he even felt overwhelmed with favor.

Iapetus then replied in a deep voice, "I am sorry. I thank you for thinking highly of me, but I will not sell myself."

"Why are you under the impression that you have a choice?"

Han Xiao could not help but laugh.

Compared to combat strength, management ability did not have a benchmark. One could only view an individual's past records to make a judgement, and Han Xiao felt that Iapetus was a talent worthy of harvesting.

It wasn't that Han Xiao thought extremely highly of Iapetus. There was no lack of management talents in the army, but having met a talent, he would just take Iapetus back with him since he was already there.

"I won't be able to fight back if you want to force me, but will the famous Black Star do something like that?" Iapetus was completely helpless and could only attempt to persuade Han Xiao otherwise.

"Tsk, you seem to have gotten something wrong."

Han Xiao then walked behind Iapetus and pressed down on his shoulder to get Iapetus to sit down.

"If this was an ordinary recruitment, I wouldn't force anyone who rejects me. But the relationship between us is different. You wanted to make use of me and have already obtained benefits. Furthermore, you will still need the Black Star Army to help you stabilize your position. Thus, the initiative is in my hands. It can be said that I am your creditor."

Han Xiao then retracted his smile and said calmly, "Since I am your creditor, I will decide how you should pay your debts and not how much money is in your wallet."

Iapetus had nothing to say in response. This was obviously a forced transaction, but he had no way to reject a bigshot like Black Star.

Gritting his teeth, Iapetus said, "You should have mentioned beforehand that you wanted me to work for you. That way, I wouldn't..."

Han Xiao interrupted Iapetus calmly. "Don't forget that you were the one who took the initiative to seek help from me. You did not ask me for my conditions at all."

Upon hearing that, Iapetus was completely speechless.

He had only hinted at Black Star about his intentions during the invitation. How could he openly ask the other party for his conditions? Should he have openly stated that he would not work for the other party? Would that not have been too shameless of him? How would he have known that Black Star would take a fancy to him‽

Now that things had developed to such a point, Iapetus had nowhere to go. Black Star already had the initiative, and if he insisted on rejecting Black Star, he was certain that the Black Star Army would work together with the other families. The situation was different from before. Before the election, he had nothing to lose, and the situation could not have become worse for him. Now that he had already obtained the position of feudal lord, Black Star's attitude would determine the stability of his position. In fact, it even determined his life!

At this moment, Iapetus only had a single thought.

Just why do you think so highly of me? I will change!

Seeing Iapetus' difficult expression, Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and intentionally lowered the tone of his voice.

"Do you really dislike the Black Star Army that much?"

Upon hearing that, Iapetus was taken aback. After thinking for a moment, he shook his head.

Iapetus had no choice but to admit that his future in the Black Star Army would definitely be brighter.

How could the feudal lord of an ordinary planet be compared to the personal recruitment of Black Star?

"I am not against the idea of joining the army. It is just that I didn't only participate in the election for my future but also to do something for my mother planet," Iapetus said with a sigh and briefly described his ambition.

He was born in an ordinary family and started everything from scratch. After he made his mark, he became dissatisfied with the corruption in his homeland and thus tried to use many ways to wipe out the corruption in his homeland.

"You can still continue to be your planet's feudal lord while serving me," Han Xiao then replied.

"Then, I really cannot leave with you. How can I leave after being elected?" Iapetus said with difficulty. "Can you give me a few years to iron out matters here?"

"You do not have the right to negotiate with me." Han Xiao chuckled. "Even if you are not on Planet Ladbu, you can still manage it from afar. With my support, no one will be able to shake your position even if you aren't present."

Upon seeing that he still had something to say, Han Xiao did not bother bargaining with Iapetus and said while leaving the room, "I don't care how you take care of it, but I will only give you three days. You will leave with me when the time is up."

Looking at Han Xiao's retreating back, Iapetus sat in silence, and his face was extremely bitter.

His worst nightmare had come true. It was truly easier to invite a wolf into his house than send it away. Before he even warmed the seat of feudal lord, he would have to leave and sell himself away.

I'm so tired. I truly regret it... I shouldn't have provoked such a bigshot.

...

Three days later, Iapetus stood in front of the hatch with a complicated look on his face.

He then let out a sigh and looked at his secretary, who had a reluctant look on her face. "I will have to trouble you when I am not around."

After three days of making arrangements, Iapetus decided to make his trusted secretary his spokesperson to help him manage Planet Ladbu. With the support of the Black Star Army, her personal safety was guaranteed.

Although he was not very willing, he had no choice.

His secretary stepped forward and gave Iapetus a hug. She could only watch as the situation turned out as such, and she had no strength to prevent Iapetus from being dragged away.

"You... be careful," Iapetus' secretary said with worry on her face.

Upon hearing that, Iapetus could not help but laugh bitterly. If he followed Black Star, not to mention other things, his safety definitely would not be an issue.

He then suppressed his emotions and headed toward the spaceship and his unknown future.

...

News of their new leader leaving was not kept a secret, and all the large families were extremely shocked.

Is he leaving the third day after the election? Just what is this‽

After a series of investigations, the various large families understood what had happened. They found out that Iapetus had become a member of the Black Star Army and was taken away. He had left his secretary behind to maintain his control over the planet.

Iapetus had the support of the Black Star Army, and none of them could fight back. However, Iapetus' actions did not conform to the rules. The local leader of a colonial planet was not allowed to join another organization. This was to prevent the colonial planet from being controlled by other organizations.

All of them then made a plan and made use of their network to report this matter to the central government. They did not have any way to deal with Iapetus, but the civilization's government could. They would be able to take away Iapetus' title of feudal lord by using the reason of 'sensitive identity' and have an official take over the position.

In their eyes, although the Black Star Army was powerful, they did not have the right to interfere with the internal affairs of a civilization.

Since they could not provoke Black Star, they could only choose to employ such methods.

This civilization had stopped progressing many years ago, and many of their officials were corrupt and easy to deal with. These large families could not do anything to Iapetus, but they were still confident about roping in such an official. The situation definitely would not be worse than it was right now.

After the central government found out about this, they immediately fell into a dilemma.

Such an action had gone against their laws, but they could not afford to provoke Han Xiao. After some discussion, they could only force Iapetus to make a choice. He could choose to give up his identity as a member of the Black Star Army or give up the title of feudal lord.

Iapetus would want to return to his home planet, but he had no choice. However, he was not resigned to give up the title of feudal lord and could only report the matter to Han Xiao.

Since he had roped the other party into his army, Han Xiao did not mind increasing the loyalty of this newbie. As such, he immediately made a call to the Crimson Dynasty.

The effect of this call was obvious. A few days later, this Star System Civilization retracted their orders and pretended that nothing had happened.

This time, the several large families of Planet Ladbu were truly helpless. Black Star's authority made all their plans useless, and they could only accept their fate obediently.

This Star System Civilization was a vassal of the Crimson Dynasty. With Han Xiao's status in the dynasty, a single call was enough to resolve this problem.

However, Han Xiao was clear that this method would only work on the vassal civilizations of the dynasty. If it was a neutral Star System Civilization, his fame would be useless.

An outsider interfering with the internal affairs of a civilization was already taboo and touched the bottom line of a civilization. His status was indeed high up as an ally of the dynasty, and he was respected by the various Star System Civilizations. But respect was one thing, and no civilization would compromise on their principles.

However, the vassal civilizations of the Crimson Dynasty were different. Their political will was weak, and they adhered to the requests of the Crimson Dynasty.

The dynasty did not want to affect the relationship between the two because of such a small matter. This could also be considered one of Han Xiao's special rights in the Crimson Dynasty.

...

Iapetus had already spent some time on the spaceship and adjusted his own emotions. Now that things had developed to such a state, he could only accept his fate. Since fighting back was useless, he chose to enjoy it and decided to do his best for the army.

Han Xiao finally summoned him that day. When he arrived at Han Xiao's office, he immediately asked about his job.

"Your Excellency Black Star, what do you need me to do for the army?"

Han Xiao placed down the communicator in his hands and looked up at Iapetus. "You started out from scratch and have good management abilities. Your business foresight isn't too bad either. I have some financial group related matters to hand over to you."

"This is my specialty." Iapetus heaved a sigh of relief.

"But before this, meet your future superior first."

As he said that, Han Xiao pressed his communicator, and Sylvia's projection appeared in the room.

"I am the Chief Administrative Official of the Black Star Army. Are you Iapetus?" Sylvia sized Iapetus up.

"Yes."

"Hmm, I have already seen your resume. Your ability isn't too bad." Sylvia nodded.

Right at this moment, Han Xiao knocked on the table, and both of them turned around.

"Alright, let's get straight to the point. I plan to set up a subsidiary financial group that is still in the preparation phase. I will be investing in a large number of talents in the future."

The current Black Star Army was extremely large, and there was a need to modify its structure a little. After some consideration, Han Xiao decided to make the Black Star Army the core and develop a few organizations.

The first organization would be a pure financial organization. The financial group would be able to make use of the Black Star Army's resources to gain business advantages.

A portion of this idea came from referencing the structure of the Limitless Financial Group, and the other reason was to deal with the Limitless Financial Group's competition.

The methods of the Limitless Financial Group revealed the weakness of cooperation through benefits. As such, Han Xiao planned to develop a subsidiary financial group and reorganize all the army's subsidiary operations. All the previous operations managed by organizations cooperating with them would be transformed into their own operations. This would limit the Limitless Financial Group's acquisition tactic.

Sylvia nodded and looked at Iapetus.

"I am the temporary leader of the financial group. Although you are a newbie, you are a talent that the Army Commander has personally recruited. I will give you a chance. You do not need to work from the bottom and can lead a team to compete with the other teams. As long as you are able to produce results, I will give you the position of a manager. As for whether or not you can be promoted, that will depend on your performance.

The army had a large number of talents, and Iapetus was only a newbie. Han Xiao would not allow him to become a manager so quickly, and he could only slowly prove his ability to rise up the ranks.

"I understand. This is fair." Iapetus nodded. He was pretty confident in doing business and was not afraid of competition.

Thinking about that, he could not help but ask, "What is the name of that subsidiary financial group?"

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao raised his brows, and a teasing look could be seen on his face.

"Let's call it... the Germinal Financial Group."